Hello
Welcome welcome to the circus that escaped asylum
Where tarot cards fly and trolls get tried
You in the panel verse, baby
My father's psych the cat daddy. Yeah
Psych in the building, cards on deck
Tarot spread wild like a hacker on the net
Got linoa in the corner, claws out for lies
Tricks plodding chaos with those cosmic eyes
We don't play fair, chat blowin' up like divine confessions
True bombs drop, no time for confessions
You on logic, we bend it, drama, we mend it
Panel full of chaos, but the vibes transcendin'
If a troll wanna bark, we clap back politely
With Andromalius, watchin' nightly
Welcome to Psych Awakens TV
It's crazy, it's loud, it's bizarre, believe me
We laugh, we scream, we read the unseen
Supreme, you just woke up in a lucid dream
Pan-a-verse, roll call, bring your weirdest takes
We mix logic with prophecy and cosmic mistakes
Alyssa in the chat, she a mystery queen
DJ electric, got the beat so clean
Vita with the panther, strength divine
She teams chaos with the stare and the line
We don't do fake, this trap's too real
We roast you kindly, but the love's the deal
gates tight they swing truth like justice in the moon like gift is subs yeah the
coke keeps growing community wild but the energy is flowing welcome to psych
awaken cv it's crazy it's loud it's bizarre believe me we laugh we scream we
read the unseen father psych the cat daddy king of the stream welcome to
psych awaken cv with truth the madness if the same t it's a family
You just woke up in a lucid dream
Cards flip, candles drip, shadows in the mist
Trolls, dogs lick, but they cease to exist
We're half chaos, half or a cool flame
And every night's a ritual in Psyche's name
No scripts, no filters, no chill in Psyche
We stream raw truth till the morning light
So grab your tea, grab your mic and vibe
This ain't YouTube, this is an underworld talk show.
You are now initiated.
Father Psyche is spoken.
Spoken.
Oh
He's all up in the thread saying we met on Mars talking about my soul like he owns the stars
And I'm in his right saying I'm in his dreams, but he's down in LA while I'm ruling the streams
I'm up in the ether. He's stuck in the chat. I want
is why he's typing in caps it must be the fumes it must be the tea he's feeding on my shadow like
it's currency why are you so obsessed Tony I just want
Like when Dex on gossip, you on your job, you hating hard
Dropping links like tarot cards, you call me cult, I call you fan
You're the sequel out of a plan, say you miss me, we never met
That's a bull kind of internet, I'm a consolation, a common thread
I'm a sermon, you're the unread
Why you so obsessed, Tony Rose, it's your name
You keep planning rumors, I just turn the-
nice grappers your devotion's pure disaster say it louder spell it right love's not cold you
can't rewrite you're talking to the miratoni not to me you can't throw the truth on you my
Go stay slow
Hey guys, oh you see Trix, come here, hold on, that's Trixie, Trixie, and I got Lola
here, hi, hey everybody, I'm really excited.
I Russian friend I finally told her about the channel and
Because I had to get I think it's a channel running good, right?
but uh
Yeah, it's so I surprised her today and I made her a song and I think she
Will periodically maybe be able to watch the show and stuff so
Welcome. Hey Russia. What's up? I know I wonder if time was always um, it's kind of time
He's always like where's your Russian friend gonna be on the show
So we've known each other I think since like 2008 or just like a long a long a long time
we've been through a lot a lot of fun crazy times and I'm really excited she's she's doing
really great yet my hair is pretty long yeah I haven't tied up today for I just
it's tied up for the first time but yeah it's kind of has been out of my face yeah
This is Lola. You see Lola and oh you have to see Rudy too. This is the old man cat. I got him in um
In January, he's 16 or 17 years old
Come on, baby
Hey, hey, Lola, that's your son stop Lola
you're kind of fighting okay well that's mr. Rudy yeah no hi guys oh so i got what i got tonight
got some cigars and hurricane punch are living me
hey tracy how are you do you got tracy x here yeah Rudy's um he's a really sweet cat
Little old man Rudy come on. I'm gonna put the link up if anyone wants to come
Say hi
Get the panel going yeah
So I went to over to money for 20s panel and then I basically like his Jamie said oh, he's having a panel come over
Say hi. I went over and say hi
Instantly I was hidden from the chat
Instantly and then I asked Jamie I said what who's time me out and she said
bronze chicken bronze chicken was there and
I'll play the bronze. This is like there's a site. I mean, I'm a psyche
Russia, but that's my name on the show here. Come on. So so I have a haters club. They actually they met
I'll play the song
This is a psyche haters clothes on
Right here
Christine's mad about crystal Tony's just full of it
Bronze chicken struts around, but it's looking like a lunatic
Sweet pea is gone sour, beets has bitter betty again
Alexander had my back, that's a real one not pretend
Welcome to the site
I can pluck those feathers, toss it in the pan
Welcome to the...
funny because he's always like, Oh, you're in your feet fees.
I hear your feet fees.
He's always saying that, right?
All I do is say hi and money for 20 is chat.
Oh, I didn't drop the link here.
I got a link for you.
Um, and then I also, um, you know, Jamie, we know Jamie, Jamie's okay.
If I tell us some of the story, if it's okay with you, I, I want to, um, I don't
want to share, but you don't want to share, but.
You know, Jamie, we know Jamie was in like a little accident, right?
And the whole yeah, and there we go, come on up trace
You know and she's having some memory issues and she has this friend if I tell too much Jamie just taught me, okay
She has this friend Katie. We know Katie. She's the you know that that woman that sits on beat his panel
kind of like doesn't seem too much but um and you know but they were close friends
and you know Katie just always you know blocks her you know ghosts her um you know
so Jamie's kind of been asking hey can you like let her know like okay she says something like
pretty bad things about me here's Tracy what's up Tracy
Hey, honey, I've finally got a few minutes to come up.
Hey, what's up?
I have been so busy.
And then in the middle of the night when you're live,
I can't because unless I come in the living room,
I'll wake Cecil up.
Oh.
Well, we need to meet every time.
I know.
How are you? Well, I hope you're having a great month. It's great to see you.
It's always been fucking raining. We're supposed to get some bad storms, but they all went north.
I'd hate to be in Vermont right now. My friend, I have a friend. She's from Russia. I mean,
she's lived in the States since she was pretty young. Yeah. Yeah. But, and she's, I just told her
And, uh, so I'm real excited. She's here in the chat. She says hi to you. She says hi, Trace.
Oh, how you doing? All the way in Russia. That is so cool that we get, you know, it's like a high-class CB radio.
how you been? I've been pretty good um you know I've had actually some uh a few people
looking for scrap metal come to my house today probably about three or four people oh really
they always like to send the state police the town police the ambulance the um the fucking elderly
Trying to get C-swim nursing homes, get my doctor taking one.
Yeah, I know the shit you're talking about.
Yeah, and I know, well, actually, you know, and Tony, but I think Tony does have a crush
on me.
This guy Tony.
Like I always was like suspicious.
He's not the only one.
Yeah.
Well, you are a handsome man.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Um, but then I saw I was in actually, I heard hellbilly's voice when I was going through
some lives like hellbilly.
I don't know if you know him, but I've seen, but I haven't ever paid attention.
Yeah, well, I did like mention. Oh, yeah
He's he told me some really interesting news, but I'm not gonna give away the news
I'm trying to do a ceasefire with Tony. So he like, you know
I just don't I don't want to fight with him. He's like, you know before
But I do I did learn some information today that he will not want repeated
And so I hope that he decides to do a ceasefire and then I would be happy not to
Not to you know, he's the one sending all the people to my house
Oh, so you finally found out who was doing all this fucking waste and tax payers money
Yeah, and people's time and even manure. I got bags of manure like and
Well, you could be beating and get dead animals for a cat.
Oh, oh, yeah. Yeah, she got the dead.
It could be worse, you know, but the thing is, man,
they don't understand this shit can get people hurt.
It really can.
There's people that are crazy out there being sent to your house
and you don't have what, and they spend all this time and energy to come get this metal.
and then it's not there, they got played for a fool.
They're more disappointed than I am,
like that I'm getting knocks on the door, really.
It's like, I got Docs, so like on a,
so sometimes you can get Docs and like,
he was like kind of infiltrated his way into my discord
and was spying in the voice chat.
And then somehow,
You actually doxxed, beat up, um, Jana and myself all at once and, uh, like,
you know, I don't know why people are worried about getting doxxed.
You put yourself out there on social media.
When it, when YouTube and all that shit first started,
I put my phone number, my mailing address,
and nobody could get one over on me because I already put the shit out there.
Back when I was growing up, we had things called phone books.
Yeah, exactly.
and uh every celebrity's docs as well and think about celebrities who have like millions of people
we don't know where you live and you know it's just when they get to wasting our money
oh we have uh we have a guest on hold me is this alexander holand one second
oh is that i think so hold on i mean i have to oh i love him it's a hot ship uh i mean oh my gosh
Yeah, I need to take some of this off the screen. Hold on. I got it. I got it. Um, yeah, but and then I'm bronze bird
I don't know if your bronze bird said
Alex you said you would fuck psyche. Oh my gosh, Alex Alexander never said that, you know
I think never I mean he was joking when he said it. I mean he's how do you know?
But you know Alex told us all about how he went to prison for 10 years
Wow
And kilos of cocaine and he did a plea deal
He got 15 years knocked off his sentence
All on the papers and stuff
That's I did somebody had to go jail for that long
Here he is. Here's Alex. Yo Alexander
Is he there
Uh-oh, he's gonna keep him covered. I don't know. He's not gonna porn bomb me. He's not gonna porn bomb
I think it's not he wouldn't do that. Do you
But he was a police officer at the time he was a ten-year New York City police officer and he got set up by the feds
On a cocaine or yeah, he lives with cocaine deal
Fighting Alex are you there? I don't hear you
Oh, you're smoking some herb. Yeah, I got some it's black
The the weed is black
Everybody is bragging about it only takes like a I mean I've been smoking on this all fucking day long
It's one left in a cigarette
I would make for 20 but money money for 20 like did not did nothing when I got hidden from his chat just now like nothing
He's like oh, she's a psyche's just shit out of luck or something. Yeah black it is. Oh, yeah looks good
It's like nice and purple
Weird everybody's bragging about they just got at the store 75 hours a quarter
Nice
I, uh, I wish I had a little...
I would give you some, but I think it's in my...
I don't know, except, uh...
I just get a friend of mine. She doesn't smoke that much. I gave her a half the
left-hand cigarette and oh she's gonna sleep like a baby tonight. Nice. Now she
even knew about the black widows that was going around. She goes, do you have any
And she's like, can I have a little?
So I had to fucking join.
I had been smoking on, and I gave it to her.
I was like, I said, one, and I lit this roach.
And I was like, will you have a boat before you leave?
And she's like, oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I'll never make it home.
And she lives two buildings down.
She was like, yeah, I need to carry her home.
Well, a friend with weed is a friend indeed, right?
Oh yeah, she brought me over.
Oh my God, she gets this crumb cake.
And it's like so thick and it's got all kinds of nuts
and everything like that.
Oh, she gives me all kinds of stuff.
She gives a hamburger and they say they can taste the difference.
It's the stuff that's in like a tube.
It's not like the regular stuff that you get.
And she, her boy swears up down, he can taste the damn difference.
So they give me their hamburger.
I'm like, fuck yeah, I don't eat this shit.
Free food?
Hell yeah.
I did want to expose this text message.
Oh, dude. Oh, dude. Come on.
So, you know, I was trying to...
Kind of be a mediator between my you know, Jamie who's been a mod here since the beginning of my show
You know and just a sweet girl. She I think she's suffering from from memory problems right now and you know
She cares about this this woman Katie. I could you know, I was
She's on beat his panel she's kind of is quiet and she just has that like
Well, anybody that hangs with Peter, you know, they're there for the meanness.
Yeah. And they really are. That's why they're there.
She turned mean on me. And so I have really, yeah. Well, so here's the, a few weeks ago,
she text message me. So here's the, I'll just read the messages.
When I first wrote her, I don't think my message is there, but she wrote me out of the blueage
because I said something to her on Bita's panel and she didn't really respond to it.
She said, tell the fucking truth.
You came for me and wanted my place, Jamie's words, not mine.
Remember the fire?
You came at my deceased niece, not true, who does that seriously.
Seek help.
It sounds like somebody's jealous.
Yeah, she's like, like a miscarriage.
She never letting me grieve the loss of my niece
to her cronies, to ordering stuff for her
on her mom's credit card, to lying to her about her mom,
about it harassing my baby daddy, et cetera.
I couldn't fucking breathe.
She smothered.
Anybody who says the word baby daddy
are very tactful and uneducated.
She said I didn't have a life from her drama. I did not want to hate her and she wouldn't accept
no for an answer. She was jealous over the baby daddy. Oh and you want to see her say she was
pregnant by him and her threats want to see her face decent from Larissa question her disabilities
Pissing yourself, my birthday wasn't about you, but you sure as hell tried to make it
about you.
The narcissistic BS you pulled, you also made it sound like it's my fault.
I never talk shit on beta, follower, are you kidding me, that's all you, that's you all
day every day, hold yourself accountable, stop lying, sweet pea, bronze, etc., are attacking
back, stupid, you started this, you dox me motherfucker, no one knew my name, so you kept
saying it first and last, I have that recorded, so don't you say you didn't do it, proof
states otherwise.
It ain't just your bed, dumbass.
It's your entire house.
You're an idiot.
You want to fight?
Let's go legal, shithead.
I'll offer that to you.
I'm playing you my name out of your mouth.
I hate you.
And you're a worthless POS.
Poor cats are so much better.
In fact, do us all a huge favor, go away.
Okay, so I was happy to go away, but.
But then I responded I said don't quite know what's going on or why you're so mad
We never really had issues Jamie has memory problems and is missing you maybe reach out to her
If she means anything to you she was in a terrible car accident and we almost lost her and then she said she has my email
I didn't reach out. I also talked to Sifa apologized to Meg's Jamie owes me many apologies
Don't quite understand why you think you're the go-between. I do not like the way you docks
Reprivate message. That's like somebody is narcissistic and calling them
get a black
And it's like and there's a reason i'm reading and it's like i didn't read these before but i think it's just important to see like
You know, it's time you stood up for yourself, honey. You take a lot of shit. You're a doormat for a lot of people
I need to be so blunt, but I don't mean to hurt your feelings, but this time you let
your balls drop.
Oh, thank you.
Yeah, I will.
Let them hang proud.
Damn straight.
When I do the helicopter and all kinds of shit.
Yeah.
I never doctor I mean the thing was it's like I knew her you know
I knew her I would be we would hang out watch movies and stuff on my discord
So I knew her by her first name
And so sometimes when she would come on panel or come on my chat she had a scream you do
Yeah, I forgot her. I just knew her real name, right? They're her first name. I never said or yeah, or anything like that
She was saying but um broad
And she's like you speak ill of the deceased take side on manipulate situations
I honestly don't ever care to speak to you again. If ever I hear from you
It'll be too soon. You played me took advantage and play the victim cool
I'll be your villain, but leave me as that and go away never speak for Jamie nor me again
You know now they fucking even saying Jamie Jamie's a nice person
Really and Jamie's like just
You know that's why I mean come on it's very hard to love me nobody loves me
She said you know what happened, but won't be honest you played a rule to do act to do
To act stupid lose my number also
I never called swat on your dumb ass never threatened you before you ever spread those allegations again take it
uh tickets me because that was a fake profile and you threw a false jacket my way on purpose
you heard they knew who was at the time they were doing this and calling people on you oh
I bet they knew it and as a friend if I knew that you were fixing to get it
And I had me and these friends and I don't have your number
But if I had it I'd be calling you going hey, man
You fix and get hit by something because that's what friends fucking do
So, you know, you ain't no damn friend if you don't try and cover my eyes because I'm there to cover you if I'm your friend
Oh, and it's okay, like, oh, but by the way, you know, I'm psyche, but it's like, my name
is John.
It's not a big secret.
I've docked myself before.
I think we all know the community is John, but it's psyche.
Psyche?
I wouldn't know you by John unless I was in the Discord.
I was gonna leave it like that, I mean, it's just like, you know, she's like, she said,
Until then don't try and so then I just left it alone for like until today and then the Jamie said Jamie has been saying
She wants to talk to her and can I please?
I'm gonna try one more time. So I wrote her again and I said, sorry to bother you.
Jamie has been very upset, confused, wanting me to contact you for her. Please call her a
contact her. If you do, I will make a public apology on my show. Otherwise, please accept my
private apology if you feel like it's something wrong. I always liked you got along. I'm very
confused. I've always been like that. You would like that when you got back with me on Instagram.
Yeah, you are very talk if there's a problem. We talked to each other and I
Mean by guns be by guns or if we got confused
I just wanted to back away from the people you hang on my man
well
So it wasn't you it was the people you were associated with and your guilt by association was not wanting to be my guilt
Oh, it's okay. My friend's a little concerned because she said my first name, but it's fine.
I even say my last name.
Did you ever think you're not that fucking important?
I mean, really, you're just another damn spot in fucking YouTube,
and if you put yourself in social media, eventually everybody's going to know everything fucking about you.
Like and I don't want to like talk bad about Bita, but you know, she's just like so in sense that her
Last name is out there or whatever. I don't have anything to good to say about her or Alexander
Mayors, so I don't say anything at all. I don't go there. I don't associate myself with it
Yeah, I just don't because I don't like you. I'm not gonna put any energy into it
I'm not gonna make a big mess out of it. It is what it is and
You know, if you don't like somebody, you don't go hang out at your fucking chat.
Yeah, but I mean, but I do believe that.
just being on a show is like, we are public figures in some way.
And it's like, you know, always presented herself like she was,
yeah, just started streaming like right before I did, like a couple months or something.
I've been at least around for eight years doing panels and stuff and I don't know.
So, so I've been doing it over 14 years now.
Wow. I had Tracy more forever and then there was
So many deaths of youtubers and then fucking Joe burned up in my live stream and
And fucking stellar and dog lips all died. I got hit with three friends
One right after the other but after Joe burned up on that last dream. I dumped that channel and it was 13 year old
Yeah
Oh, yeah, it's just I cried I didn't know that you could get that emotional but having that much
that many years of shit when I tell you was all I could do to hit that fucking delete,
but I looked at it and I went you know what I don't want these memories.
You know. Yeah. Well.
Um, this is to finish up, I told her I would apologize in my show like she asked or said
otherwise except my private apology if you feel like I did something wrong, I always
liked to go along and make confused what happened, but I said she's ready to talk if you're
willing.
I'm only writing because she asked me to and I care about her and this is her response
to me today.
She said respectfully, respectfully, she said, stay the fuck out of it.
She owes the apologies.
I owe her nothing, not even a thought.
Contact me again. I'm pressing charges. So take your fake apology and shove it right up your ass. And so that's how
That's how she talks, okay, and I
Sounds really mature. Yeah, I was can't even have a conversation could you dislike?
Well, I mean, it's like I was just and I was just trying to tell me honestly almost, you know, almost passed away like she was I mean, that was a she was in a terrible car accident.
Yes, I know.
That brings our eyes and all kinds of things and fuck her up.
Yeah, and
You know, I was like, I was like, Jamie, I really don't want to write her because she's not like receptivist stuff, but I'll try.
So I tried as nice as I could, and that's how serious I was.
You are. You would consider it. You didn't call anybody names, or the first thing I had to bet was, fuck you.
Right, and so yeah, so that's
Yeah, I'm buying me. I'd say I'd say, you know, what's my fucking name that shit?
Alex are you I don't know my Alexander never I don't know. He's not talking to us
You're not talking right now. He's just being quiet. You miss Eric the actor. I miss Eric the actor too. I love, uh
What is this on my eyeballs? We think my eyeballs are big. I just have beautiful big eyes. Don't you see look?
My fuck
I, I do have probably, do you know your eyeballs never, never, um, they don't grow anymore that your eyeballs are full size when you're like a big baby.
Yeah.
That's pretty crazy.
That's wild ain't it?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, our bodies do some weird shit when we kids.
Yeah.
Then transformation into an adult.
Roblox is about to nod off. Is this the real dish gonna do some driving in an hour. So oh
What's up Gish, yeah, I don't know
I've known Gish for a long time now ever since blogger and I got married
Right, I talked to blogger last night a little bit
Oh, I saw he was live, but I couldn't stay so long before he went live
I left him a heart and he he said I love you too
You know, and then I popped in for a second and some guy was on there with them. I can't remember
It was I think um, can't um Athens school of Athens. Maybe went up. I don't know if that's the way. Ah, maybe maybe
I think he went up there last night and uh, yeah, my blogger was actually, you know, having you know
Conversations that usually he uses like YouTube as a model and uh, and just place to get fucked up
And, uh, last night he was, he was really, you know, I kept stopping in just to watch him, you know, for a second, but it was nice.
I got to tell him I love him.
Oh.
He's a good guy.
He really is. I love him to death.
Well, I think it's great that, uh, he does have, like, you know, a true friend like you, and I know you're a good friend to him.
You know I
Said I don't really have a problem with him, but he is kind of like homophobic for yeah, you don't like quiz
Yeah, you know
It's okay. It's okay
You know not everyone yeah, I mean to each his own man
You know you're a guy. You know where they're coming from
Well, he did say what about my show on so he was on who's clipped on I think he got that's why I told you to take that ranch
It was another reason I caught hell for coming up here. Oh
Yeah, I fucking got browbeat
For like a couple fucking mods. I mean that's when he went and started playing in the cat box
I was like well, you know cuz he I don't know what was going on between you two good
Look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look, look
that's when I stole that big fucking flag that I got over the windows in my bedroom off mountain
and then pop a pill we got back to house and I put it on a trailer right in the hallway because
it's a huge like eight foot by five foot fucking american flag and uh and he says so I went to
take it down and put it on my bike and he says no you can't take that flag you stole it
You can get that flag over my dead body
Fucking five years five. No about ten years ago. He he died and I finally got that fucking flag back
That I stole from
Fucking 40 years later. I don't know if you can show that picture again, but my friend does want to see that
I think I was that all my pictures. Yeah, I can show you
It should be overdue by the gun safe.
Aw, and Jamie, Jamie, Jamie, I think she's just, she seems, I think she's mean because
I think she was like, she was a different kind of person last year, like Katie, like
you know.
You know, mean people and mean channels like that will do that to people who are eternal.
She kind of, yeah, she kind of like, as soon as she started going on Vita's panels, she
kind of like.
I didn't want to say the name, but it's the hate.
Yeah.
I mean, something's going on in their life, probably,
where they're using YouTube just to dump.
Yeah.
Well, you know, but it's like, Jamie, at least you
got to see like how I just want to at least see
how she's responding to me.
You know the truth now.
See, that's what friends do.
They cover each other's back.
When they see that somebody's getting fucked over.
You know what I mean?
Because Jamie's a very sweet, trusting person, you know?
And-
I've always been super sweet to me.
I don't, I never saw her be unkind to anybody.
Uh-oh.
So, oh, it's chances.
I know she, Katie's been-
Kind of interesting. She doesn't talk very much but you know, she
Always she opened your mouth. Obviously she had a lot fucking say
Yeah, but it's just it means it's a little bit of uh, it's a bit of drama, but
Oh, I like it. I don't think that'd be so damn mean
The public's execution uh people actually tell you, uh
You're kind of like Taylor Swift in Blu-Blox.
Hey Nancy, reality Nancy's in the chat.
What's up Nancy? How are you?
Love Nancy.
Yeah, oh yeah.
I'm actually gonna like...
Russia I'm gonna mod you just it's just means like you know you have some power
the chat if you ever want to use it just but it's basically you know keeps you
safe in the chat and stuff if you don't have to do it you're gonna mod me would
you like to be a mod Tracy or not yeah cuz I think I got it straightened out
with my husband
Okay, okay, it was all he got really mad at me and I think what's between
Even though blogger doesn't like quiz and shit like that. It is what it is
But I think he knows it. I'm not
Uh-huh, okay, I'm gonna get you more than
You know, he's got a lot of friends and I don't say nothing about his fucking friends
So I think I'm gonna override the hubby and say yeah
Yeah
Thank you, but I'll accept your wrench and it's nothing against you old man. It's just I
Like psych and there's nothing damn thing you can do about it. That's shit
Shan, what song do you like?
Shan likes one of the, oh, oh, the thing that is song.
Yeah, I made a thing that is-
You didn't write my song for my fucking YouTube thing yet.
The same thing that is, it's just, it's different.
It's just different enough to not be the real athlete.
I did, I just probably changed the thumbnail or whatever.
All right, we gotta be, you know some of these photos, sir.
Oh, here we go.
Here we go, Russia.
She's gonna-
Let me see.
I don't know if I got enough light this one's safe this one's safe. Um, I've just got no shirt on but
It's it's covered up. I might have to turn the light on here. Let me turn you sideways
No, don't let me if I turn it sideways then I get a better camera because we're on stream
Okay, like that. Just give me a sec. I got tighten the damn bolt
All right, um,
a little bit. Yeah. Oh, there you go. Wow. That's a long, that's me and Tara.
And no, there was no gayism, but I can't see titties and shit.
Let me see.
Where did you steal that flag from?
From the top of Mount Minadnok in Princeton down the road.
Wow.
It looked like an official government flag or something.
No, it's a burial flag because it's the size of a burial flag.
This is a little promiscuous, but the nipples are covered.
My best.
Oh, there you go.
Yeah
This is in that's little Phil where Papa feels Papa Phil. Yeah, but that's little Phil beside me
Okay, it's looking good. Oh, wow. Oh my gosh. Wow. You can't see nipples. Yeah, this is I mean my best always covered my nipples
But we're
At homestead we're and this is Papa Phil and Tira
And there's my flag
So that would be Papa
Yeah, that's Papa Phil
Okay, yeah
He's the one that I had to get that flag back over his dead body
And he's a big motherfucker
There's a let's see I gotta flip it again
Uh this one's a little risky. It's okay. You can just maybe cover if there's any
Yeah
It's a flash. Yeah, um, it's art people. Yeah, it's
This is Tira. Oh
Wow
Tira
She was a stripper in Illinois and the club that she was associated with got busted and
she ended up on witness protection in Massachusetts.
And Papa Philham was down at the dam with her.
This one's safe.
Oh, yeah, that's it.
My arm is covered it.
Let's see that one's too promiscuous.
That one's showing full talk because I used to walk around.
This one's all right because it's sideways.
See, really can't see anything.
Uh huh.
Well, yeah.
It's just a wild time.
Oh, let's see. Oh, that one damn sure can't be shown. Oh, no, no, no, no. That's that's a full Monty.
This one's pretty cool.
Wow, cool. Um,
This one's pretty cool. Oh
No, uh, let's see
Yeah
There we go. That one's pretty cool. Oh
Beautiful that looks like a lot of fun. That's that's the 80s or is that the 80s or?
Yes
In the 80s, yeah, that was the 80s. I just
Let's see. I'm going wrong way. No
No, Jesus Christ, not that one
Oh fuck no, can't tell that.
Tell me the album, $250.
And Russia says you are wild, Tracy's wild.
Oh, this is my tent.
This is what I lived in when I lived on my Harley for eight years.
So this was home and I parked my bike in there and that's how it stayed warm.
It was there.
And then...
That's Papa's son, Little Phil.
Yeah, I grew up with him and known him ever since.
I was me smoking some waddles.
Yeah, smoking some waddles.
Yeah, let's see.
That's it you guys. Well, thank you Tracy. I mean, I really appreciate that. I think Chad enjoyed it. We always love as a little
I know it's nice to go down memory lane with you and you really do enjoy
You know some people you show them pictures and they're like oh my god
You know, but you you really do enjoy it and I enjoy showing somebody because they don't have anybody
You know what I mean?
and you are so much like my kid oh yeah I'm his age right exactly yeah you're
both 44 year old and I love the story you have and you look like him I can show
He's been addressing them a picture. Well his first drag queen competition
You know what I mean I even got
Uh-oh, well I
Is it like I when do you when did you come out whenever you you get back? Well, I would like to wonder when you came out to you and
How you reacted um or if you were surprised or anything like that
You knew he was queer
No, I when he was born and we'd go to a friend's house, you know and
Instead of getting into shit like a kid getting into coffee table and stuff like that and grab things
No, he would empty the ashtray wipe them off
At three years old he pulled up a chair and was doing dishes
And so I pulled all the knives out in the glasses and I said have at it
you know and
But I didn't get really the clean gay guy Jean
I guess like some gay guys do I got the I got the best gay guy
No, because you were spoiled you had somebody else to do it for you
Well, he was fine. All right. Here we go. That's me when I was a little kid
I am thinking
I'm sneaky.
All right, there is, let me see.
Oh, this Christopher, when he was born.
And then there's Christopher when he got kidnapped.
That was the last picture of him when he got kidnapped.
And then this is Christopher. Let's see the night before the competition
He does kind of look like I looked like yeah, wow. Yeah, he dies and
Then the competition he won the competition and he was in the red dress
And
That was at the strip joint and then he went to the prom with the black girl
Okay, and then there's two of my friends, the one in leather, she's dead now, that was
little, and that's her wife Betsy.
And yes, I did say that, fuck and I have women that are married to each other that are friends.
That's awesome, you know what I mean, and I do my friend Joni's in this chat
She said she said the best thing about this internet experience is that Tracy and me in real life would have not
Haven't had ever connected and we are so very different, but I am watching with an open mind and heart
Yeah, that's what I was saying earlier when he was talking about having a friend in Russia
And I called it a high pollutant, you know CB radio
Except we can see each other and, you know, people take it and they use it to hurt other
people.
Well, she's been in America for, I think, I think she's been in America since she was
quite young.
But, um, yeah, she's just, you know, fluent Russian and, uh, you know.
I think she came over when she was about eight years old, I think.
Can you help me out and change the pattern so I'm not so narrow trying to?
You want to pull out?
I can fix this.
Just change the pattern so we're not lined up, because I ain't got no camera room no matter
that.
There you go.
Now I can do something with that.
I'm sorry.
Okay, yeah.
I'm on my big screen, so it's like, it's kind of like.
Okay, yeah, so it looks thank you that helped me a lot
Tracy we still have to do I want to do your astrology too. Yeah
Everything said mercury
Mercury, yeah, well
Mercury
It's the fastest moving planet. It's the closest to the Sun. It's the doctoring
The person said it says that's why you've always worked in the healthcare industry. Well, and there's so many people
I know oh, yeah, so she lived in so i'm so my friend russia is 39 now and she's been here since she was 13 in america
Oh, she got to remember what russia was. Yeah
That's cool. That's cool. So she yeah, she got the actual experience both sides
Casey there's a picture on the screen you can see or she's
She's beautiful. Oh, she's beautiful. Yeah
That's a good looking kid right there now
And she's like, she, she did a women's firefighter, firefighter, firefighter program and.
Oh, really? Yeah.
That's neat.
Yeah, I think they put a brush fire.
Like a lot of work.
Yeah.
I'll tell you what.
And that's a family, very tight.
I don't, here in New England, the firefighters are, they're like this, they, you know, they're
with each other more than they are with their family.
I didn't need to fire, um,
This is the real Theo gate. Like this is the Theo gate that sent me the dick pics. This is the same one
I saw you have money for 20, but I didn't hear you talk at all. He just sent me a couple dick pics before
He did you've got thousands of dick pics. Did he type anything going, you know something to remember him by?
He put a hairbrush next to it to show me the size that I was. Hey, Henry, what's up?
He put a hairbrush next to it and yeah, he wasn't a bear. He was bragging like you're my home, right?
He's like, he's like, he's like, he's like, let's get my pecker bigger than your pecker.
And Russia says she's also getting her CD...
L L license. Yeah, commercial driver's license. She got her
boyfriend a driver's team. You'll be able to travel and be
around each other all day long. That's a lot of work. him.
Please be careful. My my father taught his brother how to
drive and he just had a baby and he wanted to get home and
uncle John fell asleep at the wheel and and ended up getting
because he taught his brother how to drive the trucks.
And yeah.
I know they drive for like long hours like ha and my dad was cross-country. He was never home
He had a whore and damn there every
There was one he pulled the truck up
there's a little tiny town and
glass front on this
Restaurant and it was more like a you know greasy spoon and he told me take my time put my shoes on
I did and I could see right through there and there was a waitress come up
And I was maybe about, I don't know, six, seven, something like that.
And fucking, I never saw that waitress.
And then dad got him
one of his nips in his coffin.
And I could smell the alcohol.
But yeah, it must have been one of the women he was fucking with,
because he went in there and said, I got my kid with me.
Don't fuck with me.
No, yes, yeah, no my friend my Russian friend is in the chat. So
Awesome. She's a good-looking kid. I
Yes, I know
Too bad you're not too bad you're gay
It's too bad. Well, I mean you could be riding in the big rig
Well, you know
It's like no pressure is just comfortable, you know, but it is it was great when I went to a gay strip club
I could admire all the packers and the ass and the good-looking fucking man
And shit like that and I didn't have to worry about no
You know I was it
Gay men are very convenient because I don't like broads broads. I always do it. You want a bitch and
Fight and all that other bullshit. I'd rather have male. I got more male friends than new fucking
And the women that I've got that are fucking my friends are usually gay
So there's no competition there, you know
Yeah
It's okay, you know, Jamie I've had people I've had people say a lot worse
To me then. Oh, yeah, you've heard it all. Yeah, I mean I've got you're a worthless motherfucker. You know
That's why you got the hate song
Yeah
Yeah, they actually I mean they I don't know if you ever you saw those episodes, but he had a cup
We had a couple of I think those were probably his biggest shows, you know, like we're and he just had a whole group of people that were like, you know
Yeah, I can ride with you any day. Thank you. I'd like
Let's arrive between your big rigs there. Oh, yeah, it's fun. Yeah, and they'll be funny and fucking shit and it's gonna California
My fucking dad, best fucking stepmother I had on all the broads he had was a woman,
a lot less than that of California and her husband had blown up in the crystal meth factory
down there in Slab City and he ended up getting with her and she was the best damn stepmom
and she ended up dying of cancer but I actually went to have broads feeling that man she was
oh yeah she passed away in a crystal meth explosion or yeah they were in they
were at slap city and her husband was making crystal meth and fucked up and
the whole thing exploded and he died and she also worked as a
an underwriter for a car dealership.
So you know all the forms and shit
that you do when you buy a vehicle.
You know, that's what an underwriter does.
Make sure that everything's organized,
what you're paying, you know, insurance and shit like that.
But she wasn't a stupid broad.
She had a kid that had the same name,
her daughter had the same name with her,
which was weird, but she was a heroin addict.
That was the first time I ever did heroin.
I had just had a hysterectomy.
I was 22 because I had cancer.
Best day of my fucking life.
No more bleeding, no more kids.
And I got a Harley, so fuck it.
So you have the one you have your one son. Is that that I had three sons with two dead
And I the only one that made it was the first son and
Me and his daddy we we was married. I was married at 15 and he was playing Christopher was planned
He was he was very much wanted
That's really interesting, like a lot of people like do have like, you know, Alex McQueen, his brothers is gay.
Reality Nancy, I think has a transgender son, or transgender, you know.
Yeah.
Like my mom had a my mom had a gay sister. She passed away last year
But something but her younger sister and stuff and then my my brother-in-law had a gay brother
And so it's like a lot of people will you know the thing is is back when I was kid in the 60s and 70s
Um, there was this same amount of gay people, men and women, it just wasn't thrown in the
heterosexuals face with your parades and your flags.
I'm not into parades or like-
Oh, no, I'm talking about that.
Because otherwise I'm going to keep saying the queer parade.
So I'm just generalizing it.
Yeah.
I mean, but I mean, I'm-
I'm just like, I feel like sexuality is like just a part of it.
Yeah, what you do behind closed doors is none of my fucking business, I'm not paying you a rent.
Okay, hey, I'm Russia, thank you for being the chat tonight.
I love you sweetheart, and you know, it's fun and you can tell it's a fun show.
I think I have a great show and just having a great time.
We just need to have fun and talk to each other
because it's cheaper.
We don't have to go to a bar.
Thank you.
You have a good night, Rocha.
Love you, BFF.
It was nice meeting you.
Yeah, hopefully.
And hopefully, you'll come on the panel sometime, too.
Or maybe when I know we're.
Yeah, it would be cool.
You ain't got to cut your camera home.
And in December, I think she might be able to visit.
Oh, I do have this like, I have this on the table.
This is the, and I've got it.
Don't show them your table.
You'll call a gadget.
This is my Baba Yaga house.
This is my little wood.
It's a, it's a,
Baba Yaga is a witch in Russia.
And she had like a house with chicken feet, right?
And it, it was all the way around the forest and stuff like that.
But I have my little Baba Yaga.
That's what it means to sell.
What's it made of plastic?
It's made of wood.
It's made out of wood.
Oh, it is wood.
yeah it's made out of wood so it's like a little hobbit house yeah it's got really cool like little
that's cool as shit it looks like real chicken look at the feet and it does it looks like roots of a
tree yeah that's nice to say oh man i got that i got my mcdonald's coffee actually i got that
I don't know why man just doesn't buy I'm gonna put my glasses
Okay, I got you know, I get all my rings like I got these rings all on team moves if you see these rings
Look how nice they are. I mean, they're all under $10, you know, I don't mind saying I get I get inexpensive things
I think I get nice things, but so these are you know, there's this is like the Nordic
Nice the clock one is that yeah, or the compass
It's called the helm of awe, but it's like a compass, but it's called the helm of awe.
That's cool. Those come out in the 60s.
It discerns purple and green, like a gem in the middle of it.
Oh, look at that.
Look at the pentagram right there.
And then, oh, DJ Electra got me this bracelet. It's like a purple.
Oh, yeah.
I remember you getting out. That's really cool. I love the purple and black together.
But I got how much grass did I get? I bought another pair of these glasses,
like the same thing. I love them because the side of them, you can see they look a little
panned. Oh, they're thick. Yeah. But everything's under 10 bucks on Timu. I don't know if you
ever shop on Timu. I went to it, but then people was doing the little videos where
they were getting a picture of the product.
Yeah, there are some sellers on there like independent sellers and so I had to buy a generator off of them for and I was gonna spend a close to a thousand dollars and they could never get my fucking order right so I ended up going through another company, but I got a big generator in the front closet fucking out.
Really expensive things there because I think if you mind on Amazon, it's like no you can just return it so easily
You know just I just take it to the Whole Foods and they'll take it
But yeah, so, you know, I was able to get a new computer
I did because um, I don't know if you know ghost
Yeah, he um, he he's like a couple months ago and this month he's he's donated very um
Generously, and so I was able to get computer and the green screen and now I can like work my
YouTube a lot easier the webcam all set up. I'm not using my use my tablet for at least six months
I got this room right here and uh when I was streaming
During COVID I had a bar, so I'd wear hardly any top or I put tape on my teddy nipples
And I had me a desk and everything like that and we'd play music and shit like that right now
It's got my treadmill and my fucking e-bike in there my mountain bike
No
But yeah, I wanted to do the green screen thing
Right, and if we'll on stream yard now that when I stream from the computer like I can actually have this green
I have like an official green screen I put up. Yeah, I can say I
Can just say turn off the green screen, but I bet and look what it does here, you know put it oops horn
Yeah, well, I disappear. Yeah, I'll put it. I'll make yeah now
Yeah, it's just the the technology
It does you but you can like adjust the sometimes you can adjust the you can I know that stream
It's come a long way, but goddamn they went up on that price
$240 a year well what I did was um I
I was paying like 45 a month and then I went to cancel
and it's like, okay, we'll-
Yeah, and then they lower it.
Yeah, or 40% off.
And so I've been paying,
and I thought it was gonna be for three months,
but it's been like six or seven months now for 25 bucks a month.
So what are you paying now?
25 bucks a month.
Okay, so it used to be 10 when they did that.
And then all of a sudden I did that and I left it for a year they automatically build me for a whole new year again
And I didn't know that they fucking sent me
and put the premium package.
I was paying $250 a year
because I don't pay attention to money.
It's just a means of fucking paying the bills.
That was like, I signed up for the trial when I,
and then it's like, later I got like,
it said like $90.
I was like, oh my gosh,
they charged me for the whole year.
That's what I was paying $90 a year.
But it was $90 a month.
I was on the most expensive plan.
I was like,
Wow, they did the same thing to you.
Yeah.
But I was able to get it all refunded, you know, you can talk to people there. You can talk to an actual human being
That's what I like about that one. You can actually talk to somebody
Yeah, oh, yeah
And now with all the AI and stuff,
you can, I mean, it's just a nightmare talking to me.
Oh, I bet you're having a ball.
But I know I love, there's so many great things.
Like I actually, there's a browser called Comet.
It's a free browser, you know?
And it actually will, has like something called the Assistant.
And I was like having all this trouble
of doing my website and stuff.
If you click Assistant, then it will just go in
and take over your browser and do things for you.
It's so cool.
you have to try that. It's called Comet Browser and it was like hold on I get my computer because I don't want to do that.
Yeah and you can just like if you have like problems figuring out some kind of website because I'm doing I'm making a website and it's
like I was having trouble figuring out how to put the code in and stuff and it's like then I just asked it and then it did it for me
and it's really smart it just figured out so it's called Comet. Yeah because Microsoft just got one the co-pilot.
Uh-huh, but you have to activate all you have to turn it's fine. I asked you yeah
Like like there's also that you even chat GPT has like an agent feature where it I've been talking to that broad
Oh, you've been talking. Yeah, you can talk to chat to me like
Mentioned it. I asked her about I'm moving to another state and
Transferring my licenses and you know for work
and doing a seesaw and everything,
and it was going to actually call every doctor
within a 20 mile radius,
tell them everything that needs to be asked
and send emails out,
get me a reel to find me a bet.
And I'm like, well, don't do all the,
it was fixing to do it all.
And I'm like, no, I'm just asking.
But yeah, I haven't since you told me about it and it was already downloaded in my book and thing
Yeah, and I got it done drop my computer. I'm missing a few parts, but it don't mean shit. It doesn't
Now this was $750 this one. I want one with the keyboards lit up at night. Uh-huh
No, but I went after the the core processor. This is the i7
Nice, yeah, this is she would pack it but it fucking it's done me. Well, I don't run much on it
Oh, damn Canadians. Yeah, that was blogger.
And I've been playing it because in the wintertime, that's when I play on a computer. I play second life.
So what's the name of the browser?
Okay, it is called, comment is the browser,
and I think it is a free browser.
So just like a comment browser,
and then it has a button that says assistance.
And so if you have, I mean, I'm making a website.
And so it was really helpful in some of the coding stuff for that, but it will also you can press a little button
It says it will summarize the web page and it just has the AI all built into the browser that works with you
Yeah, it really I mean, it's really amazing and I'm also I also use another another
Cool browser, but I mean this this one is free. That's the coolest part about it
It's I think they're offering it free and it does yeah, they got it free forever. Yeah
And then you've got $20 a month, but if you get it billed automatically, it's $16.67 and then you can get the max, which is $200 a month, but it does everything.
Yeah.
Yes, yes, I mean, even the free one is a lot.
They do so much, you know?
Actually, I was able to get, like,
it says, Bill, you know, with this search engine
called Perplexity, and Perplexity has, like,
all the mixed in, and I was able to find this YouTube video
that said, oh, well, here's a link.
You can sign up, and it's like,
if you're a PayPal member, and sign up, and it's like-
I just got it, it says, Bill, with Perplexity in mind.
Yeah.
Just as you said that it flipped over to a page. It's downloading it says in stolen. Yeah
But you're gonna give me something to play with
Yeah, I mean it's like it's really good for any kind of task because I would never be able to figure out like the coding myself
Like I was even trying I have no clue what the fuck a coding is. Oh, wow
Oh my god, the effects are cool here. Let me mute that because I don't need you to get in trouble
No problem
It's really but it is really it's really cool. It works really great and I think you'll I think you'll love it. Oh my god
Yes
Microsoft Ed's profile one it even jams with Microsoft
Importing my Microsoft now
It's so cool and everything starts working together and then you can, I mean, they do have like a...
This is so cool.
Yeah, I love it. Also, I love doing the music. I've done so many songs.
I've done like, you know, probably 50 songs and one of the things I'm going to get my next...
Actually YouTube pays out tomorrow, but then you know next month. I'll get a kind of nice paycheck from YouTube
I'm gonna get a year. I am I
I'm trying
You know to get my shit back together
Oh, it even gives you your arm. I put I picked mercury out of all the planets. Oh, yeah, did you pick?
Uh, Saturn. Well, Saturn is my birth planet.
You know, Saturn?
Yeah, I just picked Mercury.
Yeah, it's really, I've got the cool, cool, like, uh,
it has like a little game too where you can like shoot around,
just like a little ball around the planet to get to the black hole.
Oh, it's just like little really, really nice designs and stuff.
We're gonna set it as a default browser.
Yeah.
I'm going to because it's just transfer. It's working with my Microsoft edge side bites
And I didn't have to do but click one button and it's all set up. That was easy shit. I've ever done
You see where it says assistant at the top like that's where you can like ask it if you're like it gets stuck at a
Website or something or like can't figure out where something is or have it like you can any kind of question
You can say you can ask the assistant and the assistant will like
immediately like search all these things.
It will even like take over the browser if you want it to
and do tasks for you, which was really handy
because I could not figure out how to do this one thing.
And I was just like, I'll never be able to figure this out.
And then I just asked, all of a sudden it was all done
in like 10 seconds.
That's the problem I have.
I don't fucking understand it and I've run out of kids to give it to and go here fix it
Yeah, oh my gosh, and plus nowadays coding and that's it is so expensive
You know to hire people and stuff and so it's like I would have to figure out myself
But then it's like, you know, it's not everybody goes on just looking up on youtuber. They've got fun
Yeah, well needs you got some damn smart ass
You don't understand what they're saying either.
Yeah.
So I think the AI is just going to make it so much like there's so much more like I have this one program where it basically will build you apps like and like, you know, I built like an IP to style.
I'm building IP directory.
And I want you to be on there. I mean, it's like, it's going to be.
Oh, yeah.
I just got the like the uh some stuff integrated the admin panel and stuff integrated today but
I'll be able to easily add people's sites feature sites and just have a directory of when people
are on and just um and it will be a little bit it'll be a lot friendlier than ip2 I think ip2
is kind of you know that's kind of washed up yeah it's just like the rb shit it's it's been there done
You know, you really something different and you're doing all the music. Oh, yeah
He's very it it's something that hasn't been done. So you've made it unique. Oh
And I love being able to like mix it with
Astrology and like cuz you can you know
What your base is? Yeah, you know, and it's just like it's such a
Cool way for people to like really connect with like the symbolism and like or even memorize their placements
If you have like a song about instrument and things like that you can have a whole album with your
And I've seen people that always said, you know, like me
Crocus shit. It doesn't interest me
But you know, you get to talk with a bunch of people in the panel next thing you're going. Well, what the fuck does mine say?
You know
And it does, it's a great conversation piece, you know?
Cause you don't, you're not like a know-it-all on that.
Right. I mean, there's so, because there's so much,
like it would take years and years of studying, basically.
And everybody reads the damn cards different.
Right.
And if you wanted to, I've noticed that,
that not one reads the same,
Yeah, right because there's a lot of it because there's tons of interpretation that goes with it
People there's different styles of cards
And different decks. Oh my god. There's endless amounts of decks. Oh
You can have the you get a golden girls deck now and pleasure. Oh, yeah
Something like the animal one. There's a guy David. No, and he gets way late
And I like it one to five in the morning. He'll do a live stream once twice a week and he's
I think he's in his 76 late 60s 70s and he's cool as shit man and it's it's
interesting philosophical and shit like that
Would you like me to pull you an animal card?
Yeah, and every time he kept pulling, it was an owl.
And then when I first, when you started your channel
and you said, let me pull a card.
And I said, one card and one you pulled, you pulled an owl.
I was like, no shit.
Let's see what we can do.
I like the animal one.
Yeah, this is a cool deck. This is an animal spirit deck. I think the artist by Susan Belay
She fucking she does all that with the stones and like that bold at home
and the Reiki and shit puttin' fuckin' rocks on you,
you lay down and just put a rock on you and fix you,
I guess, I don't know.
Well, you didn't get an owl today,
but you did get a hawk.
You got a, oh, let me turn off this.
Still a fuckin' bird.
and got this hawk and then also a very observant bird, right? Like just like an owl.
Very dangerous, deadly, isn't as silent as the owl. See, the Indians didn't like that
shit. I went to one of the powwows and I tried to get one of their mazes and I got told I was too
white to do that. And then I went to take pictures of the damn chief when he was in a circle and
one and I had an owl feather and boy they they they said you gotta get rid of that and they made me
give it to the master man and he did something disposed of it but I wasn't allowed to have a
fucking owl feather they don't like them on fuckers and bake the task if if uh someone
refuses a reading and you do it anyway well it's like someone refuses a reading I don't think many
So what do you play?
Did that chord have anything written on the back of it?
Yeah, it says symbolism.
It says healing.
Here's a picture.
In case you can see that, there's a beautiful pocket.
Let me see if there's a,
I do see like an Indian face under it too.
Oh wow, you can't, I think you did some pretty picture.
Yeah, there's a really amazing artist named Susan Sedon Boulay and it says Hawks symbolism
Healing vision rebirth and spirituality
There are many species of hawk each with its own legends and associated folklore the the birds have symbolized healing
Freedom vision and rebirth in Egyptian mythology. Isis the goddess of abundance and fertility
assumes the shape of a hawk as she gives birth to her son Horace, who then dies and is reborn.
She also becomes a hawk to join her husband Osiris in the underworld. Native Americans associate
the hawk with potent magic and uses feathers in healing rituals and in ceremonies to bring rain.
Yeah, I like him cards. Yeah, the Hawking and in the owl they put it pretty close
Yeah, I would say awareness and also, you know, in the bottom of the deck. There was this card. It's the peacock
I mean, I just turned over the deck. Oh, wow. Look at that picture. That's pretty. Yeah. That's nice
I've seen that picture before that's a popular picture
And this is also, you know, like, it's also, it says the peacock, it says, vision, wisdom,
beauty, and guardianship.
The many eyes of the peacock's tail feathers are associated with vision and wisdom.
In Greek mythology, the bird was a symbol of the goddess Hera, who kept it in her temple
as a many-eyed guard.
Muslims of Java believe the peacock guards the gate to paradise.
uh uh may um symbolize the soul okay so many many eyes i do love i grew up around peacocks
actually they brought a man oh really you think he's the first one on there you said greek you know
i'm i'm greek you're greek second generation greek second generation italian and fifth generation
We got I know um thing that is is Greek. I believe and we also have Apollo Apollo comes in the chat
See he's a Greek and yeah
Yeah, so we got Greeks. We got Canadians. We got a
Got a lot of Canadians. Mm-hmm. We do I noticed that
Hey clips, I will not read for you, but I don't know my big clips. This is a show about
kind of like. It does say psyche. Yeah, it's like, you know, it was more gear
tortera. No, I just made it more of a. Yeah, you went into the trauma bill for a
while. Yeah, I went through a little too much of trauma. It's okay, but babe. You pulled your
ass out a bit. Yeah, I'm, oh, I think I'm not in a very enjoyable, enjoyable place with the show.
I'm a lot more relaxed and also I'm more like a fighter.
Yeah, well, you're not fucking drunk at the time either.
I was very, very nice at the beginning and very like, you know.
Nah, you were drunk.
I was drunk. I was the drunk. I just had to do it.
You were. I mean, you know, get drunk every once in a while, get all fucking up and you was doing it to the point where he turned that fucking roller into a bender.
Yeah, oh, I think I drink almost every day and plus that would
About a day. Yeah, I would just like it was you know, I would just like wake up turn the camera
I remember one time you had a bunch of cans and you was dipping them up see if there was anything left to
I was like
Damn man
Well, I don't but you know, we all gonna go through it. I started neck it
I mean, I'm I fuck I ain't got no modesty
It's not in me to be modest and how I started out naked because everybody talked because of my voice
I was a dude and I had to prove the fact that I wasn't
Amber I need to mod Amber
Amber
Amber HHH age
Let's get you. Oh, I amber
And see
Yeah
Yeah, I'll be against a lot of motherfuckers be calling shit and fucking doing what they're done. Yeah, right
I just hope that he
Lays off because it's like he's like well now you've done made it fucking
Out there. Oh, we all know if you see the song I did about him. I mean I made a song
Here's a song. I like it. Yeah, you'll like this one. Here we go. I mean this today
Um, yeah, this is this is my response
And I did him and I did like you know, he was texting me and then I was like and I
He kind of like I knew you were obsessed with me, but I was saying he's obsessed with me, but he okay, so here
This is the song I made today
Enjoy this one here. Okay, it's gonna be good. Yeah
Downloads where are you? Okay?
My nice. Oh, wait. Okay. I put picture. Okay. I need to do video. Okay. Share video. There we go
Perfect. Okay. So here's the video
He's all up in the thread saying we met on Mars, talking about my soul like he owns the stars, saying I'm in his rights, saying I'm in his dreams, but he's down in LA while I'm ruling the streams.
I'm up in the ether, he's stuck in the chat, I ward on my roses while he's typing in caps, it must be the fumes, it must be the tea, he's feeding on my shadow like a currency.
Like it's a girl
When Dex on gossip, you on your job, you hating hard
Dropping links like tarot cards, you call me cult, I call you fan
You're the sequel out of a plan, say you miss me, we never met
That's a bull kind of internet, I'm a constellation, a common thread
I'm a sermon, you're the unread, why you so sad?
nice grappers your devotion's pure disaster say it louder spell it right love's not cold you
can't rewrite you're talking to the miratoni not to me you can't throw the truth on you my
Why are you so obsessed Tony?
These cars make you sad
You fell in love with a myth
And I made that little cry
There you go, it's the short one
That is cool as shit
Alright fuck, I even had to chuckle on that sec
Thank you. I'm getting kind of better at it, but the cool thing is like the program I use it has like
over a hundred styles of music and then you can kind of choose as many as you want and blend them
together and so it kind of you know they all sound unique and I just do experimenting you know
just like I'm learning some different styles of music and I tell you what the program you're using
I do think so because I've tried a bunch of them, and a lot of them sound like...
Which one did you end up using?
I use, it's called aimusicgen.ai.
And so if anyone wants to know, that's how I also do most of the videos through that too,
but I do make some other videos, I can animate them on another program,
and there's a few different programs I use, but...
It's but that's that's really I recommend that one for people want to experiment with the music and and things like that because
AI music Jen mus ic g n dot AI
Music and it's jam like the geo gen like generator
Yeah, and then it's like basically we'll take you to the landing page as a space where you put in the lyrics and then you choose
You know, but styles you'd like and then you generate it. It's a free version to the free version. You can't I got it
It's right there. I'm using the new
Oh good the new browser because I got it
I think what it's faster than the Microsoft one and if anybody wants to like
Be tutored or like because I can give a lot of good tips and things like that, you know, it's like I would be happy to you know
See we I gotta get your phone
Oh, yeah, definitely. Yeah, because I want to yeah
I want to I want to do your astrology and I want to make you some art and and music too
So yeah, cuz I need me damn opening song
Oh, yeah, while I'm waiting for people to come in. I need me just a short sweet fucking, you know, like a
Fucking you basic bike or something. Mm-hmm. Oh, yeah, definitely and it's like and then
Yeah, there's just it's so good that you can you can mix like your own ideas
And then they can come to life, you know, just like, it would, before you would have, it would be impossible, you need to hire a band or get a recording studio or, you know, now you can do it in basically minutes, right?
Yeah.
I know it would, God, do you remember one name?
First came in fucking got real like in 98 99
It was just Microsoft chat back then and then
Fucking yeah, who came into it? I think that is
Mind your own beeswax
He says you can't use AI coding on your info for tutoring. You still need to know the code. No, you don't that's the point
You don't need to know
I'm making the website without knowing coding because coding is too I know it's like you're a coder and it's like you're very like
Oh, okay, but you know, there is shit for a stupid people that doesn't force that
I'm not smart. I'm not smart enough to figure out the coding. Okay. I know
It would take me forever. Okay be warned. I yes, I can tutor however I like because I'm teaching people that I'm not gonna teach them how to code
I mean, I don't know how to code, but I know how to
Get up on your skin call you stupid. I know
I mean that is, you have that little prickly side to you.
I do notice you have that little prickly side.
I like it, the prickly side, baby.
I know you're a six year old coder, but I mean that's good.
I'm a-
We're not all that fucking smart, baby.
I'm a 44 year old idiot, basically.
I mean, I can turn on a computer, I know how to use-
Don't hold it against us.
Look at what he can do.
You ain't giving him credit for what he can do.
You just fucking damning him on what he can.
Yeah
By fucking telling somebody you're stupid instead of saying damn dude
You figured this much out in this short amount of time too and a time my Russian friend
Is was in the chat tonight you missed her, but she was here earlier and uh
And I told her about the show today, and I'm really excited that she, uh...
Oh, no, it's cool.
The song I made about her, I mean, this is a song I made with her, um, you know, and
then, then I told her about the show, and this is a little BFF song, so I'll put this
up, here we go.
This is the song I made.
This is the track, and this is the Russian song, right?
Yeah, this is for my Russian friend.
Oh, this is cool to want to just match, yeah.
Yeah.
Very beautiful.
My dad's pretty
许诺
That fits her because now I've seen him put you over you know
That does that fits her
She's a good-looking kid man. That's a nice song. You're staying here staying here. You're coming
So the thing that is coming up. He's a he's a nice guy. Here we go. He's in Canada here. Good evening
Hello, how you doing? Hey psych. Yeah, I didn't mean to insult I didn't mean to insult you or well
No, I just think you're you're you took it the wrong way like I mean
I know but I'm never but the truth is I I don't know how to code. I mean, it's like I've studied
Do it like a little bit. I'm not good enough to ever teach anybody coding, but there are ways like what I have is like
I know how to use AI tools that will do the coding for you if you know how to talk to
Okay, but you say you want a tutor
I would say you can't just use the AI, I would give Tracy an hour of, here's how to do this on, check me, how to do this on the music generator.
Okay, that's different, that's different, that is different though.
You did say you want a tutor for coding. So I
You do need to know coding right? No, I didn't mean I could tutor for the AI too
Okay, okay, that's different like I wasn't trying to
Yeah, I was trying to click the wings man. Like I said in chat. I don't want you to fail
I'm trying to point out like hey, this is an issue here
Why, why, why are you making it?
I need like some, I'm like, hey, yeah, that's a good idea.
It's like, you know, it's like, because it is a good idea.
And I can, I can show you how to do amazing things.
Yeah, you can show me how to use that browser too.
I have like, I have ideas that I can put into.
The world now that I could not before because I can utilize these tools that take care of like the technical stuff
And I can put more of the creativity in it. That's what I mean. I didn't mean like
Okay, so there's just a misunderstanding there and I think you took it as as me saying that you can't even instruct for
How to use an AI coder and that's not what I meant at all. I would know
more into, like, I want to, you know, do more of the spiritual side of it, you know, and all that stuff.
But I wasn't trying to say it.
Why?
You know, you get a little cross.
You don't mean something that I don't know of. I'll accept that help.
But if it does come down to you have an actual coding question, I mean...
What do you mean? Yes, yeah, I will do the coding. That's the right. Oh, okay
But the thing to understand is the AI is not perfect. That's why you need to know
If there is if there is an issue in the code you still need to know it, right?
Yes, but you can work with that. You can like continue. Okay. Okay
I'm sorry my volume is really low. I can barely hear you guys. Let me just turn myself up because it's both of you
Okay, give me a sec
Yeah, but I don't, I don't mean to, you know, throw any shade or, you know, you're, you're a good guy. You guys, you are, you come up, you come up sometimes a little bit.
I'm opinionated. I am opinionated. I try not to push it, but I am opinionated.
That was, that will get you far too. I mean, it's like, you have, plus, you know, knowing how to code, that's a great, great skill.
Yeah, you're doing better than we are.
Let's be honest. I can't afford a coder and I can't learn the code. I get it
But let's be honest. I'm at the end of my career here. I mean, I don't get a lot of work at this age, right?
Yeah, but the thing is like
58 I'm
60 and I'm still working 50. I'm not saying that that can't work. I'm just saying there isn't a lot of work
for a 58-year-old coder who really just does like side job, you know what I'm saying?
What is it? Don't you learn from home music?
Yeah, yeah, that's...
Yeah, I don't know.
What is it?
Are you on Fiverr or something?
Are you on Fiverr?
Because they have a lot of coding jobs.
Because I haven't been doing it my whole career.
It's a career that I took up later, later in life, so I didn't advance as far where
I would be really comfortable at this point.
I think it's that you utilizing the AI plus you having the coding knowledge.
I think you could even go further than you think, because there's people
that need to learn both or like, you know, it's good to know both, right?
Really, I know AI is doing so much that people used to do.
Yeah, but you know technology moves so fast people used to write to do math my father until he passed away
And he did like large transactions in real estate. He had a wow if you're a pen ledger until he passed
He never used a computer ever
And he refused to look around because the computer he was fine with that right it is
You know, of course, his secretary, you know, and people didn't know how to do that, but him as himself,
he likes to go fast and not use computers and stuff.
Everything with pen and paper back then.
Yeah, and yeah before calculators people used to do long division and stuff and now
Yeah, I was a kid when when I remember we came available for the home, right?
Yeah, like I was a kid when they went home computers and and computers in schools first became a thing
So yeah, I was right at the beginning of it, too. I loved it right from the beginning. I've been a computer nerd from the start
Remember we sit in a elementary school. I remember I was in my thirties nineteen fucking
What was it 98? I got my first one. They were giving them away at Walmart. All you had to do
is buy the monitor
And uh paid the sales tax on it
Yeah, and that was it. They were giving away e-machines
Yeah, one of the first ones one of the first cheap home ones like the Atari
400 or something like that. I see I didn't I
Couldn't play them games. No, this was a gaming console, but it also had the coding aspect
Yeah, you could get a cartridge where you could do coding you really couldn't do much compared to what you
It's gotta be in the 80s though, it just has to be in the 80s.
It wasn't in the Atari that came out with the Pong game.
Late 70s, early 70s, yeah.
That was the seven, I was seven, eight years old when that game came out.
Yeah.
And then I'm breaking, that was...
Like six years old. I was like, I wouldn't then I wouldn't then a Nintendo that the NES with duck hunt and Super Mario Brothers on one
cartridge that came with a little gun. Yeah, and these things like I
Got interested in coding at that point like all you could really do is maybe like draw a few lines on the screen
But at least you kind of learned some fundamentals, right?
And it got me interested in it and I just kind of carried on as a hobby
and then I took it up as as a
career as a job later in life.
Yeah, I dropped my, I didn't knock my camera out of you.
I thought you fell, it looked like you fell.
My camera fell.
I, well I remember when I was in fourth, fifth grade or something, we had these, we'd
go to computer lab, right, and we'd have a green, green screen, like it just had the
green, the color green on it.
We would play Oregon Trail, we would play Carmen San Diego, and we'd have the big floppy
And my first computer, I think, when I was like 13 or 14, it was a 386 or a 486.
I mean, I've been in the 486 and it didn't have the internet at that time.
I get that that was my next computer that they had.
You know what Cecil did?
He put the computers up in the bank in Tampa, Florida.
I think it was Bank of America when Bank of America first got that building.
He was on the crew putting the computers up on top of the buildings.
And there was, oh my gosh, remember the hack,
like there was hacking movies, and like now it's like,
even, I mean, hacking is a whole different thing, and.
Yeah.
I was never even, I was, it was a little technical for me,
but I was, here's what I was able to do.
I was able to call customer service
and have people walk me through things.
And that was basically what the AI does.
Oh, so you was like, hey, Colin.
What I do is I say,
I say well give me instructions and I'll look at them and I'm like I don't know what this means and so I'll say
Can you pretend like I'm 10 years old and I don't know anything about anything and just walk me step by step
That's gonna be
I mean, that's how I that's how I need the computer to or then it will make me like a checklist
And I will like put it in all details
I need that sometimes, I really because I know things that I don't know, I'm like I'm
really, I had to do something called like a deployment, I'm trying to make an admin
console for my website, and so I had to put it on something called, some kind of like,
And then you have to put into GitHub
and you're deploying things.
And I just couldn't get it right.
It kept saying fail, fail, failed, deployed.
And then I finally asked,
I clicked on this browser that one where it says assistance.
And then I asked the assistant,
the assistant just did it for me.
Like in 10 seconds.
Oh man, is that what's on that browser?
I just downloaded, oh, I can't wait to get hold of that.
You'll love it, you'll love it.
It's like, and I was able to try.
That's your whole thing set up.
I even got the music thing that everything's all there. Yep. That's the site. I see Alex is being bipolar again
Jane what happened what yeah come fill me in on the game what happened
Last I saw the Jays were leading, but I don't know what inning it was
Oh
Jays won right on
Are these the blue Jays or the yeah, yeah the Toronto blue Jays. They're in the World Series, then
One game sevens, but we're in the World Series
By the way, I'm sorry. I did it. I did like end kind of abruptly this morning
Because I was like people were getting into politics, which I like. Yeah. Yeah, we noticed that
And then he said some of the work like certain codes because I'm monetized
I'm privy to some certain information of like don't say certain things or you know, you know
So I have to be careful. It wasn't like I was trying to shut you guys down or anything. I just
Can't
You don't want to risk your shit over people's opinions
Yeah, and
There's a time and place for those shows, but it's probably better for a non monetized channel to go especially on YouTube
Go to another fucking, you know rumble is good for politics. Yeah
Yeah, the commercials on rumble are like, you know, they're about guns
Commercials
Okay, here we go Jay. Oh
There he is. Okay good
Oh yeah, I think there it is.
How you doing?
Jays have gone to the World Series.
Right on. That's thrilling.
First time since 93.
Wow.
Jays, is that your name?
Is Jays fan or are you named after the Jays?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I'm not a fan Jason. But yeah, just Friday. Yeah, that's the doctors and the Roger Center. It is
Okay, so so me and loser have a bit of a few going then for the next week and a half or whatever
Actually for the next four games because Jays are gonna sweep, right? So
You say
Who's they playing the Dodgers the Dodgers?
Yeah
No
They've won
Yeah, since since 93 whatever. Yeah one last year
Yeah, see yeah, because everyone knows man, right loser, right? Right. That's right
I just friendly jabbing with the with the guy in chat who's out on the west coast there
I
yeah
I mean you can't dim a man for wanting a team to win
but see I don't have an investment in
either way cause you red soxing
and so fuck it
I'll go for tomorrow
did you know who music biz marty was Tracy
have you heard of music biz marty
he was a
he really
yeah
Oh, you were okay. Well, you know, he came on my close. You were a lot of titty pitches
Yeah, he was actually a Cyrax troll. I don't know if you know who he is now. Yeah
Yeah, he started coming on my show when I started doing lives
He'd come up with Jamie Rose and then he wrote me and he said hey
Can you do tarot to do sports betting to predict these and I was like, oh, I wouldn't really like use it to predict that
I was like, but tell me the tell me the color of their pants
I'll have a look at their bus in their uniform and I'll pick I'll give you a over-under and that's it
You call me underdog because I would I usually say
And then I then I then he would send me money because he'd win and I said because I was just like no
No, Marty. He would go around looking for people like cyrex and he could fuck with yeah
He doesn't know he came across the right page and
We ended up fucking he was he came up on the panel and everything
And then I was trying to get stony's number to send him a fucking titty pictures
So I ended up on discord and I ended up with wings 007
his number and I sent him a titty picture thinking it was stony and then I ended up on Marty's
number and I ended up so I ended up sending four guys a fucking titty picture for I finally got the right damn
phone number for stony
So I could send the titty picture I wanted and that
And they used to have late night streams and I I'd find them two wings 007 and oh my god, we used to have so much fun
Yeah
I think he like was the version looking at me like oh is this guy gonna be the next cyrax or something like that. Yeah
That's what he does is he likes me and he was like he was really kind to me and he would send me money when he won the sports betting
He was always just kind and then he just passed away really really suddenly like right and it was just yeah
He went
He went fast he did it was you know, I bet it was
It was interesting because I just started doing the stream and then it was like that and basically I wasn't really
I wasn't monetized yet or making any money and all of a sudden he said to me 15 bucks 60 bucks
And I was like whoa, this is pretty fucking cool
If you didn't have to he didn't have he could have not told me he wanted stuff like that
I didn't know anything about sports really. I was just telling I was like, oh what name what name is the cuter name or something like that
Who's the cuter?
Oh loser. Sorry. I forgot it is baseball, right? There's lots of superstition in baseball. So yeah, I guess that counts
I guess that counts
A lot of superstitions.
It would be kind of terrible if your superstition was like,
never change your jock strap, you know, or wash your jock, you know.
Oh, they've got some weird ones, man.
They've got some weird ones.
Sports, like some players in various sports have some weird ones,
but baseball is particularly known for having superstitions.
The baseball that has like, there's like, there's some,
is there the Boston or New York or New York where they had this goat
that they bring in or something like that?
And if the goat did something, but what is this one?
There was that, yeah.
That's been broken now right? Both those teams behind. Oh yeah I remember that game. I cried.
I did that picture had blood coming out of his damn shoe. Oh yeah I remember that game.
Kurt was it Kurt Schilling? No. Who was it? Was that picture that had the
the ankle? Yeah with the injury on the ankle? Kirk Schilling I hate that guy.
Yeah I'm not a fan but it was him yeah.
I
I'm not sure see look at the chat site people are listing some of the superstitions
They don't get to talk shaft or the king of socks. I have the stuff. That's why the red socks is there
I think it's a bloody by the season
Imagine the amount of fermented. Oh my goodness Bay
I need to find out who the eclipse is though. She's uh interesting or here. I don't know. I'm not sure who they are, but
But uh, no one of the official
So but it's okay. I mean it's like, you know, they've been around for a long time
I just don't like trolls that are like
maliciously evil
Yeah, oh bae is uh is kind of uh
wrapped in a bit of a drama at the moment, eh?
Indirectly, like the drama is not specifically about Bay,
but because Bay was the provider of it,
they became a part of the story.
I heard something about it, yeah.
Well, I think a couple of weeks ago, I was like.
Oh, sorry, Bay.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
I was clipped on,
Oh, um, trip, trip kick about 10 times, like in the, with the, with the beat of stuff and,
and like then the Alexander stuff, there's so much stuff going on. Like I was like, oh my
god, every day I'm like in so much AI. Hey, Gotti, what's up? Gotti's in the chat.
Gotti, my Russian friend, um, let's hear the show. And she also, she wrote me a note and she said,
oh, you have to send me the notification when you're going live again, because she's like,
I'm really excited to be able to share on the show with people I know.
My family doesn't watch the show, nobody, and I don't watch the show.
That's why I don't do Facebook.
I can do Facebook live, but that's like family side of the internet.
Yeah, but I think my little brother one time, I think commented once in the chat
Which is she cute? I can put a picture. I have a picture
I do have pictures. She's beautiful. Actually, she's she's gorgeous. Here's her pictures. She's texting me
She said it's okay. I think
Yeah, she is
You know, well, you know Russian women are known for their their beauty, right?
So I'll show you some
Some of her as they get older they get fat though
Well here. Oh, if you put look so here you go. We'll put on full screen
Wow
Okay, oh
That's a beautiful picture. Yeah, she is
She's pretty gorgeous so very classy bride
And then she has a firefighter she's like you know chick woman's firefighting so she yeah
That she's a chainsaw on this one. She's a pretty badass and
Let me see. Oh, yeah, she sent me a picture winch. Okay, and then she has herself and blonde hair here
I mean, I'll show you. Oh, here's an AI one. I I think I
Had her right right on a cat of this black cat
Now you're doing that with this browser, right? You can't I think I did that one with chat gpt
and uh oh here's I did her as the high priestess right there uh that's in the music video ain't it
uh well I I I can't I can put that I should put that in the music video that that was I mean and
here's a few like look at look at me with the guitar oh no it's with that silly grin here I am with the
I like that one
Yeah, I'm kind of it is my it is like I do look like that. I mean it's like
Look at there's no you do not have those shoulders. I don't
That's Rudy you need to eat more
And not just fish tacos, baby, I know I love this
You need some steak and potato
You know what I even it every day Tracy is a McDonald's every I like this one a lot of me. I like that one. I
Wish I had those arms. I wish I was
Here I'm at a baseball game
That's not that looks good. I like that I do here. I'm as a
What is it the crocodile hunter or something?
Sorry there
And here's your here's your here's her again. Wow. Look at those eyes
Brown eyed girl, yeah, I would say I would say
Russians who have that fiery red blood, right? Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah
So yeah, so but I'm really excited. I think I get to see her in December
But she loved she really had a good time at the show today, and she's like, oh, I had a great time and
She said she loved Tracy. She was like, oh
Fun to go riding in
Yeah, she wants to go she's I think it's turn her boyfriend or go are gonna
You know do a trucking together and that's gonna be pretty cool
See so now we're gonna do that a long time ago, but he was more into building motors than
driving trucks
Well, that's I mean, that's that's great, too. You know, it's like more it's like the
He was building motors for the racetrack over there just south of
temple, Florida
Well, my dad actually
You know, I saw some pictures
Memorial whatever but he had a picture of himself in his legs
It is like kind of like I think it must have been the 70s
And is he had this like kind of leisure suit looking thing and he had these two motorcycles that he just bought and
My grandparents my mom's parents
did not like him because
Well, my grandma was because he had these motorcycles and she was afraid and he actually drove my mom
Home from Palm Springs to Los Angeles to her house, which is a two-hour motorcycle ride, right on the freeway
And then my grandma's so freaked out with my grandfather saw my dad
He's like he's a smart guy and he so
They eventually warmed up to him because you know no it turned out to be you know
My mother's afraid to me when I dress him. I love this
I mean, I've seen clubs that have got attorneys and, you know, it runs just like the Army.
Yeah.
You know?
It's uh
It's very military
Well in Palm Springs, we did have like these Suzuki like these red Suzuki
Scooter in Palm Springs. There's this is a head this good a crowd
We had these we had these red scooters right then not not not like that they can pull scooters
But like these little red Suzuki things you get drive around and so we were like 12, you know
Right, he's like little
Cecil used to build golf carts. He had a company and they would he'd go to like the trailer parks and the
Nuda speeches and shit and he'd make them suckers go like 40 45 miles an hour and they'd have fucking
It was a gang of fucking golf cart. Oh man drunk on golf carts racing them
That was fun. Okay. Well, what is this person? So someone asked about
Read but someone asked how much I charge for readings. I don't know. Oh, hon. Victoria J. Who knows Victoria J? Hello. Oh, that's yeah
she was
She was on on a beat is last night. Yeah, we spoke to her last night for a bit
I
Came on the vegan Patriot wig and I was like, I wanna talk to Victoria. That's right. Yeah, I gotta go
Because I was gonna press her on because she was like oh blogger you like hit your mom or something like that
And I hear her yelling her mom all the time her mom's in the next room when she's like
She here is that what you're saying?
Someone mentioned her okay. Oh, so someone said I should do a review for Victoria. I would I would I don't think Victoria's a better
I think she's funny. I've never seen her face or anything. I just seen her on clips and stuff
I think she's funny. She's an IP to and stuff and
Has a funny personality, but I don't know if she just left because I was asking for stuff
Wait, you didn't see what happened with her in
Someone else on the panel? No, I came up. I came up like basically when she was just on with blogger
They're all talking, but I wasn't I just like was like I don't I don't really watch I came just for my show
And then went on that stage and then she left as soon as I got there
She wasn't I was like there and then she didn't respond and then she's like oh
Well if you were the issue it certainly wasn't mentioned because her and blogger just one at each other immediately
Well, yeah, I know, I do, I do hear a little bit about her saying, oh, you did the vlog.
Yeah. Wait, wait, I gotta tell you, man, Goddy, what an ass. Holy fuck. You know when you dropped
this last night? Look, look, he's laughing about it now. It is funny. I have to admit,
it is freaking funny. You know when you dropped this last night?
Yeah, it was me him Jamie and
School were on panel, but school had just dropped but he was still in in the back
Right, so he was still part of the chat
So we were all talking whatever and then Jamie dropped and then I just asked God he and
School if they saw my exchange with blogger earlier on be just panel
And then it went from there and God he fucking he switched his name to mine to think that is
He took a snapshot of me
He made it his avatar and he went over to bloggers live stream
I was at the moment and tried to get on as me and I'm like you bastard
I'm gonna go over and tell him I'm telling him don't fucking do it. Don't don't so you went anyways
Well, I have to go over and say blogger. That's not me man. Oh
I'm still like I listen to like your Johnny did send me like this clip
And she's like this Gotti and I it's sounding like you a little bit. I did I was like damn
I was like I can't be like Alex and I think this person's this person and stuff
And I was like that did sound a little bit like Gotti like doing like a little bit of a slow voice like
Oh
It was funny even when I was telling him don't do it I was laughing like this is funny, but I'm like don't do it man
Don't get me in trouble
Blog is the character I love him so much
Yeah, so yeah, whatever that was
It was it can be so much fun. At least he doesn't play with fire anymore
Man the first time I met him. I was on the live stream when he cut his ass feet
Oh my god. Hey, hey, did you ever see Chris K fight the Dorf?
the Dorf
Tracy, you know who Chris K is or no? I don't think so. Okay. He's like he's like this
It's kind of was he's a white guy. I think he's in Vegas or something like that. He's kind of like
Riverside, California. Yes. He has this kind of like, you know
He does
But he doesn't do it on YouTube. He doesn't on rumble. I think I all right
But he used to do on YouTube, but then he had his fight with the he's yelling at this guy and like some parking lot
And then they they scroll over to the guy. It's a black dwarf
Yeah, and then the black door knocked him out I can actually play the clip no way
Funny, I'll bring it up. Oh my god. I want to see that
I have fucking the dwarf one. Yeah, dwarf. Yeah, he doesn't even like he doesn't he's not even like
you know ashamed or it was kind of it was pretty funny. It's funny. It was funny. So it's on a
rumble like they syndicate a lot of people on rumbles. Yeah, I got a rumble account um messenger
hooked me up with rumble
I am uh, yeah, I actually I'm I'm there's somebody named panel verse vo D's that
Decades like a lot of people for like me on beta blogger. I think and
Few other big, you know, K probably stand man stuff. I'm good to good times
Okay, so I can go
This is gonna be funny.
Yeah, it is a great clip.
Okay, I need to...
I need to go to the other thing.
I...
Trip kicks page, and it's probably I think it's on page. Okay. Here's did that channel ever get put back up the twit kick
Um, I don't know. I remember that got taken down. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, I mean the okay
There's twit twit kid got taken down, but trip kick is still up and then he's on rumble
So I'm at the rumble site right now and okay. Here's Chris K gets punched by a midget. Okay, so I'm gonna pull this up
Okay, so I'm gonna share the screen and
This is how it went. Okay, and guys, there is some racial language in this though, so do not.
Okay, so here we go. Okay, allow. Okay. Okay, there it goes. I pull it up. Okay.
Attention, law enforcement, you took an oath to protect yourself.
You see it?
You see the screen?
Make it both.
Yeah, I see it.
I will.
It's like, yeah.
I did it.
One second.
Your smile looked different.
Now imagine fixing that in 30 seconds.
You don't see anything.
Hey, don't get the suit off the pool, Connor.
You better check yourself.
What are you doing?
I ain't no person.
Now, get on camera.
Do all that.
I ain't no part broke.
You better check yourself.
I don't give a fuck.
Look at the government.
Check yourself, Connor.
It's shit.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
What are you talking about?
What's up?
What's happening?
What's going on?
You don't know what I'm talking about.
We're those rubber blades whoa is that
I'm not saying we don't.
He said he heard his name.
Now what?
Yeah.
I was in a suit with sneakers okay that was that man that was that was funny yeah
I love that one. Getting taken down by Webster is funnier than anything like with Gary Coleman or anything like that. Yeah. Oh, yeah. That guy had a rough life.
I don't even mean it in in real life. I just mean like just thinking of the little kid Webster taking down Chris.
That's so precious she's a sweetheart cat. Oh, yeah, Tracy you're gonna stay up for a bit
Yeah, okay, so he has someone to talk to I'm gonna go grab a coffee and I'll be back. Okay. Yeah, I just put myself a sweetie
That was a mini Sandman, right?
Oh, gosh, yeah, but there's there is this I mean
Many sandman who said that that was a Alexander McQueen said
That's about right I can picture that I
Saw a man on camera the other day, but it was like from ten years ago
And he's like selling a Ugeo card or something like that and he's oh, yeah, that's when he first started out on YouTube
Mm-hmm
But he's always like, you know, he's always trying to cause like, you know start something that's what he does that's his YouTube character
He's good at it
Yeah
I mean, I don't mind him. It's like, you know, but um, you take him with the grain of salt and yeah
He's a drama queen
You little bit of yeah, he loves he loves chasing content to he loves to start stuff on my show. Oh, yeah
He likes to stir the shit pot
Oh my gosh, Lenore, Lenore, Lenore, I love the names you give them animals.
Yeah Lenore, I'm a Edgar Allen Poe the Raven and that's what it means like the night.
Lenore.
Lenore in French.
I know I scream at Mike and it's like my step son was named was Mike so when I'm screaming
Well, let me see if I I want to make you have an AI song soon
I think let me see if I have a good time
Because it's gonna be the opening while I'm getting things situated
I'll say you also go to my openings. Well, this is like the opening for my
It's kind of a rap song actually, you know Goddy or no, you know, I know I've got a yeah, I
Have a cute song body here
Out of New York came a storm on wheels rolling in smooth with the mafia feels
Cuban cigar lit like it's temper pizza in one hand hot dog for dinner said psyche on board had to switch the scene
Left some poor woman screaming on live stream
Trolled her down to the void and back then crashed my show like a heart attack gotty made man
But they still my friends
Yeah, love you got it till the bitter end we fight we troll but we friends forever my friend
He thinks he's God with the lowercase g in a wheelchair still stomping through the live feed
Laughin' at chaos like it's comic relief brought
Spunky too, now that troll's a gem
Mean one sweet ones they all jumped in
Cameras glitchin', chat on fire
Mods beggin' me to cut the wire
But nah, I like my circus, I love this mess
Every troll's just a test-offin' mess
Got you rude, absurd, and free
But deep down you got loyal
But they're still my friends
Yeah, love you gotty till the bitter end
We fight, we troll, but we friends
Forever my friend
You called me a fraud, then defended my clown
Spam my chat, then held it down
You got layers, like a deep dish slice
Under all that shade
A heart made of ice, and maybe rice So let's light that cigar, raise the mic
Another night of chaos, welcome to psych You brought the drama, the heat, the fun
And weirdly it feels like
You're the one?
Got it, yeah you crazy but your family now Rollin' through fire still takin' a bow
No matter the madness, no matter the weather Within we troll
But we stick together
That's a good song. Yeah. I like that one. Not the one Gotti, guys. Do you know Crystal
tribe things yeah on that because that's when when he first came to the chat like
they're like oh he's on discord and some like
I don't know. I was like whatever it was. Yeah, that was cool. I made it personal right there.
But you know Crystal Marie? Yes, I do know Crystal. I asked you the Crystal Marie one,
because this is one of my favorites. I haven't seen that one either. You haven't seen that one?
Okay, good. This is pretty classic. I love how this one turned out. Crystal Marie.
I think it's this one
That's page once
I'll play the crystal maria page one is good to you, but I want to play one pages here, but um, uh, let's see
Okay, I think it's the one after that. Okay, so it's gotta. Oh what I do
Okay, okay, okay
How do I get that off the screen?
Okay, I just screwed up.
Okay, so.
Welcome back.
Hello.
Okay, there I'll allow.
Okay, so I didn't mean to do that.
Okay, remove.
So, okay, stop sharing that one.
Okay, it's this one.
I do I need to make sure 100% okay. Oh, yeah, this was this one right you got it
Oh
No, hey, oh
Welcome to
That's not it. Okay. That's one is this one
Chris, okay here
I hope it's got to be one of these
Me I'm gonna play just to me. Okay, so I think this one here. Come on
Let's get friends forever shit
You I have like literally like 50 of these I'm back. I
Just like I'm going nuts lately. Okay. It's gotta be this one
oh yeah that's her i love the beat
crystal marie, a midnight stream, neon eyes and conspiracy dreams
talking cops in the desert sands, tattoo maps and shaking hands
A tinfoil halo, ceiling fades in a chatroom chapel
Saints confess every broadcast feels like a holy mass
She's cookie, she's hot, she might be right
Dropping bombs in the middle of the night
White rose, black vans, symbol sex
Oh Lord, what will she say next?
Crazy close games and traffickers
Crystals leave with the digital saboteurs Truth or fiction doesn't matter much
She's fire and static and psychic too
That's so real
She's seen the symbol
And the cornfield glow, her angels whisper through the radio
There's always a villain and a secret cabal
And crystals, they're exposing it all
One moment sweet, next she's fierce
Tearing the veil with the crystal spear
Half prophecy, half improv show
Either way, the crowd won't go
Wrapped in porcelain skin
She's kooky, she's hot
She might be true
The stream's on fire
And the pixels blue
Cold skanks, lies in shadow
Sex, here we go
even like, kind of like, because it doesn't know what they look like, but it's like, you
know, that kind of does look like a crystal a lot of time. The page one looks like page
some of the time. I look like me some of the time. It's funny how it, maybe based on the
name, it just, it just, people have a certain low AI is so close, isn't it? It's crazy.
Yeah. Yeah, it is. Yeah, I think it's a really great way to like put my feelings.
For a person into like a like a nice
Little package that they can you know have forever, and I
Know the chat GBT that it's it's a hell of a program
If you need to get things done that you can't figure out like paperwork or
Transfership from one state to another
Yeah
Basically all I need is a good instructions, you know, if I have good instructions, I can follow step-by-step, you know
You know exactly where to go exactly I mean as much details possible and like what to do I'm gonna try and do my taxes this year
I know I'm tired spending 250 bucks and now they got AI so hell and walking right to it
But AI is being integrated into everything right like a lot of apps
It's being integrated into a lot of services like if you mention the tax if you go to an account now a lot of tax
Services are going to use yeah elements of AI in what they do. So it's it's
It's been integrated being integrated everywhere. Yeah, right
It's a great way a lot of time, you know, but you know, I have to know like, you know
It's gonna be certain ones are better for certain tasks. Like, you know, sure
There's some that are great to tell you what I went to was it credit comma and
They've got an AI app walks you right through it. I was gonna do it last year
But I owed a lot of money for federal taxes
because I worked for myself and I saw I went and H&R Block like I did every year.
But the more I'm looking at it in advance for January,
I'm thinking about just letting it walk through the credit card and do it that way.
It is free and I'll have to come up with $250 out of a paycheck before I even get any money back.
Yeah, I mean I will like it's gonna change the job market for sure because it's like there's so many
It's gonna be basically I said in the future. It's gonna be there's the jobs are gonna be like
AI coders and you know robot
Trainers
Looking at them from Boston Dynamics for a personal robot and not
They're coming down on the prices when I was looking at was like 25,000
Yeah, oh man, but they've come a long way
Like is it a sex robot or what?
It was just a regular robot. You know, I would want to have sex with my robot. So I need like a smash I
Need I need some and you've seen some of the robots for you guys
Oh my god, you can change their face. Yeah, everything
Do you only complain that I'm seeing I was looking up was the weight of the the dog
The robot I mean they can 100 pounds or more
Yeah, oh, yeah, I would think at least yeah, and they're shipping um, you know
And to have the countries to be worked on everything. There's a whole bunch of YouTube videos out there about those dolls
Yeah, you can actually look at um, there's one. What's it called? It's called
Mm-hmm. I think it's on Vice TV is called something something sex something and have this one chick that goes around and she goes to like that the
the real doll factory and they have all like the private parts like hanging on
It's like they have the it's just like it's kind of creepy
Like a scene out of a science fiction movie from the 70s or something
Something like that. Yeah
Logan's run something, you know, one of those old 70s sci-fi things where it's like, oh, yeah, you just see a
line of
Bodies in different stages of being developed or different stages of being assembled, you know
It was like when Q was
The character Q came on Star Trek
Yeah
No, sorry psych. I didn't mean to throw it off. Go on. Oh, no, no, no, you did it all
They I mean, yeah, they are
The sex robots are gonna be pretty good actually like even the conversation like with the character AI
There's a website called character AI and it's basically you can create a character
Like and what they look like you can even animate them and have them talk to you and stuff
But and then they'll it'll be just generating a conversation and it's like but it's actually like
interesting conversation and this tailored to their personality.
Yeah, that leads to the foreplay.
I did with Alexander, we made it Alexander McQueen like pull me over and all of a sudden,
you know, he's trying to be professional.
I'm like, he's like, okay, I call for backup.
And then I say, okay, all the cops start taking off their clothes and I'll come have sex with me.
I used to write letters like that in jail and sell them.
Oh my god, I wrote one. It was it wasn't like a cop one
But this one was at a restaurant in a linen closet and I'd leave a space
Where they could put whatever his name they want and I'd sell the lettuce the dirty lettuce to
the
The Queens the Latin Queens and Kings when they got busted up here in New England
I was in jail with them. There was 240 of us nine of us were white
12 were black and the rest of them were Latin Queens. Yeah
Oh my god
Didn't know a damn thing what they're saying
Well, I know we have, you know, flirty diamonds and I don't know if you know auto, but we had the flirty diamond.
Auto was very taken with flirty, you know, dirty diamonds and stuff like that and he
He found out she was it was oh, I remember that day. Yeah
That was a great day. He's like, I don't care. Okay. They started like screaming lotion on his body and like rubbing it
I love flirty diamond. She's the best tour I've ever seen
She is, I swear.
My God, once you get her going, you cannot stop her.
Like, I mean, with the insulting in that,
like once you get her into that trolling thing,
man, you cannot stop her.
She just goes.
I do, I like it.
She's the only one that her poor mommy
and got away with it.
You know, she was rubbing green animal
under her dress one day.
That's because curiosity killed the cat.
Yeah.
I was like stop it. You know, I don't really care. Yeah, stop, but I want to see
She did a live stream was about a week ago
Rumble it is on rumble. Yeah
Well, they just syndicate from YouTube, I think, you know, but yeah, she's, they put her on the
panel versus B.O.G., that's what the rumble account is called, panel versus B.O.G.'s. And it's like,
if you want to see, you know, Bita always leads her streams, but they put all B, they put all
my streams, even if I delete them, they'll put the whole thing on rumble, even if there's porn
I don't think they seem to care and so they put it they put all my streams up there
And you know pabs don't you pebbles pebbles? Yes, they are in pebbles. Well back before she got with Zaya
I was doing a nude live stream. She scoffed that scum bitch and put it on the other app
What the hell is that? Oh start to dig
Okay
Discord! She took the fucking thing and put it on Discord and then came in my chat. She said you're all over Discord now!
Oh jeez.
I was actually on Careless Cates. When I came into the panel verse, Careless Cates was not one of my biggest fans and everything.
page in our discord of all the all the porn bombs that she does she documents all the porn bombs
uh-huh so you talking about uh barry's old lady yeah exactly i love her yeah she's i i get a lot
i do yeah i uh she's actually really friendly actually um if you i did you see what barry looked
Yeah, if that was actually him, which I'm glad to believe it is him. He just looks like a normal guy. He looks cool
Yeah, it's fine. He looks cool
Yeah, he's definitely not this is not the same. I mean he sent me a dick pic and a and a butt
Yeah, he did but I don't think who hasn't sent you a dick pic
Well, it's just actually just you know and bearer the only ones that have oh mr. Big Pipe sent me
Outline him as we know through his underwear a couple pictures
I tell you, it's gotta make you feel good.
I mean, at least they think enough about you,
send them pickers.
Oh, I'm very flattered, yeah.
Uh-huh, I mean, shit, if they didn't like you,
they wouldn't send you the picker.
So loser, loser sent you as well?
Loser, what'd you send?
Did you send somebody else?
Loser's saying.
me
Me me as I asked who hasn't oh who hasn't
Don't try and turn it around loser I would think for sure he would have been one of the ones to have sent it
Well, I when I was in my American flag speedo that day I was
Yeah, I put my legs in my head at one point and that is there's a there's a
YouTube account called fish tacos and dick with
Oh my goodness, I'm I'm uh, I'm all you have to be careful about you
I think I'm I'm pretty decent. I mean it's like for being such a skinny guy. I think I'm I have an okay, uh
Yeah, I've got abs, I guess, right?
So, I don't know, maybe.
You can have a good stomach, and I like the hair.
Thank you, I have my hair back.
You need a little bit more from the waist up,
as far as muscle.
Yeah, I agree, yeah.
You need some like a protein drink or something like that.
I mean, I'm thin, psych, and I'm like,
I've got more,
more to my arm than you do, and I'm thin.
You're like too thin, unfortunately.
I'm 6'3", but I know, especially.
Like, I mean, you showed it last night.
I don't want to shame you.
This isn't about shaming you or anything like that.
You're just, you're very, you're very thin, very thin.
Well, I mean, it's not like, I can go like that.
That'd be the tooth tip, but see, I have a nice.
You don't have any fat.
I don't have I'm a zero percent body. I'm six foot three. You just need to work on on like I lift weights every morning
And they're not special
I have a pull-up bar. I used to do I would start I started this year doing a few push-ups, but you know
Last pass. Well, see I don't wear a bra. So I have to lift weights every day
Otherwise I'm gonna fuck you to go away
Why
I
It's just funny that that's good
Don't worry. I lift weights every day. I mean that right there. That's that's good as a joke
But that's why I lift weights, so I don't have to worry bra
I could probably gain a hundred pounds and like that. I know that you might know
because it would go all in the wrong places you didn't look in like Sandman.
I was just going to think Sandman.
You'd be having a pot belly.
Yeah.
It was a little bit of a pop belly, but uh, I mean you can see my I'm so long like just imagine how like to get like muscles on
These it would take a while. I bet you were long when you were born like 23 inches 24 inches when you were born
I was 10 pounds exactly. I don't I don't remember how long I was, but yeah, I was I was 10 pounds exactly
Which is pretty big for like Christopher was 23 inches long
Oh wow
What are we talking about? I kind of blanked out there for a sec. What's 23?
How old? I was like we were almost two foot long
Yeah, what is like I didn't get my my son Christopher. Oh when he was born. Yeah, okay. Okay. Okay. Um
That's where uh me and psyche, uh, you know because he's the same age as my kid
I see. Okay. Yeah, that's that's where the commonality comes in. Mm-hmm. Yeah, and they're both quits
Yeah, well with a good personality
Hey, well, you know Alexandra said that she's she's things that she said I was like that
She thinks I'm like 90% straight and like 10% gay. I think I think it's the other way around. No, you're quick. Yeah
Yeah, I am I do consider myself gay, but I did date a woman once they both
I mean, you still look at a woman, you know, sexually, you're a man.
I think women are beautiful, it's just like, yeah, you just have no interest in fucking
them.
And that's also good because it's like, there's not like, you know, women don't like, women
always have guys after them, right?
And so it's like.
Comfortable to be like with a platonic person. That's not gonna be like trying to get your pants all the time
And that's why I like gay strip clubs. I can admire a man's body and I don't have to worry about him touching me
There are some gay for pay guys though, you know, there's there are probably some straight guys that uh
Actually, on TikTok, there's a lot of like, you know, because if you're smart on TikTok,
you know, some guys are going to be like, oh, I don't know, they're going to be like a homophobic
or whatever.
I've counted just a few, like maybe a very minority.
Most of them are like, you give them a tip or something like that, and they're like,
You know where I was shocked is I went back on Facebook because I had been off of it for a long time man
I didn't cancel anything. It just it wasn't interested with it
And now I got hit with so many fucking pervert brides
And dudes I was like damn it ain't family no more than the same thing with X
I went on that and I keep getting hit with that shit. I gotta hold the Elon Musk. I'm like, what the fuck's happening?
Yeah, it's pretty wild there now, man.
I have an Elon Musk, like I don't have many
Alternate accounts, but I do when I was on Emma's Emma Levite and I would go into her chat as both Nicholas Cage and Elon Musk
You know, I was, you know, I just got my none of the other and it would be kind of funny.
What's going on with you and Elise, by the way?
Elise, like not too much. She hasn't been streaming very much.
And I noticed that. See you, Alexander.
Yeah, Alexander was in the chat and Alexandra put me on a 30-day timeout with her, so...
You know I met Alexander
You know I met her in person you know I met her in person
Yeah, well, I ain't got much to say good about her either cuz she tried to set me up and then got fucking mad at me over
Tommy of all people Tommy James. Oh, wow. Yeah, we had a Tommy James clip with her recently. He came on
Oh my god
She got so mad. I was talking to her the night before
And I stayed up all night and she was planning on going she was you know considered about Salem and
Going to the Halloween event nice little shit. I'm only like 75 miles away
We can do a collab and everything was cool as hell.
And then she finished up her live and I saw Tommy was live so I went and got up on his panel and talked to him.
And she flipped the motherfuck out.
And I'm like, I'm not interested in fucking him, Jesus Christ.
But yeah, she got really jealous on me, and then I became a piece of shit
And then she did videos about me that I never watched. They're just unsubscribed. That's the God
I've never seen a damn
Attitude flip so quick
Yeah, I I know I do I do I had a great time when I met her and yeah, he's like she's I think she's super cool
She did I think yeah, there are there were some like
differences I warned you. I told you she'd flip on you
But she said but we're just taking a 30-day
Hi, and and then we're on like day eight or day nine or something like that
I'm counting it I want to I want to I could but I because I kind of like wanted to talk to her and stuff and
Feel like I'm on time out. No, she has to be the boss and a friendship kind of like beat up
You know, they have to wear the pants and the friendship
Yeah
What do you mean gay time? Did you just throw that in that's the first time I heard that one what that?
He's a gay about something. Oh Alexander a thing that is is a gay warlock. Oh Alexander thinks he's a gay
I didn't hear sure say gay, but
He's messing with me now
I didn't I saw her talk about some stuff, but I didn't hear that part of stuff
But I know it is I think is a very very straight guy
I am, and I don't care about anyone's sexuality.
Except for the person I'm with, obviously,
but other than that, do whatever you want.
I don't care as long as it's me or you're not hurting anyone.
Why don't you not hurt anybody
and you're not fucking with a kid?
Exactly well as I say as long as it's legal, and it's not hurting anybody, and I don't have to watch you know
Consensual whatever
I don't want to watch anybody. I don't want to know about people's sex lives at all
You know for my own for heterosexual I don't want to know about your sex life
It's yours, it's for your personal life.
That's what I said.
It's really for your time.
I don't have much of this life, so you don't have to worry.
I don't need to hear about it, right?
Yes, of course.
My sex is, I mean, it's like, I need to fall in love.
And so, until then, I'm not really considering even dating.
Oh, Jesus Christ, give me a break.
You've had one night's dance.
I have, but they're so easy to have
that it's not, like, appealing.
I'd imagine they are in California.
Well, you know, I can go on Grindr and I can go on tonight and find somebody
I would be afraid to go on Grindr and get killed
Yeah, though I did go on plenty of fish and I got me a male
Jigolo for $100. I love that story. I love that story. Tell us story Tracy. This is a Jigolo you got.
Oh, I love plenty of fish because you can pick out the eye color, the hair color, height, everything
So I got me a Greek with black curly hair and green eyes
He showed up about 2.30 in the morning and I give him a hundred bucks and he serviced me and that's when the first time I smoked a blunt, he pulled out a cigar and I was like, I want you to, I want to smoke after you.
He said, no, it's weedled, they call it a blunt.
And then I got up next morning and my roommate was having coffee.
I ordered me a whore and the next night I was 7, 2, 3 in the morning that whore came
back fucking for free that night with an EMP.
I was last time I had sex and I think it was about 15 years ago.
How about what happened like 10 years later?
Oh yeah, he got a hold of me on fucking Facebook.
And he's he's like are you still interested and he was bald and had three kids
And I said fuck you're married
For what I needed you I said out there you some bitch. I said you might you watch standing right there
I kid and you're fucking laughing. You want to talk to me about fucking. I said I bought
Yeah, I love that story. Yeah, I don't mind. I don't mind the
bold
Yeah, I
Can't do ball and I can't do brown. I
So I'm totally out man. I'm bald and brown-eyed. I know and I'm sorry. I married the brown-eyed
man. I only had sex with one brown-eyed man and he was a guinea from an Italy, a Sicilian.
They had beautiful black hair and olive skin and he was brown-eyed. I had to lock him in
I'm the one remember that
Psych said I'm the one that's a Greek. I have the Greek background. Oh, yeah, yeah, of course
I'm gonna have the dark dark hair bald and dark eyes, right? Yeah
I'm Greek man. You're right, right, right. Yeah, my mother's Greek and Irish
Your mother is Greek. Where's she from in Greece? You know? Oh, no
Oh, okay, I see yeah, my grandma green heritage. Okay. Yeah, I don't know where
But he was a blue-eyed and light skin. Oh, yeah
You know, I've been to Greece, right?
I think that is.
I've heard I've been there.
I would love to go to Greece.
I think, yeah, I've heard that you've been there.
Where did you mention though?
I went on a month's trip when I was like 15 years old and we went to, we did Athens and
what I really remember is, well, we did a home state in a place called Oropos, O-R-O-P-O-S,
town really beautiful on the mainland still yeah and uh we also but what I really regret is that
like you know the family like the mother loved me and stuff or the parents loved me I was with
like the brother his name is your ghost or whatever he like was like very much but I was like very
gay you know as I had bleach blonde hair and was really skinny and wearing yeah I could see you being
But I had a chance to go to Santorini, but I was like, I want to stay at the home stay like for an extra week
And then it was like not an it was not very good like the other week
And then I like I heard the Santorini's like yeah, you missed out on going to Santorini. Holy crap when you're that close
I gotta go back. I gotta go back school and school bathrooms. Yeah, I don't see Greek
I don't know if he's Greek and I don't see the image. No, he's he's not
He doesn't school of Athens is not Greek like he doesn't have
Philosophy and yeah, yeah, yeah, he's very
Very well, he's a smart guy and all that's that's the whole school of Athens thing
I would love to be able to read ancient Greek
Well, it's not very different than like the Hebrew alphabet. It's actually very similar to Hebrew
And it's all from Phoenician. Oh, I'll actually modern
Yeah, I didn't mean that he's well read like in like yeah ancient Greek. I just mean he's
Red
Philosophy thing. Yeah, this is what I call it linguistic that I watch on
YouTube
He's a devil, the St. Morse bird ship like that, and he reads ancient Greek.
And not very many people can do it, but I'm on.
Oh my God, this man is to have his mind very, very smart man.
I studied Hebrew because I studied Kabbalah and part of Kabbalah is like scanning the letters and like learning the like you look at the letters.
There's like something on the 72 names of God where there's 72 letters.
to the Greek alphabet. Like, you know, there's a left is like the letter a and
yeah. Alfa is in Greek.
Ignition has a very similar sounding thing. It's like the letter a, right? And so, um,
you can, once you learn, like, one of the languages, you can kind of
Well, you know about the Rosetta stone, right? Yeah
But Greek was the key to deciphering that the Rosetta stone had ancient script
That that no one knew how to read. I can't remember exactly what it was. Someone could
This was the key, and it had Egyptian, I believe too. It had the Egyptian symbols, and it also had Greek, like it had translations of the same language.
Thank you, Greek, yeah.
And it had Greek on it, and because of the Greek, because we knew the Greek, we were able to translate the rest of it on the Rosetta Stone.
So that's how we were able to decipher some of the Egyptian symbols. I'm pretty sure it was the Egyptian symbols.
Ancient Greek head.
the most words to describe things.
It's, it's, it's really.
Now, now it's English.
Now English is the most.
English doesn't have nothing.
We have very few words.
Well, it's a very technical though.
It's very technical where it's like the word,
like it doesn't have very much nuance.
English is pretty lazy.
Yeah, but it can be very,
but you can describe things in a very detailed way.
Already.
I'll tell you what, this guy, I don't go for the devil worship and I go there because
he reads it and he shows it as he's reading it and stuff like that and it's really nice to learn.
Is there any reason or is it like you know actual like Satanism?
No, it's
I don't know, he did some interview with Danny there,
Amand, it'd be worth it because I think he'd get into that.
Just to learn it's what helps and crack the Sumerian. Okay. There we go. I'm sorry
Naya form is a Sumerian where they would they use these clay tablets
It's like the oldest like like language they they have and they they have these like really interesting
They look like a bunch of eyes like letter I like or barbells or something like all different kind of yeah
Yeah, I know that but let me just correct about the thing with the Rosetta stone because exile one just put
put it in. The Greek, the new, the Greek, the new, the hieroglyphics is what helped them crack
the Sumerian language. Yeah, but also the Sumerian language, like Zacharias Titian, like, you know,
basically translated the Sumerian, and it's a very controversial translation of it. But yeah, that's
Are you wearing scrubs?
No, I'm just wearing these pants from T-shirts with those black pants, I'm gonna wash my hands.
I looked like you had scrubs on, I was like, damn.
This is so comfortable, I love scrubs.
Let me see, oh god.
Wash my hands real quick.
Yeah, I mean, I love, um, there's a story, the oldest story of the, the oldest story
of the world is called Inanna's Descent into the Underworld, and it's, uh, it's a, it's
a Sumerian, it's, you know, Sumerian, Inanna was...
The goddess of like heaven basically and then she descends to the underworld to see her sister and every gay in the underworld
She had to take up an article of clothing like her earrings
And she gets totally naked by the end and then she sees her sister Irish keg all
who's the Queen of Hell, a kind of Persephone character.
And the Rishikigal put up on a meat hook,
and it's like, once you come into the underworld,
you can't leave.
And then so Anki, who is the God,
a Sumerian God of the sweet waters
and creativity and magic.
I've heard of that one.
Runners fingernails created these transgender beings
that went down and they charmed Rishikigal,
who thought them very charming.
And they, she said, I'll give you anything you want.
And then they said, they wanted to do Nanna's body.
and then she realized she'd been tricked and so she cursed them to you know so that's like kind of
goes into the you know maybe like transgenders maybe have kind of a maybe maybe carry that
a little bit of a curse energy from from that irish kigal and stuff like that um but um it's
like she was allowed to leave the underworld,
but then there was a condition she had to be replaced.
She had to bring somebody to her replacement.
And so first they went to her like manicurist
or her personal assistant basically.
And she's like, oh, the personal assistant
was crying over her.
So she's like, she can stay alive.
And then they went to her manicurist
and the manicurist was crying.
And then she went to her husband
and her husband was like just partying
with like all these conky bars.
And she's like, okay, she sent him down there.
His name was Debussy.
So, he got sent down to the underwear.
What was he supposed to be doing if not partying with his concubines?
Like, that's why you have concubines.
He doesn't be mourning his dead wife after three days of her being gone, but...
Yeah, he didn't mourn long enough.
Concubines need maintenance.
Is anyone thinking about that?
Eh?
No, you're more worried about the one that's been longer here.
Yeah, well, but she but she was because she was resurrected and she caught him
So it was supposed to have it wrapped in black and morning
It's funny because yeah
her manicurist was like pretty much presented as like a gay guy, right and then her and then her personal assistant was like
Kind of like a maybe like a lesbian or something like that
There's a lot of like sexuality stuff involved in a lot of this stuff, especially in the Greek too
Oh, I love it is one with is an island
off of Greece, and it's a country or something,
and it was run by women on horseback.
Lesbos, yeah, Lesbos.
Oh, Amazon or Lesbos, yeah.
You're thinking of the Amazons?
Yeah, but.
Yeah, but I don't think they're the same story, but there's some
Together catch sailors and yeah, those are the sirens. That was how they'd father
More children and then they would torture and kill him. Yeah, because he wasn't good for nothing
No more they done used his becarisms
Yeah, you know they passed him around like breeding stock and they kill him. Yeah
Yeah, that's the Amazon's but there is this island called Lesbos where the word
Yeah, it was off of Greece
Yeah, my grandfather was born there. It wasn't called Lesbos at the time
But he was born there on that island on that island. Yeah
It's a wonder he survived
There's actually a poet, a poetess named Sappho, S-A-P-P-H-O, and there's like some surviving poetry that she wrote, and she was, you know, it's kind of like, there was some lesbian poetry in there, right, and yeah, so they did get that, the word lesbian does come from the island of Lesbos, and, uh, or Lebo, or something like that, right, I don't know how to pronounce it necessarily, but, um, in Greek it's lesbos, it's lesbos.
Yeah, yeah, there's no B. There's a B sound. Yeah, that guy almond is the one that's the kind of stories he tells and it's written in ancient Greek so he greeds you, you know, I read it, I read it, I read something called the orphic hymns like or, um, they're, they're orph, um, orpheus.
That's a great story. She'll tell the story of Orpheus and Eurydice. He's sometime or Eurydice or Eurydice, Eurydice and she got bitten by like a snake and went to the underworld and he made a deal that he, if he could go get her, but he cannot look back to make sure that she was behind him until he was all the way out of the underworld.
But the last second he turned around and she was still there. But then she got sent back to the underworld and then he like.
you eventually got torn apart by the um who are they called the kind of like the
there are these women kind of wild women came and tore them to pieces and stuff like that
yeah well they used to use what was this snake venom and shit like that to make purple mused
Okay, so you're talking about definitions. They would find these sea snails, right?
And they so it was only used for royalty. It was the most expensive dye
they think because they were the sea people right so they would be able to
Find these snails that had this purple dye. It was the most expensive dye. I'll drop the link for you. I'm sorry
I was and and that's why only royalty could afford it basically
It came from the snail it came from at the sea snail like a like an underwater sea
And that's where that purple came from.
That's a beautiful color.
Mm-hmm.
That's why it's purples associated with royalty.
Yeah.
Because it was expensive.
And only royalty was actually allowed to wear it.
And that's kind of it.
I knew there was a story behind the purple.
That's why the preachers wear that purple, the sash that goes over them.
This little sash is a color.
There was some kind of story because I'm a white Anglo-Saxon Protestant
I can remember going to church and talking about the color purple and the robes on the preachers
I think that the story of arachnay as well and arachnay is where the name the word for spider comes from arachnay was
the daughter of a
I guess one of the the the dire of fabrics like, you know, I think he was a Phoenician and he would like find that
But uh, she was this wonderful weaver very talented and she was like, oh, I'm a better weaver than
You know, Athena, who is the goddess of weaving, right?
No, the thing was she was actually a better weaver than she had a contest and
um, she did
What's up?
Would she bragged about it though bragged about it. Okay, so she was bragging about it
So Athena came disguised as this old beggar woman's like, you know what you should not be bragging about and saying you're better than the gods
It's called hubris having pride that you're better than the gods
She's like so she's like you just better like, you know, thank Athena for the gift
And you know
And she's like, you know, I she's like, oh Athena wants to you know, talk to me
She can come to herself and then since she reveals herself as Athena at the contest and then Iraq the
um sows together these pictures of like Zeus you know turning into a swan and
raping Lita and you know all these like insulting things about the god and all the god's foibles
and then Athena did all these wonderful the glorified things but everyone judged that
arachnids was better but Athena has the ultimate power she hit her with the with their like
with their what's it called a shuffle and then uh she hung herself
And then she was hanging herself and she's like, okay, well, I'm not gonna let you hang yourself
I mean I'm less than the curse you become a spider as you came from the thread
I made her into a spider. Yeah. Oh my god. Oh, here's Alex McQueen. What is what are we looking at here?
Look at this. We're doing some IRL
I do love the love I love
greatness. That's why my psyche
awakens is based on the cupid
and psyche. They had a bunch
of people that men, the boys
and they cut their nuts off
to call them nymphs or
Oh, Unix, Unix.
Unix, there you go.
Yeah, yeah, you next and that was like even like Jezebel was a Phoenician princess, you know
Jezebel in the Bible
That's what they used in the the fucking you know the castles were the were those because they are safe
They wouldn't wear their women cuz they have no more nuts
But then Jezebel's Unix threw out of a window. That was like they betrayed her
She was always fighting with this guy, Elijah, but then she looked at the window and she
saw this other guy coming to take over whatever and the Unix threw out the window.
She was trampling my horses, eating my dogs, all that was left was a skull and crossbones.
Oh my, I wonder if that's where it come from, the skull and crossbones came from.
So, if you look at, there's two femurs and the skull.
was the pirate's flag.
Yeah.
It's very interesting name for that. I love jolly roger jolly roger. I love uh, but I love mythology
That's you know, I was here even before high school
I was just like I have I would just on my own by the books of myths and
For years and years and it's like and as you go grow older you appreciate more of appreciate for the symbolism in the real meaning
I was the same thing when I was a kid every place we moved when we moved out on the dirt road
and I found a book and it was all about that dirt road and the houses and there
was a devil's thing out back of our house was a spring that's where I saw
Bigfoot oh my god that place was so haunted those woods are you saw Bigfoot
Was it at night? No, it was during the day. Me and my brother, we were out, we were walking to what I had read in the book. It was on the dirt road. It was on a cart road. It, it dead end.
Nice, like, yeah, the library for like a few dollars, but I like, I opened it and it has this yellow feather, like an actual real feather in there.
Um, it's got the like the labyrinth. This is like the labyrinth. Yeah
That was too white for us. Yeah, I've been there right so it said no sauce. Mm-hmm
There's all this there's all these I've never even opened it. There's there's knowledge cards in here and stuff
It has the God pan and it was like this island. I got this at the library for like just a few bucks
And it came with everything in it. Yeah, it's not even open like some of this stuff
It's like a little little copy of the Odyssey right there. That's pretty cool
I think it was maybe five dollars, I mean it was like and then it says
Yeah, because it was originally
$20, but I don't know when this is published, but it says,
oh, Muses, who sing of the world long gone
of mighty heroes, Olympian gods of terrible monsters
and fabulous beasts.
Help me to tell of those wonderful things
for I have come to the land of Greece
to speak of her miss and her mystery.
That's Lady Ahestia Evans in Athens, 1825.
Wow.
And it says, oh, it says, somebody wrote on it.
It says, this book is the property of John Oro.
I have come to Greece too to find out
if any of the power of the God's remains.
I don't know if that was, if you wrote that on,
but it was out of-
You need to write something.
He's dark somewhere, man.
I'm kidding.
But in the cover of it, it has like, you know,
it's pretty cool.
It's like, it's like-
Oh, let's look at that.
That's beautiful.
Yeah, man.
That's an interesting-
coffee book table. That would certainly get my attention. We also have like, my dad would have
Bullfinches mythology, which is like a huge, like a big, like they had all the detail, like very
detailed. And so I, since I was a kid, I would read these and now they have great retellings of
all these on and discussions of it. I love the story of Dionysus too. And like, there's something
Yeah, have you heard of the Bakke?
It's the Bakkenal.
Yeah.
And basically Dionysus would come in, he came into the city and all the women started going
into the mountains and raving in the mountains and dancing and having these secret ceremonies.
And so the king was like, oh, get rid of this Dionysus, but he couldn't keep him locked up
or anything. He kept trying to imprison him and he would just shake the prison down.
Eventually Dionysus talked this king into going into drag so he could take him into the Bacchanal
and he hasn't climbed the tree to spy on him and drag.
And then he's like, hey, look, look at him.
They're up in the tree.
Although we're going to tear him down
and then he'll need his mother and his sisters
tear off his head.
They think it's a lion and stuff.
And then wake up the next day and she's like, yeah.
It's a great story.
The bouquet, I think.
I noticed there's something that goes on.
They all turn queer and they all get ripped to shreds.
What happened to Orpheus? Orpheus, the same thing happened.
I was thinking, I didn't know that particular story. I was thinking there's a festival,
there was an ancient festival, the Buccaneuil. That's what I was thinking of, right, where Dionysus is the god that's...
That's right.
But the book is considered like an ancient Greek tragedy, and it's a story of when Dionysus
actually came and would drive everyone into this madness, because he's the god of drunkenness
and divine revelry, right?
And he's also...
Almost on the transgender side or at least very queer kind of kind of God, right?
And you know, pan too is pretty bisexual
Isn't that the guy with the flu, pangir?
Yeah, yeah
Yeah, he was certainly he was certainly gained the cartoon man, whatever
Whatever that was man. That was gay as fuck like he was a cartoon with pan in it
Yeah
What's that so I can pay for that you an advantage I think they have an advantage and well
You know actually he wouldn't actually chase the women around the nymphs around and they would just run run away
So there's a nymph named syrinx and she changed into like these reeds
And so the syrinx pipes the pan pipes he like they were they were cut down and that that was like her cry
They were turning to Aguapolo, which is somebody
and turning to a tree and stuff like that.
And just to that's a big thing.
You're pretty damn smart, aren't you, Sike?
Well, that's not a big difference.
You have a wide range.
Your parents raised you right by letting you have all this info.
You suck it all up as a kid.
I did, because I didn't really play with toys.
I would always want to get them.
That's what I never got to kids.
I mean, toys, they was always books,
like the books you just showed me where they pull out
and alphabets and stuff like that was a puzzle.
And it went right down the hallway of the trailer.
And that's how they learned the alphabet and was a train.
Just different stuff like that. I spent hundreds of dollars on those books, man
with all the beautiful colors of the fish and shit. They learned more often the
colors, you know, because it made it interesting. They wanted to know what the
book was about.
Yeah
My dad used to like actually draw me up with the library at a library at the street a really nice library
Oh, yeah, yeah, the librarian actually call him and says stop living your kid here. We're not babysitters
Yeah, I like to read every book
I love the library, yeah
Is that Alex in the
Bottom up with the neck just okay. How's that you say something?
It's me
I'm walking in a dark. I'm going to get cold right now for my joke deals house. He lives like 20 blocks away
So I don't want to drive drunk. So I walk no I care about humanity
Yeah, I'm going to my co-go to my boy's house he lives about 20 blocks away from me, but I'm drunk
So I'm drinking drive. I care about the law. So I'm taking a nice stroll through my fucking hood to his house
I it's good exercise. Anyway, it's good exercise, baby
You know I'm saying I want to pick up the pool right now, and I obey the law bro
You know getting my BMW and drive 20 blocks and maybe get pulled over hurts him
I know I'll take a nice brisk walk to get my cocaine. I will get my cocaine
Nice and safe. You understand. I care about humans
I'll be back home in no time with Michael Cain and everything's good
And I'm working on my abs at the same time working my my abs and my ass
It's a two mile walk. So it's two miles there two miles back. So it's a four mile walk
Right. I win
So my abs my ass are getting toned and I'm gonna get freaky
Okay, and I will not get arrested because I obey the law
So my BMW tomorrow when I wake up in the morning or hung over my BMW will be there to take me to get big
And I can cheese or whatever I gotta do. Okay. Is that a statue or I mean a shadow or?
What is that? Why was that shadow so small Alex?
Remember I said I had peacocks in my city. We also you know my see I grew up in the city of Palisbury
It was a state that was like incorporated like the 30s or whatever, but from Italy we received
Thing that is is bored 58 lives with his mom imagine that
He failed that life
I'm looking at Bronzeberg's comment for the other chat. I said Alex. He wants me to take up his occupation. I'm not interested. I have my own
Alex would you ever have sex with me if I wore if I wore that blonde wig would you consider that?
You pull me over. I don't think it would take that blonde wig
When you take the wig Alex, he just needs to turn me around
You can't even leave your room thing that is with a mommy's permission you can't take a poor my walk
You need mommy's permission mommy. Can I go get cocaine? No, you cannot think that is
You're gonna make me mad.
Well, I don't want it. I
Think it's admirable in Asian culture. Come on. I'm gonna take you with me. I'm gonna take you with me. Come on
Come with me my man
Going to the coke dealers house
We're taking a walk because our exercise is good
I'm going to the coke dealers house right now walking because I care about laws
I can get in my BMW or my Denali and drive there, but why would I do that? Why would I risk going to jail?
Fuckin loser. Yo, you see Alexander mayors told you to shave your head and you listen. Do you like I'm gonna shave?
He told you to shave your head
He told you to shave your head and you did it you listen to your mayors, bro
Think that is that's how much of a loser you are you live with mommy and you listen to action your mayors
What to do with your hair?
she told you to shave your head and you did it she told you to shave your head
and you did it motherfucker what are you talking about
when when she made that video of you laughing
she made a video yes oh my god and i'm supposed to know
you live with your mommy i supposed to know about it
she told you in that video she said yo you have no hair left i would shave it if i were you
I know, because Alex is going to get psyched and there's so much trouble with other strangers.
You listen to Alex Angel, you're going to get him.
Not why he's talking about Alex Angel.
You love your mom and your story, Dick.
There's nothing you can say when that is.
You've lived that life, Esso.
You're 15 years old.
You know what he's gonna get you fucking trouble right pissing everybody off
You know, that's why he's talking up to Alexander right, you know, he's gonna turn on you too like he's done how many times now
Yeah
coffee cop fuck up you both faggot oh by the way you don't take your mom
Okay, that's enough Alex.
Oh, but you put the wig on for him!
I did, but now he's ruined the moment.
We know money he's already turned on Psych a few times and Psych keeps letting him back, like as if Alex is going to change.
Like he's not going to be a fucking backstab and prick every fucking time.
Well, Alex just plays his character.
He's drunk. I think he's very drunk.
Who cares he's drunk? That's not a fucking excuse.
Like um people like I think he's happy. He's going to get an eight-ball cock
He's a great baby. He's a good Alex. You better calm down. Okay?
Calm down stop screaming. I turned down your mic 75% and you're so loud, okay?
I'm gonna give you one more chance
You're on thin ice, okay, I can't oh he chose to mute himself. Okay. He muted himself
Reality Nancy agrees with thing that is I was the reason I get straight. I don't know. I don't I don't think I'll get strike
He is doing shit on other channels and everybody knows that psych is his home
So when they get off they get pissed off at psych and don't be
Your channel psych
Alex is going to get you taken down and he's gonna go running to Alexander and say what a fucking loser psych is
No, he's not anyway. Mark my words.
Don't say that because I don't like and negative prophecies said about me. It's like bad bad juju.
So don't even say something negative like that. Let's just say I'll be okay.
Okay, that's what I'm gonna think. I think I'm I'm really fine.
I've had I've had Alice around since the beginning.
He and it's been smooth, right?
Well, I find him and then he pays up.
And so I'm playing.
He's okay.
When I'm always willing to I was always willing to cut the guy slack and just you know fucking laugh at his shit
But he's really being a fucking prick right now
Yeah, he's good at it though
I mean goes to is anything though. He just says the same shit over and over and over again. That's not being good at something
He's just loud
He has no intelligence, you can tell by the way he talks, he's a fucking moron, it's obvious.
And that's why he has to turn the mic up so loud, because he has to over talk everybody
else, otherwise he gets totally crushed, because he's an idiot.
Everybody knows this, everybody, I'm not saying anything surprising here.
Alex, I think you're uh
Actually, you know, I do like Alton. I use this music like for you know for hours reading the Bible and stuff like that
Yeah
You don't think that is you're not gonna recover from this you understand you are now my mortal enemy. Yeah, so you understand shit
Hold on, I'm getting run over right now. I was got run over by this stupid asshole right here, but you think that is
You're not my mortal enemy you bold loser that lives with his mom
Hey Alex, I told you to stop. Okay. Can you just like stop thinking on this?
I don't give a fuck about you dick. You're a loser. You're 60. You live with your mommy
Don't fuck off
Okay, I'm gonna mute you
He's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted, he's muted
You know he puts it couldn't shut up. Oh my god
Yes, I mean he's like
Already had the coke. I mean it's like no he hasn't gotten it yet
I even got the coke man. You might have to really get some coke what he's gonna act like. Oh, I know
He apologized he apologized to me for
For a ragging on me for this for my living conditions and all that shit, right?
And I'm like, okay fine and look he's right back at it again the next day
This is how he is psych. He's there. We have to learn this shit. His apologies mean absolutely
Nothing. He is a fucking rat a dumb rat a dumb loud rat
I don't know. I don't know.
Alexander almost got over by
a skateboard time says. Yeah,
you're almost. He got that was
close. He was crossing over.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I
So if it applies to him, too, if he can't control himself, you know, get on the internet
That's what that's what I mean drama. That's where everybody wants it
I mean if you wanted somebody that was under control then you go to a preacher's fucking
It's a little chaotic here, but I mean that it kind of is like I'm predictable which makes it fun
But you never know. Yes. Yes. I'm predictable
You don't know what else you're gonna get sometimes that when he gets into this date where you just will skim the f-a-g-g
We still love him. No, cuz he's that he's crazy
Don't bring him back, but you can't but he's in an unmute and then he's gonna unmute himself
Yeah, he doesn't like it.
He doesn't like me to control his mic.
And that's why I've gotten in trouble.
Because I've been like, Alex, it's my show.
I get to control the mics on my show.
And he's like, no, you don't.
Take you.
And I'm like, oh, my god, it's my show.
I'll kick him off.
And then he'll call us.
And then he'll send me like $20.
And I'll say, OK.
He makes up for it. I mean, I think I actually if I he actually does he does love you
About you several times. He sent me on Alexander's coke dealers on the line. Here we go
Come on, we don't have all day
What are you gonna give you?
Hey Nick
You want to see the cobra his his pictures he doesn't have his scenery on he just has his picture up
So as soon as he takes the picture down, I might you just make all the way
Don't pick on things
Panels for you. Yes. Yes. I'd fuck me
What it is that really good at close-up
I'm five blocks away. I'm five blocks away from
Said the best what you're sitting there with nothing me
No sounds in the lamp
I fuck me who is that though, but for a little bit
Little dog the little shit you dog. Is it a dog?
Yeah, I think it's a white dog, isn't it?
No, no, this one.
Oh, you got, uh, Bernino Joint, or St....
Bernino Joint.
Bernino Joint USA.
I like it. I like your new name, Nick.
Um, and then we got Joint...
Oh, I care about the law.
I don't drink and drive, man.
I care about the law.
Wait, wait, wait
Horizontal one right there that that that downtown did you draw that I told you don't play with Queen
But no you want to play with McQueen see now this 13-inch Cox popping up everywhere
We got
Nick that that wide one there that that downtown escape you draw that too
Okay
I don't know. I don't know.
Hey, Mason, the drummer's here.
Come on, come on, Mason.
I need to give you some more.
Mason says, yeah, I can understand you on that thing that is.
As long as he's not bringing up my shirt, I'm okay with that.
He will amazing if you see you care about people. I gotta get to cocaine. They care. You're okay. Oh
Oh, yeah, I found this shit on the curb the other day. I was skateboarding to the lady. I had that as a kid. Yeah
Play with the weeder bone
Oh, my god, my god, my god, my
I thought we made more frisbees though
They think I can look here. There's cops look at cops
Protecting me while I go get the cocaine
What a good
really like that one right there Nick that is freaking awesome I kind of wish
you drew that one so that I could look at more of your your art like that would
be like this was mine like that yeah this was off the curb total Wow that's
I don't know what we've come up with this in the real world.
Yeah, I can smell the coke from here. I can almost smell the coke.
I fucking, this is my favorite. I can almost smell it already.
It's legal to sleep starting a rumble.
Anybody got some weed they can send me? I'd love it.
I've got black weed.
You can send me too.
I'm smoking ashes.
Every day
One time I saw Benny Blanco smoked something off camera, and then he started coming back talking like a New York gangster
And he said
35% of everything flower 35% off
So usually it's like a $50 minimum though. No new offers available. They deliver. They deliver. Yeah
Two you're three out it's 15 after one in the morning here
The ring right now, I think they close probably early, but I need to borrow if I can
Wrangle up. I'm going to eat okay. Yeah, so what are you talking about one in the morning?
I'm trying to get some, I'm trying to get some weed.
I got all the weed in the world. Thank God, bro.
I already got that COVID safe. That's number one.
That's the first thing you gotta cover in the morning you wake up you go get the pound of weed then you go on with your day, man
Oh my god, I'm a block away from the cocaine. I'm a block away from
You don't have to get in your car and
Gotta be responsible like
Exactly be responsible. There you go
It's not worth it bro a ten minute, you know five minute job, I don't want to walk five minutes might get you put in central
Is it worth it working on your body to and you're working
it's a win-win
you're working in a bunch of fields
your ass is getting nice and tight
your abs, your lungs are breathing
you're taking a full mile walk
you're sniffing cocaine, like life is good
oh my god, I'd love to
you don't want to get in your dumb car and get pulled over
because that'll happen, that's when it happens
you pull out
and then it's a wrap
next thing you know you're in jail
and you have to pay all that money to get out
And you don't get to coke!
Alice, didn't you get to go to prison for ten years over cocaine?
No.
No, you didn't?
Okay, that was a lie.
No, exactly
Why go to prison for one day if you're gonna want it, okay?
I'm a mentor. I'm a mentor. I've been there for ten years
You don't want to do even a weekend in there. Trust me
You need coke and it's like in a five mile radius. Just walk take an uber a bus
Don't get in your car drunk, bro
Not worth it.
Not very expensive too.
You know, you want to fuck a hooker.
But don't jump in your car drunk to go fuck the hooker.
You know?
You'll shit a hooker.
The bitch will be there, the bitch will be there.
Everyone will be there, bro.
The cocaine will be there.
There's no rush.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I think it's time for a song guys. Are we ready for another song? Let me see it. I'll play a song.
Which song are you playing? If you live for this mom, listen, if I'm 60 and I live for my mom,
I'm going to think of this like, fuck, I can't believe it came back to me. Like,
karma fucked me up because I was making fun of things that is. But I don't think I will be
I haven't seen my mom anywhere since I was 10. So how would I be nice to know that I'm
60.
You understand?
That's crazy to me, bro.
Living with mommy at 60.
It should be a guy like you should be a grandpa.
You should be a man handling business.
Don't you don't.
Man, come on, man.
This giving you an upset stomach.
I'm four houses away from the coattailer and I'm going to have to meet up because I'm getting my coke.
I'm going to get my pure off the brick.
It's off the brick, bro. No cut at all.
Straight off the brick. Yeah, you think I play around next you think I want fucking shit
That's cut up. No, no
Yeah, it comes from Columbia, did you smash it with a hammer put it in a bag straight
New York is one of the best places to get this shit, too
Not a lot he does
No wonder everybody played this game over that
Oh
Okay, I'll play the ghost song because it goes when you got I haven't got a ghost buddy. It's brand new here we go
You're flacky.
That's how you know the haunts a lot
Lights flicker chats in the right and somewhere goes about to die
He rose a lot like thunder on caffeine
Drop a stack of jokes keeping the scene clean
The crowd starts how the trolls start crying
Ghosts just grin
When the sky lost, it's you
They can't see the light
He threw in my storm
But I remember, I was reborn
May I have permission to crash out?
Psyche is proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud
It's still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way, still out of the way
The dream dumb dumb to the ones who doubt
baby, baby, baby, baby, baby,
Get the fuck off the block get off the block
Look at that I feel like Nick Johnson. I'm dumpster diving
hell yeah
Like a dick. Step you into the club
with open arms
With arms wide open
I just found out my life has changed with arms wide open
Let's smoke another one.
My ass was open.
Creed, that's Creed.
Oh, whoa.
Sorry, sorry.
Sorry, go too far.
I try to be like Simon.
He always says, like, whoa.
Whoa, he'll go, whoa.
Whoa, whoa.
Hey, oh.
Oh my god, look.
I found Seiki.
Whoa, what am I? Let me see. What is it? And he'll say what is that?
To me
Cuz I say man, there's no we see change
Oh, there's crystal Marie. Oh my god, I found fucking true soon. Oh my god, it's it's buried the turtle
It's Michael Blackson. Oh my god. Oh my god. There's me
Who the hell is that? Oh, there's Mason the drummer and there's a Arthur and there's
That's untrackable this untrackable untrackable. Yeah, there is untrackable. Oh
Who's that one?
Oh, who's that one that's a cue that's cute. Hey there go 300 glow. Oh my god, this is Justin Timberlake
Oh my god. That was a ghost. That's oh that looked like oh mate
The other one before
Johnson
May I have
She's like that Tracy that was good, huh?
Thank you come back. I'm here. Yeah, that is I like that song
Thank you so much. The fan was the only thing keeping me in this
Yeah, let's keep it. What do you do? Are you in the dumpster dick? What are you doing?
Find some souvenirs
Oh, well just one more thing the dust now you're at the I thought you're the copiers house already
What do you think I'm fine like a kite asshole, that's right he's moving we're sorry old Austin still live
I already got the coke I really took bumps and man that shit is pure as fuck
Yeah, that's it. It's good. It's so good that I'm spelling it all over the floor and I don't even care
Four is inside
$100 I put a fucking half of it on my hand half of it fell off, but it's so good bro. Whatever got in
Now I'm walking back home, like a nice, like a nice, you know, human that cares about society, bro.
You know what I'm saying? New York is amazing. You can do whatever you want here.
You can go get coke at two in the morning. Just do it the right way.
Don't get in a car drunk and kill people. Walk to your drug dealers' house.
Do what smoke we don't want. Do what I want. Just do it the right way.
you understand you can do it everyone here just as long as you don't hurt anybody exactly
they don't give a fuck what you do here as long as you don't hurt anybody
I'm
Honestly, it's that way here. They don't give a fuck what you do here. No, they don't bug. They don't bust your balls at all
No, just do your shit right man. Do whatever you gotta do and do it, right?
I mean if cops fold over and I'm searching I'd be dead, but they're not gonna do that, you know
Because why would they search me just remain walking?
Just a man walking home, pal.
No, that's right.
You couldn't just get a second shift.
So what if my pocket is full of coke?
You don't know, man.
That's just, man.
I don't care.
My bike comes underneath that.
Damn, that shit was good, fuck.
Oh, how many he is.
Yeah.
I'm telling you, bro.
I think so watch you all they really care about us. Just don't get caught doing it like drinking and driving or
Doing drugs and just do it right man
Oh shit, I read on the beach pizza
Come on Nick get over here
Look at this I'm walking home like a dick look at this
Welcome back
They have sidewalks here, which I like to use I like the sidewalks
Time
You're gonna get you man
One way or another I will get you I don't have any
We're gonna get you get you get you get you get you want
What's up
Yeah, or not the pretenders, right? Oh my god
Try to smash on
One way or another I'm gonna get you get you get you get you get you want me. Thank you. Thank you
Which what song am I funny New York is if I
Want it look I'm under a bridge. It's like I couldn't
Scooters around check this out. Look at this. Look at this
Il s'en se chroudre !
See, so if I wanted to right now, and it's my fat ass didn't want to
Do some school that
All over New York City, right?
I gotta take my credit card and I just swipe it on the scooter and I can drive it to my house and then
Oh, yeah, just leave it there. I don't pick it up tomorrow. Isn't that crazy, bro? I know I love those things
Fuck that. I'm not gonna take $3,000 to walk five blocks. Nah, what if I wanted to walk good?
Alright, look at this. The option is there.
Look at this dumb shit.
That's how awesome New York is, bro. They make it as convenient as they can for you.
They just like he's laying around like yo bro you got the loot you don't got to walk home
Let's do a friendly raid is there's a man in hurricane
She only has six like let's go over there and
Right his channel friendly, okay? I'm gonna put you're in the street
Over here it is kind of random because I've never been to a stream. I don't think he's a he's a friend of mine and
A friend of his is a friend of our okay, whatever
I'll be back probably like 1130, but I'll be in this chapter. I'm gonna go to
Something that is a fun thing that is
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
Why I've been preferred a simp for Ruby space sec. I don't know who that is, but
Hurricane power
Well, it's his birthday
Yeah
Hell I'm
I've been married 28 years
So is the ending stream or is he just going over to the other stream
Maybe we'll hang out here and we're backstage now. Oh
Are we know you still live? I still have the
We all share your coke that's what I wanted backstage right now and get naked. Yes or no
You know I'm still trying to find his damn channel
That's okay. I mean
I thought he was gonna like
Where's that spoon a little bit pal, but I don't blame you took a waka moly side over mine, but you don't know before me so
That wasn't the real you the Alex
It wasn't one
That wasn't the real you on there fucking video
You know the
You're right it wasn't
Wow, that's what everybody's saying
You're making me feel like Mason now
No, I was just heard when Wacomoli came up and I was like get right here to psych and you were like no
They Wacomoli help you like taking her side, and I was like
And she donated 20 bucks that day I mean it's like
I love you
And she was always like point point the camera down at your cock when you're fuck going around the lake
I
Was like damn that was hot
You know why bro, you know why I don't like you know why I like her and I don't
But she seems like a nice girl to me. She's the best. What come on?
Do you like Alex though you suspect everybody at least right? No, bro
Because she was a cheerleader
When people were doxing people and coming to people's houses. She was there like yeah, get him, you know
That's the reason I have this thing towards her, but I was like 30 years ago and whatever
Oh, it was a long time ago long time ago. Yeah
So we were friends. We were real good friends me walk and then you know, I got betrayed by her
but I got betrayed by her and her team that were friends before I met her
So right I can't be upset with the girl for being friends with her team
I mean relationship politics like groups, you know
It's like I get upset of people for flipping on me
For other people, but I'm like wait a minute. They know these people like two years before I even knew them
So why am I getting upset like they have their own relationship?
I just spent like a certain type of loyalty or something once I like what cool like whatever
It's hard to find loyalty on YouTube
I don't know what to do.
What like is it an issue there that where they would stay there for like two weeks?
They would be rotting or or would they pick up next day or something?
Oh, yeah happens everywhere, I guess so yeah in New York City
Bro
Yeah, you can walk right next to them. They don't move nothing. They're just like, what nigga?
That's right. They got added to a new
I just want to read that pigeons. I don't know why the fuck was that about or whatever
It's like
That the other half of show on Animaniacs. It was like
They were up there talking and it was a little cartoon. It was funny
That's what I bought. I bought that on the past many a time. I've never seen three that
Mean something that bird ship forever out. Where's that?
Guess if you really think if you really think about it. Yeah, I mean three pigeons
Dying at the same time like
Yeah, right. It's kind of odd right one. Maybe two. Wow, but three like something's up
Just me I think you've stumbled on to something Alex
Whatever they're breathing. We're breathing it in too. Well, at least you have the skills to crack it. So
We it's in good hands, right?
Yeah, much money in your cast they paint
All right, so there's so look at this. There's a bike path. It's colored in green. I don't know if you can see it
Yeah, well Jesus bike
Yeah, then see the green
Mm-hmm. The green, right? Okay. So New York has so much money. They repainted the green.
I've been watching these assholes paint a bike path with green paint, like trucks, like piles of green paint.
And by the way, it doesn't really need it. Like, the green paint is fine. I don't know why even they're repainting it.
But this tape and there's trucks and there's just piles of green paint. I'm like, what the fuck?
For a week, I've been watching these asses paint around the whole like three miles stretch around the park the green
You know much money
It's like a 20-man team
like 10 trucks
The paint is industrial paint. It's like a Benjamin Moore. It's like some
Yeah, they use it you're fucking
I
Must be like a hundred grand just to pay some dumb bike path. That doesn't even need it
Yo, go feed some people
But that's what I'm saying, that's how crazy New York is in money like everyone's like
Budget shut the fuck up. These people fucking paying bike pass when they want
Don't listen to you
That's it. You owe me nuts this whole week. I'm like, what the fuck am I watching? They have flaggers
You know when they have the people just standing there with the stop sign
That is like slow. They're paying that guy $30 an hour just to sit there
Well, so muscle pain so a green bike path. That's already green
Actually went further and I'm like inspecting and I'm like why are they painting it like there's nothing wrong with the past
Like it's green baby. It's not green enough
Exactly. That's great. It's not green enough. Yes. You get it. You get it, bro. And that's fowl. That's fowl, bro. That's fucked up.
That's shitting green enough in basic things. Go repaint that shit.
Like the wassar. The Bronx needs like food and water. Like fuck that. That's shitting green enough.
Like, we got a back path in the wild and angry enough, like, sorry, the Bronx is dying, like, fuck the Bronx, go repaint the back path and fucking live a time, man.
Make a back path like this, all right?
That's a people, you're so repainted, back path, right, pal? Fuck the Bronx and the night show.
The rich people with your e-bikes, these are greener paths.
That is crazy!
thank god someone gets it bro Alex have you been Alex have you been to the
the New York tourist sites like where someone from out of the city would visit
yes I lived here my whole life bro I've been okay but everything in York everything
okay so it's one of those things where you do actually visit your own
You're on sites, right because some people live close to a site
It's not a site to me. It's just like
People like travel here with time square, you know, but when you live your whole life, it's just like Times Square the shithole
I
Do understand Alex what you're saying. Yeah, I just
Yeah
Right people that seem to have a towel though life is not
For Toronto, it's the CN Tower right everyone knows it's the landmark thing for Toronto is the CN Tower, right? I've only been there once
You know and that was because I had a I had a relative from out of town visiting and that was the only reason I've been up it
So it's not a thing New York is more compact
Yeah, like you you you have a lot more landmarks than
In one place, yeah, I see what you're saying like I only said that once because it's
You're gonna see the Empire State Building like a lot. Yeah, it's just part of life
But you've been up it or I don't know you can be a go up the Empire State Building. I don't know
I used to work for a construction company when I was really young and I helped howl like the first and second floor
The empire state building is one of the richest buildings in the world
And by the way the elevator you get in it. There's no ceiling thing that is
Oh, yeah, no ceiling you can see through the ceiling and that shit flies up to the hundredth floor in like two seconds
And you're just looking up. It's so cool. That sounds cool. Yeah. Yeah, it's really cool. Nice
It's like around I think people are looking for the link
One in the lane and two in the state
Just blame it on site. If somebody's
I can't do coke without alcohol. That's one thing. You'll never you can't
You need like alcohol or beer or shot something. So now I got the coke now. I gotta go to a beer store
Once again, I'm not gonna drive
So now I gotta walk to the beer store.
What if you have to pick up a lady at the night?
What do you do?
You ride a bike.
Walk to the stupid beer store.
You don't have to walk away.
Look at this something.
Bro, this is how crazy New York is.
Look, there's a sprinkler.
What are you doing? What's up, New York?
I'm watering the green grass.
It's watering grass.
Yeah, like tell-off.
I'm swimming in my fish tank.
It's watering grass.
This is how much money there's here.
There's just machines that pop up during the night and water grass.
And then you hear
It's not like you can transport the water easily from New York
Doesn't fuck around it's like a whole different world. They don't go fuck water now look at this dick. Look how many sprinklers
Show the sprinkler. Show them sprinkler.
People get jumping.
I'm getting wet right now. I just got sprayed in the ass
Is that what you're saying you're getting wet because you were sprayed in the ass is your little
Your little pussy getting a little
Excited Alex
Alex's ass got sprayed. So he got all wet
It's a whole life man, it's a whole life. That's right. You're being responsible
Oh, you have to be you have to I don't know
Don't do it or be responsible
to not get behind the wheel of a car drunk, especially here, especially here, maybe in Kentucky or Louisiana, you might want to pull that bullshit.
That's the worst thing you do in New England, you're a car drunker.
Hey, hey, that shit here.
What do you do?
Mason, time is a big broker, okay? Most of the time you get...
I would have sold you top car and drive by me. They didn't even look at me if I was driving or drunk.
It's a different story.
No, that's not new bono
You know how funny New York is they rerouted all the buses
They're so dumb that they actually put signs on the bus stops like the bus will not stop here anymore. Look at this
Let's stop here and we'll not stop here anymore
they care enough to tell you you're fucked
like listen Louza, you wanna get to work?
you better move to the next bus stop
because there's a Chinese stop in here
do you get it?
at least they care to tell you though
uh
at least they care
not yet Adam
like we're all in the bus and stopping here
there's only one thing
that's a lot of money to have the signs to tell people
take the buses and stopping here like printout another 10,000 signs
for two million to let the losers know that the bus is stopping there
that's a lot of money
hey i take the bus single running a city dot side can you imagine
I don't know. I'll be. I'll be
If you were in like a high
position in the management of
the city and your office. Oh my
god. I gotta go upstairs.
Take care.
Don't you dare leave me up here
I was thinking big choice.
Look, there's a dispensary.
There's a dispensary, but it's closed right now.
Cannabis dispensary.
Hey, get some bud.
In your area of the city, Alex,
what kind of things would be open 24 hours?
this is the dispensary open till 2 in the morning
that's the latest one we got
I don't just mean dispensary, I mean just anything
like restaurants, whatever
no, no, everything is open
in Manhattan, in Manhattan 24-7
if I borrow, things close down
like at midnight
I didn't know you were in Manhattan
that's why I was saying
like what in your area
I
Bro, you can find anything here at any time. Well, that's that's that's the that's what New York is like known for right?
That's why I was curious like in your area where you live
It's like 24 nine. It's it's not 24 seven when I am only a fast food restaurants
McDonald's burger thing all that shit. That's 24 seven any fast food you want Taco Bell
24 seven White Castle all that shit 24 seven. Okay
restaurants close like that, you know depending they're on the weekdays they're open to like four or five
Put him in high and
Sorry, like so convenience stores would be 24-7. You can always grab smokes beer
Yes, yes, yes
24-7 yep, you want a beer you need cigarettes you got it 24-7. Yeah
Cool
It's awesome
Yeah, I'm sure it is but for you it's just home right it's just it's not a
Yeah, it's not a spectacle like we see it.
And they have rules here.
You can't buy beer.
after 10 p.m. on Sundays, Saturday night.
There's like, they have times, I don't know.
Yeah, up here in Ontario,
we just recently put beer in the Canadian stores and that.
And I think Sundays, you're not allowed to sell at all.
But if you are, it's definitely only within it.
Right here, they stop selling at 4 a.m. to 9 a.m.
Yeah.
was today Monday Monday right yeah you can buy beer 24-7 here but on the
weekend Sunday they stop it at 4 a.m. till 9 a.m.
you're not doxing yourself here are you no one can figure out where you are with
the neighborhood
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I don't know where Psych went, Mason. I think he was saying to go over to that other channel. I don't think he went.
That's kind of strange.
It is. That's not really a good way.
It went up strange for a piece of change. That's Psych's motto, though.
My channel, though.
The thing is, if he was just going to shut the channel off,
And then go over to his thing then he was you know, he's just kind of leaving it open for us to just chat
So that's exactly no, he's definitely watching if he left us up here. He's definitely still like watching
He does this I'm not gonna make it I think I'm on five percent. I still had a walk to the blue stove, but
When I get back home I charge up
Do a line on camera new
You got to do it for the chat
That's right
They love it. There's an able so dead. There's literally not one person out. It's like I own the whole shit
I
Mean that you know, I'm saying it's true in the morning. So I know but that looks pretty residential from what I can tell
See you do it right my man
There's so many cops around here, bro, they just pop up. I don't know where to like you just be the red light
And all of a sudden you look behind you into there
Like they fucking just pop out like ghost
Thank you
Yeah, that's where he went time. At least that's where he said to raid
He hurricane power's stream he said
He just dropped from this stream and that's it. That's all we know
Well, let him have his time
I mean, she's like having fun
He said apparently it's that guy's birthday this that hurricane peril guy he he jumps around his different chats
I've seen him before
Apparently he's streaming so
To show support
Yeah
Hurricane Poro
Yeah, Hurricane Poro paro
Bless him
Over there and he's coming back
No, I'm standing on a spoon. No book.
I think that is just a man. He came back strong.
I thought you weren't going to show your face around here for a while after that.
I sent you shit. I was like a hole. He doesn't take it that crazy.
I honestly Alex, I didn't see the Alexander stuff.
I don't, I don't know what he said. I don't know anything about it.
She didn't really say much. She just swung on what I said and tried to like just
The next day she already made like 10 other lives about other people like that shit is already forgotten, you know
Yeah
So crazy people try to make it like big one day and then parties later like no one even remembers that shit
Yeah, but in in an hour or in a day you're gonna be you're gonna turn on me again. Anyways, right? So I'm not
You turned on me dick. That's why I turned on you dude. How did I turn? Yeah, I catch everything
I think you said something in the chat once like Alexander's dumb something
I may have you know what I may have but you may have been making a really stupid argument at the time
Possibly possibly but still when I'm fucked up. I just like
put it in the data bank and then when I see you I remember that not even thinking of maybe was my
dumbfold okay thanks um yeah well why why do you do that I mean it's one thing to keep it in the
memory bank sure it's just it's a piece of information but it shouldn't be something that's
I guess I'm doing it to myself in a way, you know
It has to be because I don't know you because if you look around I don't shit talk you and you
You are you watch other streams all the time and you're in everybody's thing. You just lurking we know that I am
So you see that I don't shit talk you so it's like like why attack me
It's no reason just because I want one so you're down why that happened
You did once recently like a week ago. You probably didn't remember but I did what sorry
About me like Alex is crazy or stupid
That's what I mean. That's our night that we hung out and we're like a good night. So that's what it's more. I'm like wow
There's another betrayer that we were just showing. Oh, come on man. No, I was in some chat like this guy's a dick
That's not me man. You should talk like nuts man. Why would you be so sensitive over something like that? Anyways, I
Don't know. That's the point. If anything just ask me about it. Just like what do you mean by that or just something?
I'll explain it. I don't know if I'm going to ask you about it. Now I do
I know sometimes when I type in chat, it's not exactly what I meant to say like I get that I know that but it's too late. It's already done. It's already sent there.
Look at this. This bus is running 24 seven here. This place is the best. Look at it. I can get on that bus for two dollars and take it three times over.
They take care of the people who vote just in New York. I don't know if it's blue state red state whatever the fuck
It's a blue state pretty sure what I don't know what to say. It's definitely the city. Yeah
They really care about shit here. Oh
When it snows like they go crazy with everything bow like emergencies they
Deploy everything
Alex time
Time says he should talks to you. You're a bald closeted midget
I've been asked to tell you that okay
Thanks, I'm not bored
class at it or imagine so
Thanks time
Yeah, that's the way from the brew store and then I walk four blocks back home, huh, right three
the
you know, work it through your veins.
You can't let it sit there and cloud it.
That's when you get a heart attack.
Like when you just cloud your veins, you gotta walk.
And apple cider vinegar will save your fucking life.
One shot of apple cider vinegar per day.
Yeah.
Yeah, you actually take a shot of of that every day every day more than a shot I tell you to the mother
Apple cider Braggs Braggs apple cider vinegar
garlic cloves
Garlic cloves you get a garlic clove you eat that shit raw just shove it down your throat and
Red onion red onion garlic clove apple cider vinegar you'll lift to your fucking 90
Apple cider vinegar kills the bacteria in your body.
You can't get sick, you know what I'm saying?
If you're a little like,
scratching your throat like,
ah, apple cider vinegar, done.
The race is back to you.
It's basically liquid plumber for your veins.
Yeah, I'm sorry, I'm laughing at, sorry Alex.
What are they saying?
Time he's funny man. Like he's e-trolls, but he he's funny fuck. I like that
Listen, I'd like to Alex me listen
I like Alex immediately denied being bald and then remembered he needs to deny being closeted in a midget too
Thanks time
So you time has to get together with he man because he may cause me a gremlin. So some shit pocket-sized gremlin
Time both. Yeah, you guys got to meet you and he man definitely gonna meet time is this freaking clever
Oh, man, like I like his I'm pretty sure it's a him. I think he said before
What's that I just want one culture by the past two hours
time that's a guy I thought it was a girl fuck I'm pretty sure they said that
it was a guy I could be wrong
doesn't matter either way
you're gonna be on your own buddy yeah you got to go in no I have I'm a 1%
Oh, okay. I'm a block away from the blue store, and then I got a little back five blocks. So
For like 20 minutes, so
Well, I got Nick here. He can entertain us
All right, brother. I'm just doing the the narration the play-by-play if you will
Okay, Alex. We'll talk to you later, man. Oh
Now we're friends and now we're friends
Now we're pals. I only give what I get man Alex you came at me. I came back
That's just how it is man exactly. I love it
Okay, all right. Hey, if you're gonna stay until you actually drop. Okay, that's cool
Okay, I thought you were leaving right away. Okay, that's cool. No problem
Yeah, Riz me too man wine gives me the hell of it gives me a headache sweet wine fucking just destroys me man
I just I can't
What's that Nick Lord Tariq?
Shut it time
Yeah, I wish I could let people up man. I don't know if anyone even wants to come up, but
This is during my news that there are always some soft cinderella's foot when it comes to alex
Um that probably needs a bit of explanation smash like
Do you mean the slipper slips off alex's foot alex's cinderella or alex's cinderella like he can't find his cinderella
You're muted Nick in case you didn't know I
Kiss you didn't know all right. My bad
Nobody needs to hear the shit that I'm
Yeah
But thank you. Yeah, that's an
Yeah, no club
The Cinderella, okay
How do I get me
This court is saying
You know, I'd switch it from HD one to two
Every ten minutes. I don't know. It seems like I
Don't know what you're saying Nick I can hear you but I can't hear words. I can hear the occasional word
The TV was off the curb
So you got to switch it to HD 1 to HD 2 like all the time
Yeah, yeah
That's like a fuck you to the new owner
How's everyone this evening we got smashed we got Jamie we got Rizzer we got time
I don't know if Mason's still around Darrell
Yeah, all there in chat. How's everyone this evening?
Then we'll try to turn the fan on. We'll be entertained by the fan. Nice, Jamie.
We need to do trivia with the thing that you say. I was just gonna say, why don't you just let me read a question since I'm
Yeah, great, nice thing to like.
You know and we'll just let chat we'll let you and chat play for a bit
We'll see how it goes if it sucks after a couple then we'll drop it
We'll just answer. I'm gonna answer all the questions for a million read this
And since person is not here everybody has a chance to win
Well hell yeah
I got my fan back on I'm happy again
If I take a bow here before the question. Oh, shit. If you want, it's a way to get the clock thing. That is a fast reader.
Okay. Who was the original host of Wheel of Fortune?
Original gangster. Not Pat Sejak.
No
I was trying to get it. I mean yeah the original part kind of gives it away that it wouldn't have wouldn't have been say Jack because everyone would guess that right
Well now I'm just gonna be lost
Anyone I
Think it was somebody
that I should know but I don't. I'm sure you know your name but you probably don't associate it with Wheel of Fortune.
Um, Jack Benny, Steve Martin, uh, uh, and old names, um.
I'm somebody that I can't right now. We need better ash. It would have been someone already associated with
game shows
Okay, so I'll give you that
Did you have a UK version riser there was a specific one for you guys
Um, let me see what can I think of another clue that doesn't spoil it?
Um,
this guy is really, really like one of the original original game show,
game show dudes, like from the seventies.
Okay.
Can't it's like right? Oh, yeah. I see him like he's got glasses
Don't think he did not that I can remember
No, there we go Halloween Town just got it Chuck Woolery
Oh Chuck Woolery for real. I was him was he was the original host of Wheel of Fortune, I guess
according to this
Very good. Halloween. Did you look it up or did you just guess Woolery?
That was good. I'm glad somebody got it.
Equations in the feet
What's the name of the cat?
Who could drive who could drive a car on Saturday night live? Oh
Okay, honey
Drive Z the cat
Nope
The SNL cat that would that could drive what was the right? Really? That was your big
It would have been good had they written it
And maybe like hey drives either cat and they're like they could have done it if they knew what they're writing sound live
They can come up with some shit
I'm thinking they could have got that
Drive see the cat
to be hot
I don't think anybody's even here man shots not moving I
Wouldn't want to be here. It's latest hell. Yeah, no
Well, I would take this time and just go in like like most time there would be nobody here
Then I would take off and go like dig through the dumpster and go find like something and I'd be like oh look at this y'all
But I don't I ain't done that in a while. So, okay for anybody left dangling
The the answer was toonses toonses the driving cat
Tootsie, I remember that little mother
So let's drop the trivia because it's not really going
Yeah, I know there's twenty-one
If I could get one more answer that I could almost get but damn they're also
They maybe like art history yeah, I used to go to the museum watch out. I'll get that art history
Well, it can't be too dumb to make a gas though Riz
Right
Yeah, I'm just right. No, I mean, I'm sure it's boring to talk for you guys
No, I love should be a I just put him down here watching and then you can actually hear me this time
I'm just kidding. Nobody can hear if I just like it's drive C
Fuckers
No
Why was that an issue somewhere?
Whatever is the answer. I'll be
I can't think quick enough.
Gotta say it.
Say it to the phone.
I'm telling you, I don't want to get the answer quicker.
If your phone has that little button,
it makes it where you can talk.
Talk to speech.
Or whatever is going.
I don't know what you're talking about, Nick. Like, honestly...
I'm gonna turn the fan off. There we go.
The fan was on the whole time?
I don't think the fan was the problem.
Because you said one part about Daisy, and then you went off into something else,
that I don't... I don't...
Well, you are an expert listener, so I'm...
Whatever you say, I'll...
You know...
give me another thing to go topic
Once I get topics, so I'm getting ready to Halloween is coming up. Are you doing something for it? You go into a party you?
No, no, that's it
Maybe I'll go outside and I'll be
The crazy motherfucker again
Like last year I took I took the chainsaw out
And I was put to the sound effects to make it sound like it's a real chainsaw with a cell phone and a speaker
Something tells me you do this every weekend. It doesn't matter if it's Halloween or not
Yeah, I know
Yeah, no more
No matter. It's just like it just kind of all blends together
365 days
You know, it's kind of like Rob Zombie or something. Oh
I missed it later is if you're leaving
Risenstein out my dude
Like I don't know if if psych is coming back
I don't know if I should drop or not like if we should just let the stream go
Or if he's coming back. This is where I take over I insert my dominance
And if I do in fact kill the stream, I've killed another stream and then I just consider myself a stream killer
Frank and wiener
Are you dressing up Frank wiener? I?
Don't know what that with Frank and wiener from Rocky Horror Pixar, so I
Don't think I really fucked with this shit. Oh, maybe it's like before my time
Could have been
Cuz like I didn't have a DVD of this shit and like that was like when things were coming out on DVD and then we like I
Was like basically if I didn't get it on DVD
But like a lot of my favorite shit. I don't have on DVD
And so I just got a bunch of stupid shit really. I mean now it's all streaming services. So
Who the hell even buys DVDs anymore? Yeah, and I saved all these motherfuckers like it was gonna be something
Yeah
I'm like these yeah
How many CDs have I thrown out man because it's just who needs it anymore?
You just download or just listen to the song online when you when you want. I mean, it's not
Then
fucking bulky media
We like our media bulky
Are me yeah
Yeah
I'm so fucking hot
Yeah, I would take over I would insert my dominance to the stream and
Then everybody else would leave and then I could probably go skateboard
Check out a local dumpster. Well, I only bring up the local dumpsters because like I would go out like on live and there'd be a
Bad ass fucking like dr. Seuss
rug that they'd throw away at the
Corner church or some shit. I'll be like it's like a fat ass dr. Seuss rug and I'm like, oh
dope
And then it would just like and I'd be like look at this shit y'all
And I'd be like so surprised that they were throwing that away and then it's like
And then I would get something else and then I could like art something
Then I get a bunch of paint and then they throw away a bunch of brushes like every school year
The school throws away a bunch of school supply and I'll go up there and get it
Like when they go yeah, like right when the school closes and then right back when school is starting back up
The teacher start throwing all this shit back up and then I'll come in up there and I'll get clean
I'll just clean the house and that's why I've gotten glue and paper and
I've been able to start like art and shit more because I never had the paper or paint
that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, that's right
That was for the day pocket video and then this shit
That's the man, I can't even fucking like that dude
Yeah, that's for the how high I just made that like
September 10 I
Was just like off
Offline all day and then like I woke up and like heard about Charlie Kirk and shit on September 11
So that's how I remember that shit because I was like
I was fucking doing this shit all September 10th, I was just like, but I don't ever have that much paper to do that, like, uh, that's what I'm saying.
Oh, it's such a, uh, oh, fuck yeah.
Dude, this place is a shit hole right now, but that just means you did a lot of shit.
Yeah, I mean it definitely looks lived in I give you that for sure whenever you do a video if the room
Looks like all put together and shit. You didn't do a good video
You want it to look like motley crew came in
Fucking had a hurricane
Hurricane Motley
Like you're just saying for your home. That's what you want. Oh, I know like if you're doing a video like if you go
Okay, well like psych won't play any of them. It's not like I mean they are pretty stupid
But like you can go to the videos and I have like tons of fucking videos
Okay, okay, it's fucking ridiculous, but I mean I've been doing on fucking since like back at like 2013
Maybe I started I think it was like December 1st because I would start doing birthdays
And it was like, uh, well, December 1st is a Woody Allen and Sarah Silverman and it might not be like
Because sometimes my phone would just pop up shit and I would just be like is this the right birthday, you know, so
Maybe it's like the day before or the day after but I would get right around that time and that's when I started was like December 1st
two thousand thirteen I spent my bad. I wouldn't like all the time videos, but it was like for a good portion
Of time that I ever had a phone. I
Would try to like fucking do something
Like clippy or fucking I can't stop saying fuck
It's okay, I'm not offended I'm typing at the same time. I'm sorry
There do I have water the fans off? I'm getting double fuck here
I don't know because the guy who runs the channel said that he's coming back. I mean, I doubt it. He's probably
Whatever
Let's just smoke some Normandy. That's this style of bud. I
Call it Normandy because you can smoke it. Yeah, you can smoke it if you were in war
Somebody had to smoke it
Um, hang on. Uh, sorry, JV just suggested you show me a piece of art. Let me just do this first
You got
What did she say? What did she say? Did you see is Kermit and Piggy that you did? Oh, yeah. Yeah, it's I just
I gotta get up again
Hi, Johnny, you're out on top of Kermit
You know Kermit I put that together for Jim Henson's birthday
I like to get to somebody's birthday like uh, it would be Bruce Lee's birthday, and then I'd be like what did I get?
from Bruce Lee
Like what did what did he get me or what did I get in person?
It's kind of weird
Or when you say like that
Like I made these uh, nunsha
They're gonna knock down the whole mountain of fucking DVD
It's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it
I was like, hell yeah. Thanks, Bruce. You feel that Bruce actually? Yeah, Bruce Lee got me though. And then
Oh, it was like fucking uh, what was it? Jim Henson's birthday?
And I was like fucking I always heard Jim Henson like made a
Kermit out of like his mom's old
fucking
Raincoat or some shit. So I was like I went around the house
I found this green jacket and I put it inside out and I was like, yeah, this look just like Kermit
Then I found these like eyeballs
They're like they were like on the curb and then I hot glued them to it and they fucking
Made a homeboy out of fucking some jacket
I'm like, I don't care me. I can't fucking I hate doing this shit
Like maybe if I was dressed up like Jim
I like to have like a beard, you know, like if I'm like Jim, I'm like, oh, hey, Kermit. How are you doing there? Oh, I'm okay
You know, but like I don't talk with Kermit a lot. So it's like
No, okay, and then I was a kid yeah at one time even I was a kid and
When I was this lady came over to house it was I've never told nobody this story
And this lady came over the house. I think she's like a family friend and she had like this fucking
Doll and then like I might like been like a little smart ass to her like to the I can't even remember what was said
But I felt like it was kind of like I I got this like, you know, like
Just just like a fuck you from the like a whole interaction of like
Like having this dummy and like I was just I don't know. I think I'm just turned off from like dummies
So like when I see like Jeff Dunham or some shit, I'm like, I
Mean, that's awesome that he could do that and he's really good. So I can't really hate
but
I'm still kind of weird it out
So getting back to the Kermit
you said that maybe if you were dressed up as
What's his face I can't remember his name
Can you dress up? Well, I do have it all on
So why didn't you actually make a Jim Henson costume too at the same time to use
It just involves like a fucking beard, so I mean here's some fucking hair that I got off of Erica Badu's perm
She's a nice cross seen her outside and I was like I love you
I love you too. I was like, oh my God. No, she drives by and I'd see her a lot and then
she'd like put her hand out the window and be like, she does this like sexy little wave
with her fingernail. I don't know how to explain it. Hey Garrett, maybe you can just like some
And she's like
And I'd be skateboarding I like no shirt. I wish I could put you full screen man
You need to be full screen because we you know, you're just a little image. I got this in here
So now I feel more
Feel more Jimmy
Yeah, you feel more Jimmy. That's a kind of inappropriate. Oh, yeah, I thought so
I was gonna have to get to stop get that hand out of my ass
Ah, today on the Kermit Farm Show.
Kermit!
Kermit, how'd you solve it?
Oh, shit.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Kermit!
I need my bath massage.
Does it have to be massage right now?
Kermit!
No, Jack!
Jack!
Jack, close your eyes. No!
I
We usually do that for 10 minutes or so and tell Jim it's off. Oh
Just don't feel like
Let's just curl up
curl up in a fucking ball I
Fought oh wait, we got this guy over here
How do you not show this all pants halfway down? What's going on?
Well, yeah, these pants don't fit
Or just Halloween fuckers fucking around. Yeah, ask me about Halloween didn't you?
I was I was I was I was I was
Didn't he?
This guy
Don't let the bike get in my nose
Have some pizza it's on the house. Yeah psych order this favorite pizza place
Oh
How do we know that's not psych?
Psych are you here?
Fuck you, Jamie Rose
Lenore
Stop it. Oh
Man, I'm already psych's biggest fan. I know all the
inners and outers of all the whole show. Oh, yeah, you know where the you know where the bodies are very so to speak, okay?
We should have an all-star
event and like
remembering the top 50
guests of psychs, you know
But who would be like top five would you say or somebody in top five top five guests?
probably like, uh, well, I want to say who started it all
Piranha
Shit she put in some time. Yeah, I don't know about Piranha
The uh
Was I was thinking about Meezer
Because Meezer was here. He had his cards. Oh shit. Oh people
People put up with Meezer shit for a while. I
Don't know if you knew Meezer you got to go back
I remember him. Yeah, I know of him. Yeah
Music come back
Yeah
Joker Joker he was there. I thought Joker was gonna come visit and go see psych
Like living a dream, you know, I was like man, he's beating me to you know, I'm gonna go see psych
But Joker was on the other day, right? Did you see that?
Nah, if I did I was probably too tired to remember maybe yeah
He was on I get excited when I see old faces
You get excited people that kind of thing
Yeah, I go to our old folks home. I see no wrinkle has faces. I was like, oh, I'm gonna play with them
Play connect the dots anything I can do
I'm kidding. Anyways, go on. You you like seeing the old the old crew
Yeah, but I like new people too like thing that is to come in and I like I don't have long
You was what they all on first day. I see them saying that you know
But like before you know it you could be here a fuck a week or two and I'm like
Yeah, oh geez
Screw that that thing that is man. Don't worry about that guy fucking idiot
But who are who are the other? Okay, so you got piranha you had?
shit
me or
me sir
Joker
Yeah, I want to know what you want to put like page on there
Page okay, it starts to seem like too simple. Yeah, like oh, I like
Page
Very very likable. Everybody likes her. I mean, that's just how it goes. So yeah
And then you want to put like beat us and shit, you know
Oh for sure beat us and shit, but I was trying not to like bring people up that would cause a ruffle
And so I don't know, you know
What man, that's a whole bunch of drama all the time
They can't ever seem to be just chill. It's like a damn Maori episode over here
Shit all the yeah, but that is the community, right the community is a drama
Sometimes it's okay because sometimes it's funny and it's kind of harmless, right?
But then other times it's like I don't really like what's happening
You know
Go get some water
Let's go get some water
Like yourself though
Time wanted to do some dumpster diving. Is that on the agenda tonight?
I don't even know if we can go outside with this stupid-ass Wi-Fi
What a good ass that was that was a good answer
We should just go out and do a Wi-Fi test, but then if I go on I can't come back
the
Oh my yeah, Kerry can be the lookout though. Just in case
Man, we should bring a flashlight. Yeah, I got a fucking light on the phone, but that don't
Do I even have a flashlight right now?
Somebody in front of you what is happening right now?
Why was their hair hanging from that jacket like a lot of hair? Oh, this is my Jim Henson beard
Okay
Oh, shit.
Just me pop character. Oh
All right, where's those pallets grandpa? I
Don't know we just keep seeing the same sign. Are you actually moving?
Yeah, it looks like it's dropped it for you
Did anybody else get freaked out by that hair?
Like, it just seemed like all of a sudden there was a person standing right in front of him, like with a jacket and hair and like, what the hell's going on?
Jeepers!
Aw, Nick, come back! Aw, no!
He's not going to be able to get back up either, shit.
It's just me and I...
I can't do it.
So...
Chat...
Yeah, you did Jamie. I didn't see the piggy. Did he show the piggy? I don't think so. I don't remember.
Okay, well, we're five hours into the stream. I think he's had a good stream. He can clip it here if he really wants I
Think we'll say good night for now. We'll part ways for now if he comes back. Maybe we'll
Join together then
Okay, so I'm gonna drop
Talk to you guys later
Walked alone through shattered skies
With nothing left but haunted highs
A thousand no's, a million tries
Still Joni's name was in my cries
Every crack a line, I swore I'd break
They tried to dim the fire in my chest
But you only whisper, don't you rest
I jakoś...
That's my hand.
The hand of God.
The grass sways, lives are made and whose tattoos tell her days
Hair flows free, like a river bend
Sweet summer, dick or son, everybody's friend
Sweet summer, wild and free
A mother of ten with a heart that can't see
She's birth or star, let her love shine
thousand scars. She carries them softly like the night hold stars. Tattooed maiden with
fire in her skin. Every battle she faced she rose again.
Face every mile
Tattooed maiden with fire in her skin
Every battle she faced, she rose again
We eat summer.
Am I muted?
I'm muted.
How am I muted?
What is going on with the lion's booty?
I don't know.
It didn't quite generate.
Maybe it was just born that way.
I don't know, but oh, here's good.
I was muted.
Oh yeah, I was too.
Yeah, that poor lion, I mean, but.
She's got a lion's ass
My ass don't I mean I got a nice ass
I'll see that that last remember booty the other day when I was dead and I speak it. I was like damn booty. Okay, don't lie
It's powerful
It bites back
It's like he's like like he's like looking at it like his ass is sitting next to him
I love that though, it's so catchy.
So, how's everyone's day?
Let's see, it is now, I guess it,
oh, you know, today is the 21st.
A few, you're monetized on YouTube,
you know what that means,
it's a special holiday.
Hey, guys, baby.
Yeah.
Morning, baby.
So, oh, it goes to, it goes to over so,
you know, we'll do Halloween special.
Birthday.
Psyche Thursday, I'm doing a 24-hour lab. I'm doing a sleep in a tent for 24 hours that I've raised money for my outreach
So I'm doing like a fundraiser thing Thursday. So stop through and say hey because I'm gonna have a long time. Oh
Awesome. Yeah, definitely. You're sleeping in a tent. I am I sleep in a tent for I stay in a tent for 24 hours
Today's backyard in your backyard. No, not in the backyard, but yeah, not too far. Don't we're safe. Hopefully
Yeah, I'd say and I'm gonna eat it because it's like fucking 39 degrees at night
And so me and my husband he's like, babe, you're doing your thing to Thursday. I said, yeah
He's like you might want to get a heat of like it or something. He's like, it's gonna be fucking co-dots
So but it'll be it'll be fun. I'm play play some games and
Order we were my tent. We'll keep you company
Yeah
Stop
Yes, I'll be sure I start it like in the afternoon late afternoon
Hmm. Yeah, I'm sorry. I kind of I left the panel then I kind of nod it off a little bit, but I
Got a phone call saying wake your ass up and so
That's what so that was a thank you Johnny for I
Put the Joanie song on yeah, so I don't know. Do you see my my Russian friends tonight summer?
I told her about the show. I thought I mean her song and stuff and she had so much fun though
Yeah, she liked her Tracy was on and
She got a kick out yeah, I was in Europe a little bit for that and then I went and
Me and my husband went and had dinner and he called me. He's like you want to go get something to eat
I was like sure so I just got back a little bit ago and all they could shoot
Yeah, well, yeah, so yeah the 21st is the his payday on YouTube this month
You know they pay so it would be for probably September or no, hold on
They pay for the month or more. Yeah. Yeah a month before and so
September was a little bit of a slow month, but you know
ghost sober is gonna be a
Better month and so I mean I have a happy Thanksgiving, you know, we love Christmas money
I
think I'm gonna
invest in like a year subscription to that the AI
music service because if you if you buy it by the year you're able to
Record your own voice samples and they'll put your own voice in a song. So maybe I'll you know, maybe I'll have some
amazing I don't know
Hopefully I sound pretty good
You're telling me Joni's still on this shit about me being on that guy's panel
I don't I got he I listened to the clip and it's like, you know
It's kind of rising of the ghost and the Tony situation a little bit or it's like, okay. I could see
There's a similarity in the inflection and like a little bit of that it's but it sounds like you're like
She's talking about some other people some guy from Maine King of Pines I wasn't on it
I wasn't on the panel. She thinks I'm some dude that goes there
Yeah, so I did you know and then
Yeah, I am I'm kind of teaching her about some of the things people do like you know
They can take a sample of a couple minutes of someone's voice and then they can make basically make you sad
Say whatever you want and call into shows and
Maybe you wanted to be me. I think that's she wants me to go do it
I think that's gonna happen. You're gonna say it enough that I'm gonna end up doing it
Oh, here she comes
Here we go fuck
What up, wait wait now listen God
My god, I forgot about it, but your little buddy down there underneath you brought it up today. Didn't you?
Oh, me you brought it up on because I said I did let him listen to the club
Yeah, well, she wanted me to listen to the clip
Just in case because it sounds so much like you but without you would like a real flat like without your your funniness
And I just wanted you know, it just says an old thing. I said to him. He just rewatched it not a big deal
I believe you I can't I believe you okay, I was I but you know
But but I just had reassurance it did kind of I'm not completely off by rocker. It did sound like you, right? Right?
I was like
Mason just now, right
Quantico I
Get that it was like I was like it's not it's like it would have to be him really disguising his voice or maybe like using
Yeah, why would he do that like for for that big buffoon in Maine? Why would why would I talk shit about you?
What why would I talk shit about you? No, no, no, it wasn't about me
It was a response after an incident
Supposedly allegedly. Yeah, and then that caller called in go ahead. Have you met Joni summer?
Hi summer
Hi beautiful back
Wait, I got a nice one that's apparently oh
you see the lion the lion show her show oh you didn't show her so she can see
no not the lion i mean yours
oh my oh you don't want to see my eyes look at her sexy mama see maybe she does
Yeah, you are something how far does that tattoo go down that shirt on a bun?
You know what the NIP's
I have a tattoo on my kitty too. Oh my god, you know what I can't even like hold a candle to you my friend
I feel so like low and small.
I'm right underneath you.
You're the queen.
Let's put the ladies on top.
And I'm going to sit on my face.
I'm going to sit on my face.
Ah!
I can't say anything cuz you haven't know I got so many trolls right now. I'm right now as we speak
I'm being copied. I can't speak. I was I won't say anything either. No, not you. Trust me
There's a but as a zillion of them. I give us a key a run for his money
Can I tell you the song I heard?
Not until you put me under her so she could sit on my face. Oh, that's what you meant. I went like I went
Summer sitting on mine right now
No, yes, I'm sitting on guys, which is fun, but I want to complain. Oh, no. Oh, see I'm gonna sit on her face
Okay, there we go yours. Yeah
That's better that's better there's adults in the room. Oh my god, this whole thing was I've been high
And Joni's like, how did they do this?
She's like, listen to this.
And I hear this woman sound like Joni.
But like, smegma is a word for what grows under it.
I don't know.
What the hell?
What was the song?
It was another streamer that some fucking fuckface put
my name as the donator, like, you know, with the money.
and put my name and then like saying it sounds like me but like not me and then I mean who
does that who take I mean is that a compliment a curse is that a stalker can someone just explain
it are you new to youtube joining us it sounds like this the first week but I mean it's horrifying
really quite honestly to have somebody do that like it's worse than that
It's like get off of my yeah, I called in that show and I said get off of my fake dick
Who's here? Oh
Mason oh, no, it's so late. Are you sure you should be up this late? Are you said him?
Mason are you there? Are you hello? Yeah, maybe that's his brother
Yeah
Is this
Hey, what's up, Gotti? Hey, what's up? Hey, what's up? I'm Joni
I put I put Jonesy, but it did work. I don't know what I'm doing. Yeah, it didn't show up like that though
That's why I said he's gonna help me later. I got a whole session plan with the psyche on my laptop
I'm not
No, get you together. He's gonna fix it. He's gonna help me and we're gonna make
Oh my goodness
It's the 21st day's the sauce is right. I know that the the the Libra
Psyche yes, yes Mason, so it's just like I mean like I'm trying to figure out what kind of channels this is like a drama channel or no
I'm gonna sing I have to sing the Carpenter's don't you sometimes we have fun sometimes we do
Sometimes we do drama. Sometimes we show tits. I mean, it's just a summer. Yeah
He's like what's summer like what is the whole purpose though like of this channel though like it's supposed to be about
Oh
Good thing he's not above me
Uh, good evening everyone, good evening, good evening, never been here before, never been here like a virgin
I'm sorry, Mason. I'm sorry, Mason.
I guess he wouldn't let you
are you a virgin?
I got up right away.
Because I knew you were coming up.
There's a different time.
Come on here.
I have a question.
It was funny.
Mason, are you a virgin?
We're gonna double tag you. Summer. I don't answer stuff like that. Oh
Last night that you were you touched some boobs, right?
It's like I never touched anybody's
Mason Mason have you ever been abused as a child?
All right
He's named after your name after the soap opera character named Mason from Santa Barbara
Thing that thing that is yeah, so we're still cool like right
Sure, I'm ready to I'm ready right now to convert to Christianity
Hey god, there's at least a half a million women screaming your name right about now
Trust me. I hear it every day
I usually scream your son's name. I usually say because you know if I say god now, it's a little weird
Because I'd be like I think I use I'm like, no, no, no, we'll don't scream jesus. Well, don't scream goddy. That's not a whole
Who the fuck is god?
I mean, I mean, we're all interested to know, like, your experience, though, like, of what we just did.
So, it's like, I don't understand why she asked me if I was a virgin, though.
Like, why would she ask me that?
Oh, no.
Well, ask me why I would ask you that.
You went to first base, right?
First base.
We're playing baseball now.
Just kidding.
Has anybody touched your chest?
Whose?
Faith and faith.
Oh.
No.
Never?
What about your penis?
Oh, whoops.
Summer, why are you going that far though? You don't have to go that far
We were talking about sex before you came up here
So I'm gonna continue. I mean I was she was sitting on my face and I would sit on her face though
after hours
Are you uncomfortable with it?
Is that Joanie?
Yes, that's Joanie
High five, Joanie
I'm trying to figure this all out
You're a little lunatic you need a laugh baby
Give me a little fucking psycho laugh
Thank you
Johnny why don't you guys go out what you guys have I'll take Johnny out. All right, take me out
Tony yeah, we're exactly with a leash. I'll walk you all over town
Summer you're ready a married woman though
Yeah, but somewhere that doesn't mean anything I can do like what you know talk about you though because you're already married I
Know but I asked you if anybody touched your penis
Oh, but it's that stuff is private though. I mean, I'm just up to talk about summer because personal
Okay, how about this? I'll tell you something private and then you can tell me something private
Somebody touched my vagina just a little bit ago. Has anybody touched your penis in summer to play to her kids
I got your pounds. I would already be married to her. I would already
And I will be with her okay Mason. All right, all right
He was just saying, he was like, what the hell are you doing?
I don't want you to make me feel like I'm coming home.
We're just playing around, Mason.
It's okay.
You have to midnight.
It's been a little while, Mason.
Those poops are too big.
No.
It's too big. What are you crazy?
It's too big, bro.
Oh, come on, man.
If you can't handle it, just say it.
No, no, I can handle it, bro.
I mean, enough is enough.
I only have a California king, bro.
I mean, it could only play like four of us,
but it's like 10 people.
Oh, my God.
They're gorgeous!
They're not bad!
Age, summers, tits, we're half our size.
I would already have murdered our husband, and we would be married in Mexico.
Alex, shut up.
I would see him.
We'll be teed.
He's told my husband before that he's waiting for the break line to break.
Yeah, he's a troker.
I'm going to cut his break lines.
He's going to fly right over the cliff.
And then that bitch is mine.
You understand?
No, no, no.
And so what?
And then you're going to make her change your tits?
Is that what you're saying Alex?
I think that is.
Yeah.
Why would they say that you have Star Wars shirts?
Do you have any Star Wars shirts?
No.
Time is just kidding around.
Time is just joking around.
He's just kidding.
the
Oh my god, come on down.
I'm just kidding.
Joni.
What?
Leave me alone.
I didn't do it.
Joni.
I wasn't there.
Start singing that song.
I wasn't me.
Just kidding.
Easy says hello everybody. No, he did not say hello. He said one bombing a cave from David
I wasn't me.
He's doxing and being an asshole. Don't try to twist it. It seems it says hello. Oh
You're so funny
Well, I guess that is the way he says hello
Shit easy you are my mods. So if you have if you like what that's crazy
You know and don't don't privacy complain you form on 420. Oh, yeah
What do you do?
Why not? It was the best thing that I ever did. It was the funnest thing I've ever done in my life. What do you mean, why?
Alex, what happened?
I put a 12-inch cock! What do you mean, you know? You guys didn't see it?
Dude, what I told Psyche before that you are associated with Psyche's channel is true, you know?
No, I am known as a Pornbomber now, guys.
Psyche has a pornbombing machine on his side. All right? Don't fuck with Psyche.
I'm gonna get me trouble because you want to be a fucking at home bomb less
I pump bomb money for 20 and I even put my psych on accident
Don't do that one again
The shitty ass one
We don't get along but she did not porn bombs fucking psyche get the fuck out of here
When you go live baby, when you go live
Me and her, when you go live
You well formed by me because I put my shit up
Tell her
Are you sure about that?
Yeah I'm positive
I'm gonna come up with Christine
And just drop a fucking top on your forehead baby
Christine can't come up on my panel all by herself
She don't need to come up and get a screen
Tell her
I'm gonna get you, watch
You're worst in sight
What you see money for 20 like hey money
You want a bet $50. Yeah
Okay, how long is the timeline?
Well, you never go live. So I don't know
You know more than a month I'll tell people on you but if you go live once in a fucking year like I don't know
Summer I don't have all the time. What are you talking about?
You will have on your bullshit hot summer thing I'm talking about our thing
24-hour stream. Yeah, you will be there baby. Like I was last time Ian me and Vinny
Potts and pants will suffer with you. Okay, remember last time you found a little cat that stayed with you
Yep
She will fucking not 24 hours and a straight
You think I'm gonna let you up now Alex
It's a mine fuck isn't it a mine bender
You know, you know, you can blame LES and money. They loved it. They were happy at combom them. They were laughing. They loved it
The hard way hide the 12-inch hard way, yes, you did my man
You learned a hard 12 inch way
You know that people think that that psyche's having you do that
I don't give a fuck what they think he's not and I'm not so they're wrong so let them think whatever they want
I can not do with that at all
Don't think he's facing enough
I'm gonna bring heat on him listen if people want to bring heat on him and they don't mean that's not gonna stop us you understand
I'm not gonna back down people's pony is gonna say oh Alex now he's gonna get more manure Alex because of you
That's not gonna stop me. That's actually gonna make people even harder
No, let's understand me. It's not bothering psyche. No, you're funny for 20
That's why because it's fun drop listen, I told them
I'm gonna go back to psyches before I go let me leave you with a little token of my appreciation and drop a tovins cock
That's all it was a little token. I say the left thing that is
Yeah, Mason, I got a lot of
A lot of kites Cox around me
Today Alex, can you turn down, please?
Don't even have nipples
So we're some of stuff that's way too like, you know far like, you know, it was just okay mason
Conversation up again, I'm gonna make you so uncomfortable. You ain't gonna know what to do with yourself
So God to let us just we moved on from that and this is your last warning next time
I'm gonna make you wish you were on panel all night because I'm gonna sex troll you all fucking night long
Who's she talking to? I know she's not talking to me. Is that you think?
I'm not talking to you fucking jackass.
I know that. I'm wondering, who are you talking to?
Macy's summer. Don't take it personally. No
It's it. Move the fuck on you're not gonna obsess over this. Okay. If you do I'm going to sex troll you
I'm telling you right now. I don't back down from her
Mason
That's what she's trying to say if you're gonna bring it up then she's gonna
Be
This is what you say. Fuck you and do what you want Mason. Don't
just do what you want to do
talk you into that stuff online
chill man i'll just hang it out here
ok then forget about it
if it does come up again
you can voice your concerns
at that time until then
don't worry about it
this is an adult party
are you 37 years old?
it's like 30 in the morning dude
still out
it's like what i'd do wrong
Do anything wrong, but you're supposed to just like hang out at the party
Because last night what I'm just hang out. He's not a little puppy dog. I'm just hang out do what you want Mason
psyche
Want to come talk about cool stuff man stuff that's cool and then boob school
So more once a place you like she hasn't got even out well in a while. That's what it is because you could be my
You know, it's you baby.
I'm going to have a party and you from the channel for 24 hours.
Go ahead.
Sign me up.
Somewhere.
Somewhere does have a live stream.
Remember that big just comes out of her mouth all the time.
She teaches me a few things at one.
Cock is always on her mind, man.
It's not yours though.
I can promise you that.
summer this is like an open panel free panel the last name is Dickerson the name Dick is in her
last name Dickerson
me down baby
it's like me being called Alexander Cocherson
Steen to you Cocherson
or Pussy sir Pussy sir
like the name Pussy written his last name
it's not a really funny feature
I thought it was funny picture when I was looking on YouTube that someone had posted and I missed that this person had posted this picture
But like I kind of got a little giggle from it. Maybe well, please you do too. Let me have a
No, it's like no, it's like I don't have a problem with women. I mean, I just don't want to talk about sexual stuff though
So you're gay that means you're gay dick
You're gay Mason
No psyche. I'm not gay. I just don't want to talk sexy.
Okay, Miesin.
You don't want to talk about women or sex. That means you're gay.
Miesin, we've established that that you're uncomfortable with it, okay?
We've established that.
Okay?
I want to do is talk about women and sex.
Miesin, you understand?
That's how my mind operates.
I don't think it's like that.
It's a comfortable way though.
Like a safe and comfortable way.
that you're
Whoops. So you feel comfortable. I'm in. I'm feeling
uncomfortably uncomfortable. Look how big her boobs are.
Oh my gosh. Five feet tall.
Look at this. Hold on. I'm sorry.
I think I'm sorry. I just saw this picture. I have to show it. Yeah. Okay. What is it? Oh my god imagine if I if he told
Would you else stop thinking?
That's amazing. You're talking that you're talking in your sleep
Had a couple people and all
involved in it
Come on
Does imagine being triggered by an alex
Oh, is that supposed to be me? Is that thing?
That's supposed to be me dig. That's supposed to be Alex
This mr. Ghost told me
On there's me as the priest
Got daddy in me. I didn't have you to deal with a frequent panel guest. He takes issue with
Okay, oh, that's saying
Okay, look at this one
He's gonna come up, and it's all gonna be over
That's Peter and psyche getting married and Axan Joe mayors is the priest
Now glad it's classic, bro. Wait, but it's a Jewish wedding and psych is apparently Liberace is that
There's a good shot. I mean
It looks hot there
Look at that turkey neck
Peter doesn't look a day over a thousand
She looks beautiful
Oh my god that collar bone is ghost over happening or what ghost just hanging out there in chat
Hey, my god, my god. Got you so you're too close to the camera man. Like it's hard to see your face
My love. Yes, baby
Is it this you said the solos is it solos team? What do you call the solos? What do you know?
I guess it was september 21st. That was one of the longest that the end and then we our days get shorter
Is that thing things that it's september 21st? I guess that's that's when fall starts. That's the equinox. Oh, yeah
It has passed already. Yeah. No, I thought it's a 24. Is it not?
September what is the day that it's the shortest day and then
December okay nevermind
Forget it. It's not leap you wait that wedding was promised 2,000 years ago. What the hell baby I
Still didn't got a smash
I have here. He's threatening. All right, ghost. Whatever you want. Drop drop the money. I guess and then you'll have the power again
Don't bring up
Donate a dollar fuck that's that fuck cheap fuck. I'm I muted it. What's that?
I can't do this. Can you hear me? Yeah
So say it's already false. It's already fall season right now, right? It's already fall. Yeah
the
thing take this kid under your wing where you
why are you trying to act normal Joni?
you're not normal
go back to the fun house laugh
she's anti-light meat, they net it
she's talking like a wight talk
every time she laughs, she farts
whistelice is your dana
Oh, yeah, something's wrong. There's my iPad. Oh, no, who's that good times to be there? Oh good. No way
Yo Johnny's lap will bring me out of a depression you know sand
Okay, we have another guest coming up, let's see who's coming up. We have I know right
My laugh makes me fart involuntarily, so I can't do it anymore
you can't fart voluntarily anymore
no i don't want to laugh
it has to always be voluntarily
oh my god
i want to have a choice in the matter
what about when you fart
what are you gonna fart do you laugh
soma can bend over without peeing
it's for the virtue of liberty
excellent
i like your style
Johnny they have a catheter for that. You ever seen someone go to the gym every time she bends over
It's a creed juices all day
You know what I'm saying?
You're muted, ghost.
Ghost, you're muted.
You're super screened my fucking videos when I'm working out.
There you go.
Yeah, I see.
Of course, I examine everything.
I look for the camel toe.
I look for everything.
You do the thing with with the pages feet man. That's fucking. Oh man
Yo, she took over sandal where she was golfing and her feet were black like she was like stepping on tar
I'm a bit dirty Canadian
You screenshotted. Yeah a million of them
That's how I pull bomb. Oh, this is a psyche on accident because I was trying to pull the picture up and I just hit a cock on accident
But man, you're gonna love it trust me you're gonna be like there's no way that's just from grass
Trust me someone's gonna agree with me like that's not just from grass Alex
That'll be on board
Anyone with half of a mind will be like there's no way that's
All the way around
Dude get over yourself. Well, that's what was when I pull up the pictures will be the judge of that. That's my point
Sometimes watch your feet stop being a bitch to wash your feet. How about that? You know you you or you got dirty feet too, right?
That girl is a goddess what from what I got is we're dirty
The way she was painting and she's got like
Can play handball before it she's not a guy like
You ever seen a forehead?
Oh yeah, because it's finished, you guys are up here, you're gonna fuck it up.
I can play handball over forehead.
This is our report for today.
In the other day, you were fawning all over, and I didn't have a lot of them.
No one believes.
Bro, I was fawning all over her stupid avatar, that's a lie.
You see, in real life, it's gonna be black hair, a forehead from hell, and dirty feet.
You know how little kids pick on each other when they like each other punch the girls and stuff
That's what Alex still is stuck in that stage
About the women he thinks are pretty
I know you I'm gonna be longer than anybody on this panel
Yeah, because she's getting attention now slow. She's got dirty features
But anyway
Johnny's singing
Yeah
Mason do you sing
Wait one thing that is do you sing?
I'd say the drums. What a dick. Is that why you're called Mason the drummer? That's funny
Yeah, that's comedy, bro
Okay, that's what my name has that I know how's the shirt doing? Are you still wearing the same shirt, man?
You are
No, you're not you're supposed to change it dick
That's what they made all the shirts, you know, you're out of Macy's
You just couldn't say Macy's.
it's okay it's okay mason i like
mason send your shirt to syke
syke what do i do here man
syke send your shirt to mason
mason how about like you find like
are you like that color
where is this where are we going
it's your fault you haven't changed that shirt
for three days so he follows your lead
i changed his shirt
no you haven't you have that same shirt
for three days mason's following your lead
you have to lead by example bro
I changed my shirt
You changed it last week as a month chart. You've been saying it's my mouth mention for two months, bro
Yesterday
You know what you need you need one of those rollers with the little stickers that take the cat hair off
Stop coming up
On the clothing
Thing that is you got a star wars shirt
No, no, I don't
Don't you sweat daily
You wearing you sweat you pee you throw it in the hamper new shirt the next day like I don't get it
Is that you hang out on the way to where you went the same underwear from 92, but there's my hangout underwear
all of the
the
I ask for donations for the outreach that I do because it's for the outreach that
Some dumb face that's showing me fucking a pound of wheeze
Dollars
what
You better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you
What if I say please what happened to the gun?
Why would you want to bring him back?
Just to prove you can at least give us freaking five minutes
All right there
Yeah, he's teasing you he's playing with you because he's teasing me he figures you are going to bother me
About Star Wars shirts, which is what's happening. So time wins
I don't know. I don't. I don't
know. I don't know. I don't
Well, where the fuck is actually like that side I mean like I said, there's an echo. That's Johnny
Her avatar goes when it's happening I could pay my own way
I'll leave no, yeah, I'm not saying you're you have to leave
The echo was coming from yours. Is it me?
Johnny
No, but help me. Okay. Just help me for a second. I have a technical problem. I
Got a technical problem
Okay, I have an iPad right now
Turn out the volume on the iPad TV I can see your boobies and you really need your little noodles
I think it's because you're still watching the actual YouTube stream on the TV volume with the volume. So it's okay
Layers which one the TV or the iPad whichever one
Yeah, let's be must now do it now is there no echo. Yeah, oh my god, I can see your boobies and noodles and now I can talk
Thank you. You can bring Alex back. I'm not going to ban him.
Alex.
Okay, Alex. Oh, he left. He already left. Alex.
What a crybaby.
I think Alex might be paid so I'm going to roll a low.
He's going to grab a and all so he can come back and he'll be back.
Alex, you guys need to independent queen.
He doesn't need me.
That is really cool.
You really have no Star Wars shirts at all.
Hey, hold on, I got him.
Hold on, Matt, Matt, what's his name fucking?
Mason?
Mason, has anyone ever touched your penis?
No, they've touched mine and I don't have one.
Has anyone tickled your booty?
No.
Has anyone ever put your penis in your mouth?
Oh God, what about a finger in your ass if I was a rich man? No
Would you like me to put a finger in your ass Basin? Oh my god my
Would you like me to touch your penis? Oh, I'd like you to touch mine if I only have
I don't know what you're doing.
is pretty annoying isn't it? That's exactly. That's all I would do. I don't think you ever answered the question though. What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did you learn today? What did
Are you sure are you sure I can't stick a dildo down your throat and make you gag so much that your eyes water
And then you spit really nasty
Gotta go psyche it's Mason. Are you okay?
Yeah, psyche talk to me man. Yeah, I'm here. Well, what do you think about that those days it can that kid?
We put can we play with your buddy? Hey, son, are you okay? He's looking for help
Missing we're all gonna play with it, okay
I'm here to talk to you I'm here to talk to you, man. I'm right here
Mason do you know that if you just move your jaw a certain way you can make your mouth bigger and it can go down deeper in your throat
Was that wrestling's an upload job? Look, can you repeat that, please?
What a hooker.
The only hooker sing that song.
Like a virgin.
Don't you dare call me a hooker.
The issue is that I've already answered you.
I've already said no.
I don't have Star Wars shirts.
You sure?
And that time was playing a joke on me.
Like a virgin.
So that should have answered.
That should have stopped.
I don't know.
He's why I go such for why that's all I want to know why you guys boys
No
If you felt like you didn't answer
If you guys were in wars you might be cool. Is this a debate?
Alex god damn it. Oh, do you want to make it one?
God damn it Alex
You're so loud I can't hear anybody else because I have to keep the volume so low what
Who are you talking about my friend Alex? Yeah
You're not talking to a silver man
the
I
Exactly summer I care about the law. I'm a low-biting citizen, you know, it's funny on the way back
Like three DT cop cars Joe, but I mean they were just eyeballing me and I was like go ahead
I'm their boss
You don't get out of that stupid
cause it's only good.
What do you do?
Do you have a burger?
It's like if you have a burger,
these burgers at large fries
and I had like four coffees.
What do you have today?
Are you going to fix your fucking camera?
Why are you so big?
you remember that movie where the guy ate McDonald's every day for like a month remember that movie
oh it's super size me
super size yeah
he died in a Miami boom
he died a few years ago
I'm married so you don't have to worry about it
he did a few
do you think it was McDonald's?
holler
yeah he did a few of those things for the white guy
cause right after that he did the uh
whatever where he did like some some really strict diet and he got really really thin
That's what fucked him up
Yeah?
Who's gonna 69 psych?
That's what he cares about everyone
He's good
Mason wants to
I don't know
Someone's gonna take one for the team
Mason?
No, Mason
No, Mason, are you gonna...
Mason, are you gonna...
Why you do that?
I had two hash browns, I had a sausage, McFinn, I had two coffees in the morning, and I had a large fries, $10 burgers.
That's the time I had a sausage with McFinn in 2004.
Back in elementary school, right?
Big pits and big ones, baby.
I haven't Donald Trump day
Did you enjoy the food you had at school?
Did you enjoy it?
Sex based and it was like fucking sex
Oh cool
You didn't pay the kicker yet, oh
No, why would I do that word?
Name your price
Bates like name your price
That's 200 hours 25 a day. So that's two weeks. That's two weeks. $200 to get rid of me for 24 hours. That's it
What it's 25 hours for 24 hours, bitch
You're not special 25 hours and you're gone for 24 hours, bitch
two hundred twenty-four hours no if you want it if you want it if you want to
talk about the electric if you want a timeout page maybe any of us two hundred
dollars and go say get kicked out either
How much is it to kick me out?
How much to kick everyone else?
$5
If you give me $500
I'll give you $200
I'll give you the whole panel
I'll give you a Canadian loony to kick ghost
We don't want your fucking Canadian dollars brother
What's the loony worth?
$0.71 or something
Oh shit
That's about 43 cents, roughly, who's on the loony now who's on the
Your eyes close your eyes
Bro
What's up? What's up? What's up?
What's up? What's up?
Let me pet your pussy
I hadn't showed the babies in a couple days
Now that's a good woman
Yeah, that's what have her size I would have enjoyed that if what
They're just too big.
They're too big, bro.
Hey, Saki, can you put me first?
What did you say?
I want to show you guys something as well.
She's going to have back surgery in a year, bro.
Yes, I'll put you first.
Well, Saki, what happened?
Saki, you're answering me.
Saki, but you left.
Where did you go?
I disappeared into the abyss.
Uh-oh.
There you go.
He disappeared.
He has charisma like a cheat.
That's what he's showing you.
How to go somebody.
What kind of gay shit is that?
Okay, what are you going to do, Mason?
Mason, what are you doing?
That's it
We see your t-shirt Mason. Let's see a t-shirt man
Mason you come to my panel all the time tell me how pretty I am you come and tell me how pretty I am and everything
So why can't you show me your shirt?
Mason you go to summer
Wow
I
Made some hold on hold on Mason you go to summer's
Hold on. Yeah summer. I'll talk to you before like on your channel
Yeah, crazy you have been all innocent
It's like you got dandruff on your back. I do not hold that was an awesome trick ghost. That was frickin
Don't be a ponytail guy bro, please
Your world premiere of that trick
That was your world
You see so much shirt you see a little shoulder you pull that one string. That's it the whole thing comes over
I don't want to laugh and encourage him. I have it in my eyes sometimes.
You know it's true, Johnny. That's why you laugh. You know it's true, baby.
You're so mean and you're so funny too. It's like a shoelace. Just pull that one string.
It's like a sparkle effect. That one string.
That's it. You're looking like Twilight here.
What?
Alex, do you want to try and dig through an astronaut uniform or something when you're trying to make it?
No, man. A nice string right there.
And you're in.
I don't want to show myself.
Holler.
That is a good point.
I'll give them that.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
I'm gonna make County whistle. Hey sis, they make fun of you. We'll make fun of them. Don't worry
We'll jump in. I'm just here. I'm just here to have a good time. So I'm not trying to do anything wrong
Are you having a good time?
Yeah, all right
By the way, Jay, is that you again?
I'm sick of you
You got too many tattoos, I don't know whether to read you or fuck you like I don't know
You're both
Do you have to with your eyes
Like I mean your eyes are still free while you're blackened. So don't you have a spider?
Have a black widow
I
I'm gonna leave because you know what
3 a.m. Every night she makes it move look the laughter is breaking
When she gets on fucking a mate a male
And I have man eaters had to eat on my belly
Man either
That's probably a conversation piece
You got it the black little wife bites the house when she's done with it
Oh
No summer to tattoo that you had
that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that's all that
Oh
Like after them I'm stabbing I gotta go get the blue
Come on I'm a comedian baby
I'm a comedian. Not funny
your dick
The dick is in the chat so he heard me the dick is in the chat
Dream catch a boy when you don't stabbing people do you go to like the hardware store and get the little paint change for the feathers
What are you, mom? Shut up, bitch.
I know he's even talking to you.
We're talking about hitting somebody against a fuck.
Are you igniting a man?
What is this about?
Shut up, bitch.
The fuck? I'm not even talking to you.
I'm talking to an easy loser.
No one gets a fuck.
That's that D-Li and it has a dream picture tattoo.
I don't give a fuck.
What are you standing up for him?
Fuck D-Li.
The bitch at the fuck up.
That's a good argument.
Fuck you. How about that?
Don't bitch. Shut the fuck up.
No, you can't.
No, and you can't fuck you lie fuck you
Eli
I'm a
Bitch I don't give a fuck bitch
Why don't you go suck easy stick?
the fuck out of you bitch
you don't even believe in God
what the fuck up
just like
i really do tally you out for a fucking night bitch
because he manifested that
that bullshit in his fucking life
he got murdered
yeah my ex got murdered
i would do a mercy killing
2142 Sourdough, that's where you find easy, in the Bronx, as a hill, his name is as extrespo
2142 Sourdough, he is Doctene, he's wanted for stabbing Eli
Zidney, he is Doctene on your panel, your channel's gonna get hit
But don't jump to conclusions, this iconic arachnid is mostly misunderstood, she's not a bad girl
she just looks like one. This is the Black Widow. Black Widows are a type of spider,
perhaps best known for, well, you know, sexual cannibalism. That memorable behavior is where
the Black Widow got its name. She has a sweet side right, but it's like the mean side is mean.
cool vindictive
Basically, you know, she's asked about
You know, oh, you know
You've had a lot of relationships like five
Exes or something and she's like yeah, and that one of them is murdered and
Holy
With me, but you know after we divorced, but she's like
And what happened?
She said you'll never figure it out, and it was like she said it was a joke and I would have been like yeah
It was a joke, but then after tonight she's like oh, yeah, I had a call clumsy. He said he's gonna take care of
if anybody bothers me from Texas, he's in a
I don't know
Violence or something and it's like she was referring to Alex. I mean, what the hell is going on Dita?
And then I hear all of a sudden people telling that this car reverse that you're part of like these people they clip me
That's what they do dog. If you go on you you
Yeah
And because he had emas and he's like if I ever become paralyzed I am gonna kill myself
I don't know. He didn't do that. I don't like it. He's a fucking, like, talented...
Talk to y'all later.
Did you kill him?
Why, where could I have it fun? What's the point?
Did you shut it off?
Yeah, I'm not leaving now.
We're sitting around having a good time. Like, this is dumb.
I think the Black Widow triggered it.
Yeah, but my Black Widow's fun.
Who left?
Alex got kicked off the panel because he was up there screaming fucking he was not been fucking easy
Okay, hey
First of all you're gonna lose your mod because I will
Take it out myself. You don't need to like threaten to like privacy strike me. Okay, you're my mod
And so you're not my modern anymore since you already privacy strike me twice the other day because of Alex
I would have taken it off. You just asked. I don't know what's true or not. I mean privacy strike to you easy
Yeah, but you're a you're a lot Alex is up here screaming at address and you're getting mad at the person
He's he can ask me
Sikey take that out. I can I can black and take it. Why does he hear that?
Don't worry about it. I'm not him because he's being a bitch
Sonic was just dust on your panel. I know but I can take it off
I mean, it's like what do I mean in the stream right now again, then like, you know, whatever
I mean, it's like I'll do it when I
But you don't sit up here and bitch when people do it to you
No, I don't my only my name is John Bates. You're down in beach, California
I mean what? I've had like five people come here looking for scrap metal today. I think I'm pretty much done. All right
That's my life. Yeah, I'm good. Y'all have a great night. I love y'all
This is a stupid you're literally getting pissed off at the guy that got fucking doxed on your shit
Well, but then you want all of us to have something to bring you when it happens summer just try to strike me though
That's the thing you keep letting Alex do this shit. He's not on the tail right now
He's not I picked him off as soon as you said he'll be up here in five minutes. He's not
He's been a Alex. Oh, if you send me $50 tonight, I might let you on later, but you're not on tonight anymore. Okay. There you go
Yeah, that's the second year right now, and I will take it out easy. You don't feel like you know
Get bitching in the chat
Technically it's 24 hours because summer did pay to get you know take for what?
No, I didn't I brought it back because y'all were talking about bringing them back so I didn't send any money
Yeah, I didn't know he's gonna be like that though. I just want to argue with him. That's what I said just bring them back
Not bad. I didn't think it was gonna put up here and dock somebody on the fucking panel
Once again Alex runs another fucking panel
Yeah, Alex man. Yeah, it's a pattern at this point
I should be he doesn't even realize it and he does realize it. He doesn't give a fuck psyche
You just don't realize it. Alex is doing this shit on purpose. Mason got cut in the crossfire
Where's Basin at you fucking that off you guys like that conflict
So they're having fun talking about tits and having a good time and fucking numb nuts like for no fucking reason
Because it is he gets triggered
No, man, what is it Alex you just need the attention so you do this just to be the bad boy just to get attention what?
Well, no because it's he's gonna get he wants to get psyche and shit and psyche just doesn't see that and I've told
Psychi just a billion fucking times. I've known Alex for a long time
He thinks it's a fucking game he thinks it's funny and it's not I
Don't think anyone found that funny. Okay, maybe I'll
What did you just say?
Staying it, brother.
Can't stop.
Won't stop.
So, just like, is Psych fixing the video, or did he leave, or do we know?
He's in the back.
He's pissed.
Okay.
Thing yes, sir
How are you doing tonight? I'm okay. How are you? Oh?
I'm having a ghost over brother. I'm having a good time. It's good. You sound like you're having a good time
Gotty what how are you doing?
That's good
That was the most depressing answer I've ever heard.
I'm not doing good with it.
You want me to lie?
I'm not doing good.
I'm doing great.
I want you to whisper sweet nothings into my ear.
Again?
Well...
If you're asking what I prefer I prefer that I'm gonna cut your throat ghost
With a turkey fucking knife, I'm gonna just cut you like a pig
Like that. Yeah, is that what you want to hear? I like it
What's your favorite scary movie? That's literally what you sound like
This is how it ends, you know
Yeah
Now he's honestly probably crashing
Yeah, he's like it's not me it's the cocaine fuck up. I
Mean, it's not even a good argument though. Like it's not me. It's the fucking drug. I took I mean
I mean, you could you make that excuse if you'd like
Accidentally, you know, you were driving drunk. You hit somebody back. It wasn't me. It was the alcohol. It was amber Duncan
Oh, well, motherfucker, you drink
Well, don't even bring them up anymore dude Alex fuck
you love doctors they just got to like a list of people they just write down everything
They go to their files
Let me see my roller-decks. Who do I got in here?
You know my favorite thing to do is like tell them I'm from somewhere and like I'll give them like a fake address
and they literally like post that like it's like
Still could affect somebody right it just may not be
At the end of the day
Yeah, that I get somebody else if it's a real address. Yeah, and somebody else. Yeah, it's gonna affect them if they do something
That is sure. I never actually use the real fucking
Addressed in whatever yeah, what if one of these crap man?
What if one of these crap middle people goes to psyches, right and on their way there they crash and die
That would be murder, right?
Now would be a stretch to
No, I mean on the streets is you know that's already there to die the people
Normal people would some people would argue that but in court. I don't think that would
cause an effect
In one of the other one of the other communities I go to right this is unless you can show that the doxing
Tell me tell me if this was was to cause the death like was to cause
There's this there's this guy I know from another community I used to go to
He went to an olive garden. He tried to rob the olive garden. This was years ago
So he tried to rob the olive garden. It was he had a gun
So he he left the old garden with whatever money God he started
He got in the car get trying to get away the police started chasing him high-speed chase
Well during the high speed chase that the cop crashed and died
He got 15 years. Yep. I think I forget what what you got you got second of your mass lot or whatever
But he got 15 years, but that's on him, right? That was his fault
Here's the better and this actually did happen
There were the person that got in a high speed chase and the cops were chasing them the cops ended up hitting somebody that was just crossing the road
Merck them and then the do got charged for it. Yeah
Yeah, I agree. Yeah, totally during the the occurrence of
Someone dies never would have
Commit the initial crime. Oh, he did was he was just running from the police
They're
Because the guy is running
Yeah, so he's
He's initiating right there in the death. He initiated. Yeah. Yeah, nobody goes to death while he's committing the crime
It's not first-degree murder. Obviously. It's not second-degree. Maybe it's a case for third, but man slot
I believe you got like 15 years for that shit
I guess that's the one reason he was only 18 and they're like, you know, and the judge even said like I'm sorry this happened
Like it wasn't what is your fault. You shouldn't have been running in the first place
But like I know you're not the one that hit them, but yeah, yeah charged. It was like involuntary man
Yeah, yeah
Yeah
It's just like it's not just like but it's kind of it's similar
It's like an extenuation of if you're robbing a store with somebody and the other person kills somebody
You're both charged off murders with the murder, right?
It's kind of like an extension of responsibility
During the commission of the crime if you weren't committing the crime
It wouldn't have happened. That's why you both get charged. That's why you get back when I was in high school my
Friend, I mean I grew up with him. He wasn't really my friend, but he
his cousin
You know shot somebody but he all he did was he's the getaway driver. That's what he did. He got like 15 20 years
Oh, yeah, you still get time for that. Yeah. Oh, yeah
Like this cousin called him like come quick me up. He come and pick them up and then yeah, he was the getaway
That's what he has to prove he has to prove that he didn't know anything about it
But still you're gonna get fucked with that one. You have to you have to prove it
Beyond a reasonable doubt
I think that's how if he has a text or something saying, hey, can you pick me up at eight o'clock in front of blah blah blah, you know that maybe that's specific
Well, what happened in that certain
Circumstance was the dude got in the car and he had the
poop you still on him and
He told him what he did and still drove him. So oh
Well, there you go. That's that's an accessory after the fact right there, right? Yep. Yep
Yes, they want to get you they're gonna get you. I mean
Just give my reason
Yeah, how how heinous the initial crime is of the other person, but that's why they overcharge
You know, yeah, so that they know that not all of it would stick and they can peel away what won't stick and leave you with
What's this is why you can get paid a lot of fucking money to be a lawyer if you're a good fucking lawyer
You get paid a lot of money, man. There's a lot of excessive time done for uh
Small crimes back in the day, but these days they just fucking
They're letting every murderer go every fucking rapist go. It's crazy. I don't know how we went from tits to this conversation
Oh, Alex fucking
He flipped the whole fucking
Yeah
Uh, well, yeah, it depends right it depends. I think mostly as far as what you were saying God
He depends are they mostly on how much publicity?
the the crime
Right
Yeah, what good what kind of lawyers are getting how big it's for sure as far as you as far as you
But you I was more talking about you saying that that they let a lot of shit go these days
And it's like, well, not if your case gets a lot of publicity.
And it's and it is your fault. You're not gonna they're not gonna really go easy on you, you know
It's a thing. You know what you hear about letting a lot in this country now. So so he's been arrested 50 times
And the judge just let him go again on a $2,000 bail just yesterday. We're hearing a lot of that now
Why why not on the rest people go? I don't have a good purpose. They purposely letting these people go to do these fucking crimes
and these judges
Dude, I've even heard stories like where the prison's been so full like that's been years ago
It's been so full that they were letting people out like to like promise to appear in court like
This is a better explanation than than giving it intent. I think just the fact that there's such a backlog and an over
Uh, yeah, it's clogging the system, you know
I think that's probably more the concern than it being done on purpose.
I mean, they are purposely letting people go.
I'll give you that. No, I give you that.
But I think it's more done out of necessity and not because there's an intent to...
Make society shitty or what? No, I think there's an attempt to make society shitty
So what they could take advantage of that because what would be the intent to let these people go just so they don't have them in prison?
Because the system can't handle it at the moment and if they're gonna progress at all
They have to do something so either they they try and get through the backlog. They cut the backlog. They
Raise the bar of what they're gonna prosecute, you know, they have to do something because it's just too much
It's like how many planes are landing at an airport. There's a there's a maximum capacity
You can like yourself
No, it's crazy
Listen if you want to argue about the individual things that they're letting go that's a different thing
I'm just telling you
That's a better explanation of why these things are happening as opposed to it being done on purpose
Now if you want to talk individual things, yeah, we can go through them
And I'll say yeah, that's fucking stupid and you know, I wonder why would you do a thing
What would you do if you were in charge of things? What would you do?
What would I do if what if you were in charge would you do you be more uh
Tough on crime would you if I were in charge? What would you do?
Don't like fix what's the fix? No, I don't know I mean honestly, I don't I don't think there's definitely a fix
That work we should be tough on we're not we're not tough on those
The tough we should be tough on
You should be very fucking tough on certain things
Yeah, I think I think I
Think we should be I think we should be even tougher on things. I'm talking
Fucking shooting for us
Not to sound like the the liberal the big liberal here, but
the cause of crime is
Is important to right like trying to reduce 100% so there's and and and why that does play a part in everything
Hold on but like domestic violence PDA PDFs type stuff stuff like that. We're not doing anything about murder
We're not doing anything about right now. You want to talk about crimes that actually you can go and say, you know, there's
resources that are lacking in certain communities, well, and all communities at this point, you know,
and different things like that, yes, but then there are certain crimes that you can't do that for
Sorry
No
They agree. Yeah, no
So if you have a will to do there are crimes that you can blame research lack of resources and shit like that
Would you agree with me, oh sorry thing good, sorry I think there's certain crimes that are just like can we say like I'm forgetable like
Yes
Is that really beta all imagine that I'm not even that
Was that really her what it's against the law. No, I should some surprises here and I is beta
Anyways to go back to what we oh high Apollo as well, sorry
Go on. Where are you saying?
What up, Malacca?
Um
Will you just call me? Yeah, we're not sure he was a little
Yeah, you got to break the heads you got to fucking really crack the skulls
You got to do it in front of everybody too. You got to go up to the gangs you got to go up to the fuck
Fucking bodies in the street, you're not even discussing it. You're just giving me the Trump agenda
If somebody else sees it that's what they're not gonna do
If you're back there drop the link, please
I got it. Okay
Dottie does have the link. I
Got the power of the link. There you go. He's also kind of a dumb dumb. Yeah, I'm unless you ever know. Yeah a little bit
How do you feel about death penalty first of all should I think that's great
I think we I think absolutely a hundred percent
Okay, so it should exist now
What rises to the car of punishable by death?
everything. PDF files, beaten up, domestic violence, murder, arrest of a soul.
In this country, women are children, yeah, I think we should publicly do it.
Like domestic violence, like any domestic violence, or are you talking like that involves murder?
Well, I mean, there is a threshold, there is a threshold. If you want me to explain the threshold, I think, like,
Because I you can make the argument that a woman could do it to a man's one. I agree
But if you sit there beating a shit out of your partner, uh, fuck it. We'll put him to the stake here
We're gonna do it publicly. That's what if you're watching that
Yep, if you see somebody on TV that you know, we put him to the stake. That's what you're not gonna do
You're gonna be that car. Are you?
In the heat of the moment who knows
Well, if you fucking grew up, watch the fucking TV and see if you can keep up with it, that's probably not going to do it.
There's blind rage, crimes of passion, you've heard that, I mean these people are not thinking.
They're gonna be thinking a little bit more clearly if we fucking just murk them
Things gotta be fixed man. We can't keep going like this. I can fix these fucking bad bad problem
I'm gonna pay ten dollars
We're not gonna waste years on death row
Victims family
Yeah, I'm not even a bullet don't even use it 30 years later
And you can fucking be done with them just like that you can reuse the knife about 20 times before it gets dull
You want more revenge than it's not revenge dude, it's not revenge then
You get rid of a problem thing is revenge always a problem. Okay. Okay. I mean
Think about the victims do it think think about all these victims the methods that you want to use seem to be a little bit more
No, I mean, okay, like they gotta be harsh these people to be the liberal, okay
Do seem a little excessive a little inhumane if you will
Inhumane to who
To that's being the you mean though the rapist murder that just got a
These people do the stuff and that they should be punished, but I'm saying to be put to death through inhumane means I
Think might be a little more than I'm gonna do publicly. That's what I'm gonna do publicly
Well, now she's fairly inhumane. I mean, you can still get inhumane inhumane is what they didn't hear me
I'm not arguing for their crime. Okay, I'm not
I'm not I can see that they they deserve the death penalty
The real humane thing is to kill them because the inhumane thing would be what I would do to them
well
Arms and legs off and put them in a fucking
It still doesn't solve how well it's a good argument though because it is actually
It's better to kill them humane you saying that if I would do or they need to go they need to be gone
He's saying if I would public if I would just like put them out of their misery
You know, give them the whatever whatever publicly whatever we're gonna do, you know, give them the bullet if I can say that on youtube
uh
That's a good argument. Is that better than like having to spend years in prison?
Here's my argument against that better. Of course, it's a many times better
Yeah, it's a man. Do you know why religion is spread throughout the world because a fear of god keeps people at you know
Why they put that to the sword?
So you gotta put a fucking fear into these motherfuckers that they're not going to be going out there and doing this shit
Once it's a few of them see what's going to happen to them
How does that work for a crime of passion or you know that kind of thing where someone just loses
There is no deterrent at that moment, that's what I'm saying. You killed someone you killed someone you're gone. That's it. You're done
Okay, so
So then it's not a deterrent. It's just that's just the punishment. It's kind of like you know, you fuck around and find out
Exactly you fuck around and find out. This is your gift. You just want a prize
No, I don't I like I said I agree that in the case
Of the death penalty that they deserve it. Okay, I can see that it's just the manner of death
that I would take
Let's not get ridiculous. I don't want to pillow fight to old age or something like that, right?
I just don't want it to be vicious inhumane something that that shows a
deterioration in society
when you start executing your own citizens.
No, don't. That's where the problem lies.
People start talking that shit and then it fucking devolves into,
oh, we're turning into a savage society.
A savage society is when you light a woman on fire on the subway
and she's standing there burning and the cop doesn't do anything about it.
That's a savage society who doesn't do anything.
That's a big problem, man. Yeah, that's I do agree with that
Yeah, that's that's that terrible thing and that would deserve like the death penalty
Let's say in that case if that person was saying when they were doing it
Right thing what I'm saying is you're trying to be ration. What I'm saying is things are so fucking bad
Things are so fucking bad in this country. You got to do something equally as bad to fix it
All right, then when things are fucking semi-normal you can slowly ease up and start going back to normal
But that's how fucking bad it is here now right now
Okay, to what to what extent then if you've got like 50 prisoners now that need to be executed on a day
why we just
Bulldoze them in front of something or what we drop something on them. What do we do in that case?
We put them to death and then you start with the other ones that was coming in
He's got us keep doing it and we gas them or something like that. You got whatever it takes whatever it takes to get rid of them. Yeah
You can't you can't have this debate on what's humane and what's not humane now because you're forgetting about the victims that they took the lives that they've taken
No, nobody's good. Nobody gives a fuck about the victims, dude
Yeah, don't but don't say but no no no no
No, no, no, no, no, no, you're putting you're putting that on me. I never said that I never implied that with
What I'm talking about right? I'm talking about penalizing the person that did it obviously I do I am concerned about the victims
Right, that's why I want justice the victim can't come back to life. I agree
That's why taking revenge on the person that did it is kind of meaningless
It's not a revenge, right? It's already done. It's already happened. It's already been done exactly preventing it would be great
Preventing it from happening again to prevent all things. No, you're taking you're taking that person's life
That person's life is forfeit because of what they did. I know it's not revenge
It's getting rid of believe me
I thought about this down to the individual level to the person that that is the victim like the actual individual
The person that has their own life
like I've thought about this you're not thinking of future victims though when
you if you want to keep this person alive you're forgetting about future
victims I didn't say to keep them alive did I I said that they so what are you
debating we're debating we're debating a humane death yeah I think that's that's
the crux of it that's what I was arguing anyways like this like what the
fuck that lethal injection shit that doesn't work one guy you got like three
No, there are other methods. I'm not saying I get a big rock. I can get a big fucking rock and just knock them over the head
They'll be very cheap
Rocks everywhere
Like I'm not I'm not a far lefty or anything like that
Center left in Canada, which you know, I'm a liberal that puts me like in the middle kind of you could be a fucking liberal man
But think of what you're saying
Just think of what you say I do I've given it thought like I said, I'm not a far left like
Like crank who's just sight that we're recites things, you know, I'm not like that like I've actually thought about this
And I don't like the thought like if my government if if we were doing that if we were executing people in a
Irby I don't believe we do anymore. I think it
It was banished a while ago in any case, but we did we did
Putting someone to death in an inhumane way. We'll just
Will snowball it'll become more inhumane more inhumane it'll start becoming a revulsion within society
That does the way I'm thinking about it. Why we have like an incinerator. That's like a thousand degrees
We just throw them in there
Maybe thousand degrees maybe two thousand maybe they'll burn hot if we can show that that it's it's basically an instant death with you know
No, no real pain. Yeah, I
Don't subscribe to this instant painless death thing the suffering that that person has heaped upon the victim
See, there we go again. You want revenge. That's revenge. I mean, the victim, the victim needs revenge to revenge.
The victim needs it. The penalty is losing their life, and that's all. Not losing their life with a lot of pain.
Well, I mean listen, it doesn't matter what you do if there's any ounce of pain
It's gonna be the same thing. You're gonna say the same thing. So when is it enough?
Are you gonna find something where they die?
Don't be ridiculous and don't start putting like really ridiculous. How are you gonna find something like millisecond?
Milliseconds of pain. I'm not talking like that. I'm talking like, you know, like a slow lingering kind of death something that
Hours or something like that, you know, well, I don't want to go through all the methods
But there's definitely ways, hanging was one of them, usually.
Yeah, I can't say I'm completely against hanging.
There might be some cases where I would be like, okay, not that way,
because there are different ways to do it, right?
But it's not like I'm completely against it. It is a very instant death.
Listen, you know what honestly nobody has to see it. It gets done. You don't have to see it
You don't have to see that I squirm
The guy dies. That's it. If you're not watching it and he doesn't die the first time
We did yeah, that's it. Yeah, we don't have to worry about how how people are killed
You don't have to yeah
But you don't want that to become a usual thing where people don't die on like on the first try right? No, no
You don't want them squirming. I mean geez
So you would make it better so that they actually do
For you think we'll try to make it better for the bleeding heart Canadian. Thank you so much
Thanks, Uncle Sam
No, I mean like I'm not
Like I was trying to say I'm not life is a precious thing news flash a blogger blogger blogger
Make them sorry your buddies here
Yeah, no, not all life is precious, although I do
You know feel like if something is alive, and I'm not talking about
Little I don't know like amoebas and shit like that. I'm talking, you know, like mammals and shit like that if something is alive
It got that life. It kind of deserves to have it and it's no one's right to really come along and take it away
I'm not a geese hunting and that kind of shit. I mean, I I agree
Sometimes it's necessary to do it. What about abortion, but it just in general. No, but the life hasn't been created yet
What do you mean? I
Don't want to get into
Right but like if something already if something has life it it it has earned it just by
having its life yeah summer just by having its life and it doesn't and no one
has the right to take it away unless you know the government unless they do
something and you have the death penalty yeah that's it summer the chicken nugget
let me get some sweet and sour with that it's like are you here I don't know if
people want on man it looks like people are joining in the conversation that's
All right get the sweet and sour anyway. I'll eat it God if you got the link drop it man. I thought I did
It's not there
Coast is in the back. So thank you for sleeping. I try every panel blogger. It's tough keeping up, you know
Sometimes I find there's already one there
Let me see coffee in a sick man. I would love it
That's why if someone else will come up or if you guys want to start talking I would love to go for a cigarette make a coffee
Go ahead. You gotta do what you got to do man
Just don't rape or murder anyone on the way. I gotta fix my butt plug too
Keep that to yourself. I won't be back in a few
Get some chicken nuggets too
So what are you doing in bed?
Yeah, I'm just laying here
Do we bore you?
No
My back just like so I'm laying on my heating head
So what do you can do you can stay up for 24 hours?
Not tonight. No, I mean tomorrow
You know people with you, right
Me yeah
And all of you
Oh, you're not gonna have people there with you. That's crazy. I
Got a 38
I mean at least have somebody you know around you
I'll be around people. Okay. You know what you're doing. I don't need to tell you
I've done it before
Let me know if you need backup. I'll come I'll come flying in
I'll be I'll be not far from my house. So I'm good
Yeah, Canadians Canadians got a different sense they're a little more liberal than the average American liberal
I'm sure they have prime up there
I don't trust no politics
Hmm politicians like
Politicians is the biggest
You see them every day
Like he let people up
Yeah, for God, I can't yell right now
You can't yell for him whoever is his number call him call him on the phone
Somebody does. Oh, Joni does. Joni left
Send over one of the scrap metal guys
It's not funny, I know it's not funny nobody needs that shit
No, I think he caught the guy that did it
He was talking about somebody called BK earlier today. I don't know who it was. I
Don't know. I think you're saying that's the guy
I was a report reported to the cops
Jamie Callum
No sleep for the wicked
Yeah, it's just me. I see this shit too much and
I the only way to solve these hard problems of hard answers
You gotta be really tough
You gotta get enough people without willing to do the the hard things that need to be done to fix society
There's a mixture of both that needs to be done
The hard medium
If it was me, I'd strip these fucking politicians of their wealth. I know that sounds like
Communist but these motherfuckers know they've taken way too much from too many people. I honestly I'd do as much as
Like 99% of their fucking wealth
Yeah, they'd still be you know, they still be fucking millionaires, you know most of them
Yep
Fuck
It's only Pelosi. I think I think she has like 200 million
She's still have two million left
Yeah, exactly
These fucking projects that they build and everything while everybody's fucking living like a slave
It's a fucking sin that that's like the biggest sin you do that's your own people man
Ghost, call Psyche. He has his number.
What do you mean you're lonely? You got Apollo back there. You guys can snuggle.
Oh, Beta has his number. Beta, give him a call.
Oh, he did. Oh, good ghost called him
This boy seems to win holler. Did you wake up was he sleeping?
Well, listen, sir when
When you're when you're called ghost, you know, you can do whatever the fuck you want. You know I'm saying you're it. Oh
Okay, yeah
Would you like me to give you that power Goddy if you if you say I'm ghost
You win you can see
I'll give you that I don't need that kind of calm God. You need it. You need it, sir
Howler no, let's get a fucking debate going. I don't give a fuck all that stash all that fuck it you guys are being weird tonight
What what are you talking about go ahead?
What's wrong when you want to run one started to be good. I'm waiting. Yeah
Yeah, I like the room
Good evening finally somebody that wants to run one. Hello. Hello. Hello
Thank you. Good morning. That's a beautiful fucking man right there
Let's talk about God I know
Well, if you speak English I know
Goddamn
How cool
Let's have some fun. Yes, let's have some fun. Let's have some fun
Apollo go ahead
Could we have a debate? Oh
Do you want to have one? I don't know if anyone actually wants to hear us have a debate, but I'm down the same page here
All right, no pun no pun intended page. We didn't good old page
Give me a reading. Sorry. It's like what's the topic psyche good? I
Why is this man so why is this man? I got a topic
What's up, why does it mean so beautiful?
Is the glasses
Stop talking about me, please. Oh, sorry sir. Hey, look look if you guys want to get gay. I'll leave just let me know
Well, listen
Ten dollars is ten dollars. How gay you want to get sir ten dollars? I wiped my ass with ten dollars. I
Never seen it. It's like you've ever seen it. I'll send it to you. Oh
Send it in this like not to me some of them
ten bucks
That's what you're gonna do. You're gonna sit there and check the fuck up. I'm gonna send it in now
Donuts or donuts donuts donuts get some Christmas
We would say don't let you fat fuck
Like a good donut as much as the next guy come on. Oh, yeah, you also like well psyche likes a good dough
No, you know saying yeah, be this here. Come on. Don't act up
Be to get your Persian ass up here. Come on. Let's go
Is she oh my god, you're fucking up last night, but yeah, if you're Jewish don't come up here
Okay, I'll leave
Paul you and be to get along
Nothing against her and she was so respectful to me so
No opinion about her so that's a yes
She's doing hell nothing not my business our blogger of flirting
Okay, they got something going on. That's cool. This is like a weird. That's like high school kind of like flirtation like a weird
It looks like it is. Yeah, they're trying to like it kind of ignore each other and then trying to pay attention
It's kind of weird
I think in the spirit of an open panel, I think I think Apollo I think you should be able to I think you should run one sir
All right, it was over your head. No, it was over your head
Me no me no paglade in English. I
Know
Jamie it's a Jamie I
Try my best to you know, I and I was nice. I was pleasant in my mail to her and then she like wrote back
You know, I'm not pretty nice so
Sorry, if you don't, yeah, I covered it earlier with a little incident, but somebody, so...
It's cryptic messages.
It was, oh no, I mean, I read this...
That was mysterious.
No, I read the text earlier of a...
Someone I was trying to...
Hey!
I was pleasant to the person
And then the person's like go fuck yourself
Won't be the last time either
You should make a song called go fuck yourself. Hi, Apollo
What did she say? She said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said, she said
Um, respectfully stay the fuck out of it. She
Apologies, I owe her nothing. Oh
Not even a thought contact me again. I'm pressing charges. So take your fake apology and shove it right up your ass
Who's that kitty? Yeah
Well, Katie, right? Wow be it a blogger you taking the link
I'll put the blog off in the crash out on golly. They want to private don't want to take it private
Well, they got to be backstage first, right? So they got to go to their own back
With my Star Wars hey the ghost if you want to fuck thing go to Canada, right? Don't do it here. No, I don't like
Like a certain party
That looks like a baby Fawzi. Can you not give us a some ASMR please sir?
The summer yeah, if you're gonna eat your snacks you in silence. Sorry ghost. No, I'm just just open
Your bag of treats back off see she's down
Oh
Beat us down for a freak off right on right on
Okay, I'll record surreptitiously
Oh, you're gonna watch
I'll play juice
He's a watcher
Apollo serve drinks
Blugger won't mind if I watch
But you love bottled water
You know it, but liquor
Oh shit
And this song is this
We set up your figure now
Here
Oh
We're having a fuck up here.
I've been shut the fuck up.
I just got back here.
Russian friend?
Oh, the Russian girl.
Russian, the Russian.
It's hard to find Zanzi on a beautiful rock
Does she have a name?
Alina, that's what you were saying about earlier, you know, Alina Russia
Like R-U-S-H-A
Was she on camp?
No
I'm Baba Yaga.
Baba Yaga, yeah.
Baba Yaga.
John Wick here.
Dasvidanya, bitches.
You know what that's what made me think that thing and how beautiful that man coke the allow hold on a second
I don't see the Baba Yaga house hold on one second. I can show you. I have it right here
I have the I have the Baba Yaga house
I'll show you bubba bubba. Oh, I'll show you right now. It's not shit. I'm like see like doesn't it walk around. Yeah, look
It's like you got a swarm of bees in there. Oh shit
That is a Baba Yaga house. Where'd you get that?
and
that
The coolest not not like something you think might work for the coolest like, you know, I'm getting a little bit hurt right now
You always leave us
You went into the closet. Do you mind ghost?
Well, yes, he hasn't been in the closet in years
Oh my god
And that closet can you find out of things on a Star Wars shirt? If you don't mind and it's to pay. Oh
And then we're gonna give $10 to join the panel and then we're gonna have another $10
It's called Baba Yaga's house, okay, so I have a couple things
This is a little doll doll. Oh, it's a ram's head
These are actually like really cool dolls, but are they like voodoo?
I would say they have a stiff spears, but here we go. Oh shit. He made a doll.
That's Sam man. He made a doll of Sam man.
I'm cooking pop I'm cooking. Let's play some Mugio
What kind of dolls
They're real demon
Demon dolls
You take someone so you put in the doll I've seen a movie like that before
There's lots of there's plenty of dolls of tails like tradition rituals. What did they call it like?
when he's when they're known around the world of humans being transferred to dolls or transference
Oh my Chuckie
That's Damballa, but that's voodoo that black magic. Damballa is the big serpent like a huge serpent like huge
The one that's gonna swallow the world
Damballa
I'm pretty sure it's a well.
Russia, he's actually actually speak in the road. That's what they literally said
Kick your ass out of the chat. I mean the cons consult nobody
Five foot two
Who the fuck is on 4-foot-11-foot?
That's like a girl's height.
Holy shit.
Is that true?
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
Yikes.
Your cat's tall, I guess.
You just saw your cat's tall.
All right
That's because she doesn't like me on real bad, man.
That's a goddamn beautiful song right there. Shut up, guys.
Who's that?
A beautiful fucking song.
Why is your video filled with guys?
Oh, I'm trying to cut that shot off, babe.
I'm so glad it's good to be here.
Oh, shit.
Do I have to miss you?
To dance?
Yes.
You don't have to always dance.
Because the fuck are you doing?
You always have to miss me to dance.
I'm gonna dance in your back after I talk to you, okay?
Okay.
Oh, I'll go on this one.
Should we stay right for it?
Yeah!
That was fun.
Oh, I'm gonna crash out.
I'm a good boy.
Oh god, he's getting left.
That's good.
That's the key.
Oh, we can crash off?
Oh, we couldn't get them on tonight.
He's the king of the late night ring, crashing out with a heart that sings.
Janner is so half-saint, half-storm, breaking norms just by staying warm.
In a world where I was just a friend.
Last to fake when the screen went dark, he kept me awake all the noise fades, but ghost remains.
Oh
I don't
We don't wanna go to the pond yet
Thanks for everything
Oh, gotta have a good time.
What a fucking beautiful song.
So yeah, it can read.
Now, can I have some mischief myself?
Hold on, I want to show you something, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on,
Not you've actually meet up with information to come out
All right, and I hope you know what it is. I'll give you a hint. Oh, okay. Oh, Tony
You don't want the OF information to come out
You've seen oh, yes, or oh, yes
Oh, they need to know what all the fans
I'm not saying anything else.
OK.
What's he do there?
Play with trains?
Not at him.
Oh, my bad.
boom shaka like a fool
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
oh my shit, turn it off
what is this, is that jade a picket?
oh my shit
look at the moon
oh shit
there's a flower
oh shit, their hands are fucked up, don't even remember
totally good, yeah, vlogger
like we don't all have it over anyway
Will it is funny?
Like when Dex on gossip, you on your job, you hating hard, droppin' links, I tear you apart, you call me cold, I call you fan, you're the sequel out of a plan, say you miss me, we never met, that's a bull kind of internet, I'm a consolation, a common thread, I'm a sermon, you're the unread, why you so upset?
What a dumbass mom.
Why is the name of the stream called Bronze Chicken?
I thought that was a mission to crash off.
No.
Go stay slow
Why are you so obsessed?
Tony Tony
What's this Tony, right? You don't have Tony's fucking with you, right?
He's in love with you. Yeah
Obsessed, and that's why I made the song. But anyway, I have this stuff from King Diamonds on dearly large.
But I would do VIP King Diamonds.
That's right, you did.
And I'll show you the stuff and I got in my merchandise bag the guy gave you a coat didn't he give you a jacket or something?
Hell Walker, you know, but
I'll show you what I got in the thing. That's his legal name to hell Walker. Tell Walker
How you doing?
Fool everybody by taking cancer, and I'm not gonna stop saying that because I a lot of people do
Yeah, yeah, okay, so here's the
Sorry, I did that too. Oh
Hannah's a bitch like she was
You're so right about her god, okay, I'm right about everything
I told her I said gaudi is God and I told her I said go choke on she told me to like go
I'm much on fleas. I told her to
Anyway
Yeah, she's very rude and she's you know, okay, okay, so here we go
I'll put myself. I would like her to apologize
So what is this? I don't know it's like some kind of like I haven't opened this
This is a swag bag. You got pins. Yeah
He paid he it was a VIP. I was like the fourth row or whatever. Okay, it's a very cheap
The coolest thing is where's the dice? Okay. Yeah, there's this nice a dice cool. Oh, yeah, so this is like a little
dice
There's three four five days
You get four hundred for those on eBay right now. Yeah, I know you're probably kid. That's the bag was $400
Yeah, be a piece of guess we have to meet him too. We got these
I
Didn't pay it. No, he took what is that tattoo? Yeah, these are temporary senses. Okay, so there's okay. There's one
There you go over the the kid. Let me get one of
Evil king diamond. Oh, this guy looks like he's trying to hurt now. This king diamond guy
70 years old from Denmark. I mean come on. Yeah, he's an old man. I never was into him
He's actually was really good. It was it was a sanitarium theme. This one says
Grandma
Grandma and then what else we got in this I got the cast this was it was a sanitarium kind of thing
It was actually really cool.
And then there's the guys.
Is there a ghost part?
Who else was there with him?
Was it just him?
No, there was an opening band,
but I don't remember the opening band really.
I mean, I barely really like had seen King Diamond,
but it was really a good show actually.
It was really theatrical.
Like it was like, and they had this like two staircases
and they had this big bat and they kept,
and it was like, you could see inside the bat.
And then they had this one.
We were checking it out.
But I like the big I like these dice the bed like they're really nice dice
Yeah, those are cool
See what you get one forest police. Yeah, you don't mind. Well, that's okay. Yeah, eight or four
Fuck another one. Oh five five six. You got it. There you go. I got it. Okay. That's it one two six
Oh god, he won one person's life.
There you go, there you go, there you go.
There's a little, there's a little, no case.
Oh, he's got a little case.
I think he did something called Moe.
Moe is, Moe is Tibetan divination using the five dice.
And so I can do Moe.
I can do Moe with this.
No money, more problems here.
Follow it.
well, that's true, but I'd still
Depends on who has the money or gold for some of those problems. Oh, Paula. Where are you motherfucking?
I didn't even know things still here
Yeah, I'm just hanging
Lucifer, whoa, I know
He's more of an angel in a saint
Do I have permission to cash out?
Who the fuck are you talking to like that?
Straight up.
As a matter of fact, next time you want to join the panel,
as a matter of fact, you can get $10.
Who the fuck are you talking to like that?
King Diamond.
Oh my god.
Well, if you sat there and shut the fuck up
and put your Star Wars shirt on.
Mace is on here.
Star Wars shirt.
Oh, you have...
Oh, but I did get to there's somewhere in autograph picture. I'm not damn. It feels good to be a ghost
Yeah
That's the coolest thing the worst thing yeah, it's like that that sword came thing that you got the snake
That's not a sword. Don't fuck
You see this nunchucks, it's nunchucks. You're right. Yeah, we're gonna crash out
Or was it it was in San Diego December 1st? It doesn't say who the opening band is
Your affirmation
What a best opening bandit thought was Monster Magnet.
Do you like Charles Claybrew's Chucky the Killer doll?
When I was a kid, I thought that was pretty cool.
I think it's kind of like, you know, a little cheesy.
It's not a bad movie.
Charles Claybrew is the best movie I've ever heard.
Um
What movies do I like for me do I like I would say hereditary I would say like you know get out
I like that's a good fucking movie. Yeah, that was pretty good. I'm not gonna lie. It was pretty good
Hereditary good scary movie that was a good movie and
Are you talking about like payment
Oh, Paimon, yeah, Paimon, yeah, Paimon, yeah.
Well, I think it's Paimon, it's pronounced that.
Well, you can pronounce it both ways.
I mean, he really doesn't care.
Well, what's the correct way? What's the correct way to say it?
Paimon.
Paimon. I say Paimon.
Paimon going to the fair, right? Simple Simon.
Paimon.
Paimon the Paimon.
But
Different answers like payment in the movie that was one of the like the rare like good goaisha films
They usually are like not as good or realistic, but that was pretty
realistic
What do you mean by realistic
Well as to the Goetia the spirit of the Goetia like in the true state like these sometimes they make them like these weird demon monsters
I thought I saw a pieman or paper movie where it was on it was my best friend's exorcism
I think it was called and it's like some scary like like little like you know
I'm gonna be honest with you so you're my good friend, but you gotta be careful the way you're talking about shit
Why?
Because and mother fuck dirt like it's just like a fear movie like if you ask for shit to come in guess what's gonna happen
Well, you well, we we actually have power over demons and so not really scared
Well, yeah, the power of Christ definitely does do that, but you don't believe in Christ
Right, but it's like even the humans have power over demons. What kind of power do you have?
I've got a power to I have a demon trying to if there was a demon trying uh
Because we're we're like a level higher the angels don't have free will because they're just gods will
What are you going to do give them a card the most powerful thing you can be actually
Pretty cool loose other than god itself, right?
um
There we go. There's lola. Oh baby
I
Don't think
Unless we get a $10 donation
I hear you $10 I raise it to 20
I
Yeah, we've already
Tomorrow we're gonna be discussing cyber Satan
Cyber six, but you know what? I'm today's payday. I'm happy my book. Actually, that's okay
I didn't get paid
Mesa said oh, he said cat. I'm sorry. I said
My cat was Mason like to join the panel Mason. Come on. You can play with my puss. There's little
You guys should probably be lonely. He's kind of
He's got a bit of that tizum, you know, I'm saying I'm not saying it's a bad thing
Yeah, we can see it in your face
Fucking beautiful song you play just now we call cats I they take your breath away by the way second you send that to me
Which one? That new go song?
The new one. That was beautiful song.
Play the thing that is song. That's a good one.
Okay, I'll play the thing that is song.
Yeah, I got to play thing that is song.
Yeah, that's a good one.
You will listen to it and you will enjoy it, okay?
It's too good. It's not right to be for you thing.
It's a good song.
It is a good song.
Alright.
I have it right here, it's next to this...
That sounds like a dumbass song, that sounds like a dumb-dumb song.
That sounds like an old song.
That sounds like an idiot song.
Yeah, it sounds like...
Let's get moving with it.
That honor
Playin' the ghost one
What's that, what's that girl's name with the boots on?
That's the one I got, yeah!
Nancy Tanatra?
Yeah, yeah, he has that little voice in it
That was like a numb dumb song
Oh my god, we love this song
No, it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's
He stands his ground, clears the gloom
You question your gods, defend your rights
And still wish you peace at the end of the fight
Generous heart, never cruel or mean, Searching for truth somewhere between me and I hope he finds beauty in the life he still gives, maybe somewhere between me and I hope he finds beauty in the life he still gives, maybe somewhere between me and I hope he finds beauty in the life he still gives, maybe somewhere between me and I hope he finds beauty in the life he still gives, maybe somewhere between me and I hope he finds beauty in the life he still gives, maybe somewhere between me and I hope he finds beauty in the life he still gives, maybe somewhere between me and I hope he finds beauty in the life he still gives, maybe somewhere between me and I hope he finds beauty in the life he still gives, maybe somewhere between me and I hope he finds beauty in the life he still gives, maybe somewhere between me and I hope he finds beauty in the life he still gives, maybe somewhere between me and I hope he finds beauty in the life he still gives, maybe somewhere between me and I hope he finds beauty in the life he still gives, maybe somewhere between me and I hope
Who sees what I see, the brave kind of gentle that lets others be free.
Think that is bold and bold, warm in the cold.
Or more than gold, he fights for fair, stands for the truth.
That is the reporter of the documentary
That is Michael George
I have been to Niagara Falls
So you recognize it
Yes, exactly
This song is so good
It was
That made you laugh
Sound like shit. Go song is way better
Different man, they're different styles
We're different we have different styles
You should have I was talking to loser a child, I'm sorry
That's wrong sound like ass
Oh come on ghost please don't insult me.
Well listen the ghost song was way fucking better.
What's the psyche song? Is there a psyche song?
Yeah, it's a psyche song.
Yeah it's called Dung Dung.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Okay.
I don't know. Is there a Psyche song?
There's like 30.
Oh, yeah, there is a Psyche song.
That Psyche song.
Father's Psyche song.
I will get some credit, though.
That song, okay, my bad.
It did sound good.
Psyche song was a lot better.
Is this one? Hold on.
Did I ever miss you at that show?
Cards were true.
Stars have whispered to us.
What about double the speed?
It already sounded like that shit off. Shut up blogger. Did they go freak out?
Precure I don't because I didn't get the
Photos I can't be I didn't get the link man. Oh, well
This is a great sound to us that one
That was concerning hobbits or the oriental you thought we wouldn't recognize it, but I did
I like, I do like this song.
It's just the way I feel about it.
Let's make it, let's make it like your daddy.
Feel for me like that.
Oh, Miss Yumi, bring me some food.
Hakuna Matata!
That's her I like this. Yeah, I'd like this one with the Japanese. Yeah, it sounds good. Yeah
He's not two faces three face
You have to recognize his symbolism.
I'll tell you what I got you now.
That's something pretty good though.
He's got a blue flame, you know what that means.
Sartre?
He's in the closet.
He's hot.
Oh, God.
Good point. Haha, I knew what to do.
Is that the best way?
This is like watching Titanic all over again.
It's always got a snake in the picture.
Hecate, hecate.
Hakuna titi.
Hecatiti.
You pregnant?
Not my babe, what's that?
Hey Javi, I've got a question for you, who is your son-in-law?
The both sides of you.
Who doesn't make the noise?
Yeah, he does.
He's identifying with Tech of Tim.
That's Latin.
So he ain't even put on your eyeglasses, please.
What a beautiful man right there.
He's surrounded by snakes.
Fuck it, you guys wanna rock one?
like my part of it favors that kind of it's good shit. Thank you. The pan flute. I do like
well, so I got a problem with you, brother. You're wet. I got a problem with you. You have a
problem with me. Okay, good. You call on Jamie. You're a BFF.
Well, Russia, Jamie, a lot of people,
BFF is like, you know, I can have a lot of great friends.
Listen, you used to call me your BFF.
What what the heck a day? Yeah, what the heck a day? Um, the heck a day?
Actually this one I like this one too
Shit
That was that was fucked up that was rude by the way my phone is all fucked up. I gotta take off. I'll see you guys
Okay, bye. Bye. No
Bye
No
I don't know. I can't actually I can. Um, I need to focus. Okay. Um, it's the, it's like, there's a good game.
Can you draw me like one of your friends girls? Yes, I can. Should I please? Yeah. Okay. Um, I can't see very well. Oh, hold on.
No, I'm not going to stop.
And this is what you think about things.
Crown of truth, robe of flame, calling out the trolls by name.
He reads the cards, they bear the soul, every panel's a cosmic scroll.
Lenors at his feet like a priest, his feet line, tricks and lullag are the shrine.
He speaks and riddles, laughs at sin, Rudy and Marbles just stare at him.
As you'll see he breaks your doubt with cosmic
He's seen the lies, the feuds, the fall
He built a verse to outshine them all
He don't flinch when the weirdos call
He just grins, says welcome y'all
Wisdom wrapped in meme and madness
Love and logic, joy and sadness
He turned your chaos into art
He'll roast your soul and read your heart
Light the candle, hear the purr
Truth is closed, don't make it stir
Every troll, every broken soul
Finds a home
one verse one show he spins the stars and makes them glow father psych keeper of night
cat daddy walks between wrong and right
did you hope i looked that good when i'm that old you know did you really hope i looked that good
Um, is everyone having fun?
I hope everyone's having fun.
I'm good.
How about having a ghost sober of a time?
You have a ghost sober of a time?
That is the goal.
Okay, I found one more.
One more.
She's the season for it, so.
Last one.
Damn.
Damn, you're just gonna ignore us.
Go ahead.
Help me.
Help me, John.
That's fucked up, Gary.
John.
Wow.
Yeah.
Always think wave
Seeds on shit.
I don't know if that was locked as monster, perhaps. Perhaps. Perhaps.
Can we start by slapping your fucking keyboard?
That's not me.
No, he's talking to me.
Making me hear it.
He has to pay ten bucks to talk to me, okay?
Like, I know that was directed at me.
that he needs to pay $10 in order to speak to me.
You know what I can do right now, thing?
You know what I can actually do?
Stike, I believe your guess is-
Yes, I think he has to-
Without-
You know what I can actually do, sir?
Do the preliminary responsible thing.
If he would like to apologize to me, you know what?
I'll be good to say tonight, I'm gonna apologize to you.
I'm sorry for saying that, but.
Listen, if you apologize to me, I won't get you to fuck off this fan. All right now
Well, it's only been two days we've been arguing about this shit to say you sorry
Okay, thank you
No, listen sir, I need at least ten dollars before I think I'm starting to hook this thing wait thing
Well, all right thing
Let's have a ten dollar off and everybody
Well listen, I at least need to donate something, you know
Oh, it's sidewalks thing is a wonderful awesome. I like I'm adorable just
Yeah, it's in a pony tail bun thing. Whatever. Yeah, that's a beautiful man right there
What about it nothing I said it goes like it what about it
Because look it takes the hair out of my face and it looks like a different color hair or different hair. I
Do have a nice who said I don't know your fucking here out then who had a nice who isn't a nice jaw
Listen, sir, you don't like to have like hair in your eyes. You probably shouldn't grow it out
You look into my eye
You can you know what color I have actually
like
I color you can see my color
By the way, I'm frozen the fuck up
You mean to say I'm sorry. No, I can't tell at least I can't tell they're green
Are they okay?
No, you're gonna leave me here with thing
Does that worry you
No, not at all. I would never be bored by you sir trust us
You would never be bored by me. Is that what you said? I'd never be worried by you at all
Never a day in your life. You can never worry me. I
Don't know
Well, you don't know what you don't know about go ahead and explain. What do you not know about I think if I really
Hard I could make you worried, but yeah, go ahead and do it
I don't want to put in the effort first of all
I don't want to put in the effort, but you don't want to put in the effort
You don't know you just made the fuck up. You don't the fuck you're talking about
Listen, sir, you can never worry me. I'm the person that's here to worry you
You should be careful what the fuck you're talking about
Yeah, listen you could never worry girl. So you know better. You're a good boy
You know, I didn't say that you couldn't worry me. I just you're the one that said I would never worry
I'm talking you thought I crashed out about like
Me saying like oh you said I have to give 10 hours to join the panel
You thought that was a crash out. Would you like to see a red one?
Didn't say you had to give ten dollars did I we've been through this how many times now five six times
Hey, okay, so luck finally arrives for three zodiac signs on October 21st, okay
So I'll tell you about this so I do astrology okay October 21st better luck
It's finally arriving for three zodiac signs the Scorpio moon brings intensity
focus and opportunities for transformation.
On Tuesday, we will feel a very intense rush of luck,
and for those who are ready to act decisively
and trust their instincts,
it'll be even more powerful.
Unexpected opportunities, fortune encounters,
and helpful twists of fate may appear on Tuesday,
and we are ready and waiting for them.
Nobody's caught a square during the Scorpio Moon.
For these astrological signs,
the energy is especially potent.
Fortune favors us,
whether now or personal or professional matters.
We've been preparing for this.
Bring it. Okay. It says bring it. Okay. Hold on. Who's coming up? Oh, who's will goes? Okay. Oh, okay. And so Aries, okay
I'm gonna skip over Aries. Okay. Okay. Who else? Taurus and Gemini. Okay. We're gonna do those three signs
Might be a good day for you
Um, these zodiac signs are most likely to become rich. Let me see. I don't know probably
Yeah, so what's your sign or your Libra? Okay, so the thing that is is a Libra, right? I remember that
Once October ends who will benefit the most I guess let me see
Taurus cancer
Virgo Scorpio
What's that Aquarius Capricorn Oh Capricorn Capricorn may have felt like they were hiking uphill in October. Yes rude
They can finally see the top the energy in front of you foster success structure rewards will last a long time
Even working hard behind the scenes and others are starting to notice your path is stable again
Whether with money emotions or work the annoyance of waiting goes away and progress takes its place
November is a time when you know all your waiting was something real. You're ready to move on school
You have developed a strong foundation.
Ghost keeps going on and off.
Hey, who's Alex?
Who's Alex at McQueen and my PD?
We're still going.
I have like a half of a hurricane punch.
So I'm going to drink this fucking drink.
I love you, Alex.
Get back up here.
Get your ass up here.
I don't care if EZ tries to private strike,
but I'm just going to fix the stream anyway.
Get on up here, Alex.
Come on, I love you.
Come on, buddy.
I love you, Alex, and the people that people that people have said, I didn't ban you from anything. Summer didn't pay. Anyway, the thing is, um, oh, hold on. Hello?
I'm not kicking you off. No, it's like, it's, I don't know what's doing it.
Who's they?
You can't, hold on, you can't talk in the chat?
From the panel or the chat? Or the chat? I'm not kicking out of the...
No, I don't know what's happening on the panel. I don't know why that's happening.
I'm not doing it. I'm the only one that can kick you from the panel, okay?
Like the ghosts or something?
Okay, I don't know what's happening with your technical difficulties. I'm sorry. It's goes tober fest. Okay, you're
Okay, I love you
He'll appreciate the
Yeah, I love you at the end. I don't know. He says he's being kicked off by somebody
But I don't know anybody off here. Okay. Oh, oh Alex McQueen
Yo
Alex I
Didn't do it man. I didn't kick him off this time. You don't have the power to kick him off
I only I have the power. I mean, I'm learning. I'm learning stuff. I'm hacking. I'm learning hacking shit
I'm going old out, baby
There he's back and I'm hacking everybody shit. Don't kick off ghost. It goes sober. He's not allowed to be kicked
I found my passion psych is dropping 12-inch cocks in everyone's face. I love it. Where's mine?
Can I can I get one? No, don't don't tell me they don't tell me. I don't want it
There's a good panel. All right, but I'll put like seven hours. No, I mean in my actual mouth. I want your dick
Okay, okay
Well, somebody's gonna have to travel these are you to New York or meet a Cali
Summer
So I'm in love
Wait, wait, wait now we're in a love triangle
It was just you and me dick and I know you like you like ghosts a little but nothing that is in there
So now we're having a like his bald head
Oh, it's heber hammer. It's like I like bring it bitch
You know who's bullhead I like all J-dog. He's got a lump at the top. He looks like a fucking garden though
You see J-dog this is it is weird. Well, that shit is shaped
It's like a pair with a little lump on top. How are you my guy?
He looks like a little Mexican
Garno.
This is my sexy Hebrew hammer.
Hebrew.
Are you going to get flexed tonight?
Am I gonna flex for you, baby? No, not tonight. I'm it's too early for that prison body. You have a prison body
Morning it's six in the morning. What do you mean?
Alice has been in prison for ten years and he didn't have sex one time with you buddy
I'm not gay dick. You had blowjob in the shower one time, right?
Never never you jerked off in front of your cell. No man is
This man you let him watch you let him watch you right?
Alex, it takes two men at a time.
Lofi?
What if you were doing it with your eyes closed
and then you're like, that's a lot of pent-up tension, baby.
You need to relax.
10 years.
Imagine coming out of that shit.
Imagine the first pussy.
That guy had a piece of this.
That's just that shit, huh?
He still went to the hospital for covering that bitch.
He did not look a dirty old baseball glove.
Oh, come on.
12 hours straight, a marathon.
I'll be the catcher. So the gentleman next to you psyche the gentleman in his chair
Hi, nice to meet you sir. I see I've seen you on a few panels and
Yeah, you look good psyche
You look really good actually. Your hair is not all really nilly.
It's not.
It's in our beautiful face. It's a good cheap phone structure. No, you look healthy earlier in the chat
They look you look healthy now because you put your hair back like what the fuck these people are crazy
He looks exactly the same like he always looked
Ghosts
But we can't even
Am I on camera? Is this really happening? It goes getting kicked off by a magical source and he's calling the site
This is like a funny
Ghosts, right? Yeah
magical ghost kicking off ghost
And he's holding site
Are you on a pile of garbage psyche, honey? Is it trash bags?
He's like swimming in trash
the
Oh
What the hell is ghost bro, he must be freaking out
Stop kicking off
He's asking for the link for crying out loud what that was going on that there was ghost over
So, you should have the lake here. I'm gonna put that.
Heber hammer, can you put it inside of me, please?
Oh, you see?
Whoa, you like this out of that.
That was pretty forward.
the
Who does that say harder on the can? Hey, Alex, would you like to know what would you like to be?
Oh, wait, what you want to run it? We're gonna set this up the fuck up. I would love to run
Psych you got rid of us and didn't summer to psych
He was boxing people you should have a dick like
You that picture of hammer reminds it's that an actor is that
Million
My steve it's a galaxy girl. Bye-bye. Oh my god
Bye-bye first person shower. I think you should go bye-bye who?
Do you know what I mean?
Watch this watch that thing that goes are you jelly goes
Don't be jelly.
You like my powers?
Big pipes.
Don't be jelly.
Streamer of the month.
I was never streamer of the month.
I'm really insulted.
What the fuck is streamer of the month bro?
It was your month and fucking
Mr. Big Pipes and I was it.
What am I this isn't gonna like me after this and I haven't done anything wrong. I've been just chillin
You're the one kicking him. Aren't you all hammer you got you've made him a co-host at home
Somebody's kicking him, bro
Somebody's kicking him, baby
Oh my god, whoa psyche. Come on. Really didn't
Really didn't people have a journey. That's like did you go to the Alex New Queen School of Detection?
Hmm
Can I stick oh
Oh, well, we're gonna end alive
I guess what what happened? I didn't pour bomb
I don't know why he's all has an arm for me for whatever reason all of a sudden I love ghosts, but whatever man
50. How much is that 20?
Bye bye
Well, I made you what didn't summer give you 25 so no 45 hey for 50 bucks. I'll flash you my chocolate surface
She didn't
Got him. Oh well, I can edit this out and I'm fine. Bye. They got you